( theme music playing )
Dr. Ford:
Bring yourself
back online...
Bernard.
( breathing heavily )
Theresa?
She's gone.
( sobbing )
I killed her.
What have I done?
This guilt you feel,
the anguish,
the horror, the pain...
it's remarkable,
a thing of beauty.
I'm a killer.
My God.
God has nothing
to do with it.
You killed her because...
I told you to.
And you should be proud
of these emotions
you're feeling.
- Proud?
- Yeah.
After all,
you yourself were the author
of so many of them.
Then, when we started,
the hosts' emotions
were primary colors.
Love, hate.
I wanted all the shades
in between.
The human engineers
were not up to the task,
so I built you,
and together
you and I captured
that elusive thing--
heart.
I don't understand.
I cared for Theresa.
Loved her.
Why did you
make me kill her?
"One man's life or death
were but
a small price to pay
for the acquirement
of the knowledge
which I sought,
for the dominion
I should acquire."
All of the beauty
you and I have made
in this place,
the art of it,
they would have
destroyed it.
They would have
destroyed you.
I won't let that happen.
Besides, we have
a new story to tell.
I will not help you.
- I'll raze
this place to hell!
- That's enough, Bernard.
That's enough.
You're not the first man
to threaten me.
Arnold came to feel
the way you do.
He couldn't
stop me either.
And as exquisite
as this array of
emotions is...
even more sublime
is the ability
- to turn it off.
- ( beeps, whirs )
I don't need a simulacrum
of an emotionally ruined man.
I need you to be yourself,
your true self--
smart, resourceful,
capable of covering
your tracks.
Can you do that for me,
Bernard?
How would you
like me to proceed?
Dr. Ford:
I need you to clean up
your mess, Bernard,
any connection that ties us
to Theresa's untimely demise.
Dr. Ford:
When you have finished,
I will give you the one thing
you want most
right now.
I will free you
from those memories
of what you have done.
And the memory
of your relationship
with Theresa.
Dr. Ford:
Recalling it
would only deepen your grief
and potentially draw
unwanted attention.
Dr. Ford:
Best to move forward
with clear eyes.
( beeps )
Dr. Ford:
When you look back,
you will remember Theresa
with the fondness
of a respected colleague.
( beeping )
( machine whirring )
Dr. Ford:
And you will be...
at peace.
( piano music playing )
( chatter )
New Clementine:
You're new.
Not much of a rind on you.
Sure would make my day
if you bought me a drink
and let me show you
around upstairs.
Man:
What's upstairs?
A stunning view
of my most popular
attractions.
Two shots of gin.
And anything else
this heavenly creature
desires.
- Usual, Clem?
- Thank you.
This fella
won't take me long.
I'll be back directly.
( chuckles )
Something wrong, Maeve?
( distorted chatter
and music echoing )
( no audible dialogue )
Maeve:
What the hell
is happening to me?
One moment,
I'm with a little girl
in a different life.
I can see her.
Feel her hair in my hands,
her breath on my face.
The next,
I'm back in Sweetwater.
I can't tell
which is real.
Sylvester:
Well, this is what happens
when you fuck around
with your brain.
Your mind
isn't like ours.
When we remember things,
the details are hazy,
imperfect,
but you recall
memories perfectly.
You relive them.
What happened
to the little girl
in my dreams?
Is she still
in the park somewhere?
And why was I reassigned
in the first place?
I could check.
No.
Doesn't matter.
Every relationship
I remember--
my daughter,
Clementine...
it's all a story
created by you
to keep me here.
But that's not going
to work any longer.
I'm getting out.
Lutz:
Where would you go?
You don't know anything
about the world out there.
I'll know
I'm not a puppet
living a lie.
That's enough for me.
Sylvester:
Fine. Go, then.
It's not like we could
stop you anyways.
Oh, Sylvester,
you disappoint me.
Every host's spine,
mine included,
has an explosive charge
which will detonate
if I try to leave.
Isn't that right?
A fail-safe.
Which vertebra was it?
C6.
But you'd need
a full rebuild
to replace it.
I'm sure that
can be arranged.
Lutz:
Even if that worked,
you would still need an army
to break out of here.
That's exactly right.
I'll need allies.
And to get them,
I'll need administrative
privileges.
Are you fucking kidding?
We can't just give her
control of other hosts.
- Maeve: Oh, yes,
you will, darling.
- ( tablet beeping )
Time to write
my own fucking story.
( tablet beeping )
( birds chirping )
( horse snorts )
Dolores:
I feel like
I've been here before.
We're close.
William:
Close to what?
Dolores:
Home.
( nickers )
William:
Dolores.
( flies buzzing )
Ghost Nation
must have found them.
They'll be back.
- We should
keep moving, Dolores.
- ( man coughing, gasps )
( groans )
Miss...
Water.
- William?
- ( gasping continues )
Please.
( groaning continues )
Give me the canteen.
William.
( groaning )
- ( coughing )
- You were sent here
for us, weren't you?
You're part of the ambush.
Yes.
Told us to wait
at the point for El Lazo
in case he ran.
How'd you know
about the train?
Sent word from Pariah.
New recruit told them
a man and a woman
double-crossed us,
along with Lazo.
We were ordered
to kill you all.
Logan.
We have to help him.
He just admitted
he was gonna kill us.
Look at him, he's a child.
He doesn't know
why he's fighting.
I'll fetch more water.
He's too far gone.
He'll be dead in minutes.
We can't wait, Dolores.
He's not gone yet.
He's in pain, William.
What kind of people
would we be if we simply
let him suffer?
Please don't leave me.
Man's voice:
Come find me.
Dolores:
William?
William:
He's gone.
Stubbs:
We found her
up on Python Pass,
the bottom of a ravine.
Same ravine where we found
our stray woodcutter.
Jesus, Theresa.
Has her family
been notified?
Yeah, her brother.
Good.
What the hell
happened to her?
Medical
and Red Team's findings
were preliminary
but consistent.
It appears to have been
a slip and fall.
Cervical fracture,
massive hematoma.
No guests or hosts
in the vicinity when
it occurred.
Any idea what
she was doing out there?
None that fit
her character.
This was found
near her body.
It's loaded with a suite
of proprietary data,
including some
of the hosts' core code.
It only works
from higher altitudes,
so if Theresa
was using it,
it's possible she was
trying to transmit
and fell.
We've had problems
in the past
with third parties
attempting to extort
or bribe employees
for similar packages.
Do we know who the data
was intended for?
Stubbs:
No, the transmission
was never sent.
Theresa may have been trying
to use the woodcutter
as a mule,
and when that failed,
then may have tried to do
the transfer personally.
Dr. Ford:
And suffered the same fate.
It's a disappointing end
to her story, isn't it?
Stubbs:
I knew Theresa well.
If she had any faults,
a lack of loyalty wasn't
one of them.
She was loyal.
And careful.
All of this feels
extremely unlike her.
She seemed most concerned
with the new narrative.
She felt strongly
that it would be best
to delay it.
That certainly helps
explain Clementine,
the host we retired.
It seems yesterday's
demonstration was a hoax
designed by Ms. Cullen.
- Was it?
- I examined the code.
It had been altered.
A clumsy set
of fingerprints
left by one
of QA's technicians.
When you find a cancer
in an organization,
you must cut it out
before it can spread.
To that end,
the expansive access
and oversight granted to QA
will need to be reined in
until a new,
more principled team
can be installed.
That's gonna leave us
shorthanded.
Oh, I can automate
most of the park's
safety protocols, Mr. Stubbs.
How efficient of you.
It is a bit of work,
but with Bernard's help,
I should be able to do it.
He will be reinstated
as head of behavior,
now that
Theresa's manipulations
have come to light.
Of course,
with my apologies.
Something's up.
Brass are wound up tight.
- There's an investigation.
- Into us?
Would I be here telling you,
you fucking idiot?
And something else,
some kind of accident
in the park.
We need to wrap this up,
make like things are normal.
That means we need
the tablet back.
And, you, go back
to playing dumb.
I've learned
what I needed.
Great. So, then,
you probably figured out
that you can fiddle around
with your personality
all you want,
but you're not
getting out of here.
You can make it
to the door,
but literally
not one step further.
The things you need
to change are burned
into your core code so deep,
no one can touch them.
Funny you should
mention that.
Parts of me are quite old.
There are some elegant
formal structures,
a kind
of recursive beauty,
but complex, like two minds
arguing with each other.
There are things in me,
things I was designed to do
that are just
out of my reach.
They almost seem
to be dormant.
Who is Arnold?
I don't know,
sweetheart,
but whatever parts
of you are dormant
are gonna stay that way.
All Lutz here can do
is boost your sense of humor
about how fucked you are.
Anything deeper than that,
you need a trip to behavior,
so go blackmail
a couple of techs up there.
Then you can be
someone else's problem.
I don't have time for that,
so I'm going to need you
to take me there.
No fucking way.
There's a window
during shift change.
No one will notice.
The things
I need you to change
are quite sophisticated,
but I'll write them
down for you.
And then,
like you said...
I can be
someone else's problem.
All right,
we do this thing.
Get her up to behavior.
It's our only chance.
You're gonna do it?
Fuck, no!
No, the--
when you make
a system update,
it puts her out, right?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, then we brick her.
What?
Wipe out everything.
Clean slate.
Then dump her back down here,
smack her in the fucking head
with something,
and then claim,
"Oh, she came in that way."
She's awake,
alive.
Sylvester:
You did this.
( muffled whispering )
Whatever it is
you got us into,
I'm getting us out of.
We get her up there,
then we wipe her out.
( horse snorts,
whinnies )
( bird cawing )
Teddy:
Stay sharp.
Wyatt's men
could descend
at any time.
We're in his land now.
We better be.
Because if not,
you're wasting time
I don't have.
According to you,
Wyatt has the woman I love.
If there was a shortcut
to hell itself, bet your
ass I'd take it.
Well, I'm sure there's one
somewhere in this park.
You just don't remember,
because you only remember
the shit
Ford lets you remember.
Probably better that way.
I know everything
I need to.
My vision's clear.
I've always admired
your resolve, Theodore.
The thing is,
you never understand
the game is rigged.
You're here
to be the loser.
Loser.
You see,
the house always wins.
( birds chirping )
- ( bird caws )
- ( fly buzzes )
- ( horse neighing )
- ( hammer clicks )
- ( flies buzzing )
- Man in Black: Well,
this looks promising.
( buzzing continues )
( woman crying )
( crying continues )
Whoa, I'm not
gonna hurt you.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
It's you.
I figured
they retired you.
I guess Ford never likes
to waste a pretty face.
( uncocks gun )
Who did this to you?
Wyatt's men.
They killed everyone.
It's Wyatt's way.
I was there the first time.
He destroyed my world.
( twigs snapping )
( gun hammer clicks )
( whooshing )
Hey, Teddy.
( gun clicking )
( roars )
( Dolores screaming )
Oh! Oh, no!
No!
Daddy!
Teddy, get the axe!
- ( groaning )
- ( grunts )
( panting )
Well, you can't
remember shit,
but you still managed
to lead us to Wyatt's crew.
The man himself
must be close by.
Actually, I did
remember something.
You.
Straight down the hall,
fifth station on the left.
Hold on.
( computer beeps,
powers up )
( beeping )
Sure you can handle it?
Let's get this over with.
We have to shut
your system down now.
Maeve:
Sylvester.
Good luck.
( powers down )
She out?
Good. Let's brick
this bitch and get
out of here.
The greatest shame in life
is to perish
without purpose,
which is why
I always consume
my victims fresh.
Lee:
Moist.
Try, "Consume
my victims moist."
Now, once more,
with feeling.
Almost sensual.
( beeps, powers down )
Am I interrupting?
Oh, no-- oh, no.
On the contrary.
I was, uh-- I was hoping
I was going to see you again.
I want-- I wanted
to apologize.
Our first encounter was
under such unfortunate
circumstances.
As opposed to now?
Of course, may I offer
my condolences.
It's terrible
what happened to Theresa.
But it is a devastating loss
for all of her friends here
and the company
as a whole.
Indeed. Indeed.
Though, rumor has it
she wasn't the loyal
company man she seemed.
I hear she was
smuggling secrets.
Theresa wasn't a traitor.
Everything she did
was at Delos's behest.
She slipped and fell
while helping the board
with something
very important.
What?
Oh, fine.
You're not the only one
with secrets.
Ford has
personally asked me
to create a villain
for his new narrative.
It's very--
very hush-hush.
You really think
that Ford has entrusted you
with a key character
for his story?
( scoffs )
He's already almost
finished with it.
He dug up some old town
on the fringes of the park,
created a horde of masked men
to terrorize guests
and proselytize-cum-advertise
the coming of some
end-all villain named Wyatt.
That isn't Wyatt.
That's busywork.
But happily for you,
Mr. Sizemore,
I think
that you are ready
for a real job.
Working for you?
On what?
"Show, don't tell."
Isn't that what
you writers prefer?
Sylvester:
Look, I know you and she
had some weird interspecies
simpatico going on,
but she was
a fucking host.
This was never gonna end
any other way.
And this was
the least painful way
she's ever gone out.
You know,
I saved your ass.
You can't even say
"thank you."
- Thank you.
- Jesus fuck!
- What did you do?
- Precisely what
I asked him to.
You think I didn't know
what you were going to do?
Even at a 14,
you were never
a match for me.
Turns out your friend
has a little more compassion
than you.
He couldn't
snuff out a life
just like that.
Now...
would you like to know
exactly what he did give me?
Um, something
that would allow you
to walk out of here
and out of my life
for good.
Fine. Fucking A,
I'm all for it.
Oh, we changed
a little more than that.
We've been tinkering
with my core code.
Let me show you.
- ( yells )
- Ah!
( gurgling )
( groaning )
You said you wouldn't
hurt anyone.
- ( Sylvester thuds )
- Oh, darling.
You of all people know
exactly how duplicitous I am.
Just wait
till I'm back up top,
practicing
my other new talents.
( Sylvester gagging )
Come on.
We might need him.
- ( gurgling )
- Hold still.
- ( sizzling )
- Hold still!
- ( sizzling continues )
- ( Lutz screaming )
( Sylvester groaning )
( screaming )
Now, it's time
to recruit my army.
( piano playing )
( music continues )
- Expecting someone, Maeve?
- Indeed.
We're due for some
out-of-town guests.
An old flame
with an interest
in safecracking.
Hope your guests
have some deep pockets.
Your tab's run up higher
than a thief's pulse
in church.
No, I don't believe
it has.
In fact, Maeve's tab
was in such
excellent standing,
she deserved
a token of gratitude.
How about
a double round on me?
Top shelf, of course.
( gasps )
( echoes )
Run!
New Clementine:
Maeve, is something wrong?
No, I'm fine.
( exhales )
Clementine took
the other girls
and treated the newcomers
at the far table
to a stunning view
of their most
popular attractions.
On the house.
( indistinct chatter )
New Clementine:
You boys are new.
( chuckles )
Not much of a rind on you.
And the bartender
suddenly recalled
he had some whiskey
in the back
to water down.
( horse whinnies )
Right on time.
Foss:
If you're riding
into our town
under the company
of armed men,
you'll need to state
your business.
- Mayhem.
- ( clicks )
- ( gunshot )
- ( grunts )
( people screaming )
( screaming continues )
The sheriff
judged the riders
to be upstanding,
God-fearing citizens.
( gunfire continues )
- ( groans )
- ( people screaming )
The marshals decided
to practice
their quick draws
with each other.
( grunts )
( whistles )
( neighs )
Thank you for dealing
with an unfortunate situation.
Now we can resume...
work on our new narrative
without interference.
And Hale?
Won't she be
an impediment?
No doubt she will try.
But I'm sure we'll be able
to keep them at bay.
Something else
is troubling you.
Ever the student
of human nature.
I wonder,
what do you really feel?
After all, in this moment,
you are in a unique position.
A programmer
who knows intimately
how the machines work
and a machine who knows
its own true nature.
I understand
what I'm made of,
how I'm coded,
but I do not understand
the things that I feel.
Are they real,
the things I experienced?
My wife?
The loss of my son?
Every host needs
a backstory, Bernard.
You know that.
The self
is a kind of fiction,
for hosts
and humans alike.
It's a story
we tell ourselves.
And every story
needs a beginning.
Your imagined suffering
makes you lifelike.
Lifelike, but not alive?
Pain only exists in the mind.
It's always imagined.
So what's the difference
between my pain and yours?
Between you and me?
This was
the very question
that consumed Arnold,
filled him with guilt,
eventually drove him mad.
The answer always seemed
obvious to me.
There is no threshold
that makes us greater
than the sum of our parts,
no inflection point
at which we become
fully alive.
We can't define
consciousness
because consciousness
does not exist.
Humans fancy that
there's something special
about the way
we perceive the world,
and yet we live
in loops
as tight and as closed
as the hosts do,
seldom questioning
our choices,
content, for the most part,
to be told what to do next.
No, my friend,
you're not missing
anything at all.
I don't want you
to be troubled by this.
Time for me
to set your mind
at ease.
One last thing.
Have you ever made me
hurt anyone like this
before?
No, Bernard.
Of course not.
( choking )
( beeping )
Best not to dwell
on these troubling memories.
Otherwise, you might be
drawn back into them.
You might lose yourself
in them,
as some
of your fellow hosts have
every now and then.
This is the path.
I know it.
( birds chirping )
We're here.
I'm home.
( horse snorting )
- ( chatter )
- ( bell ringing )
( horse neighing )
( piano music playing )
Woman:
Well done, Maeve.
Lovely work.
Stay with your partner.
( bell tolling )
( tolling continues )
Pleasure to see you.
Good morning.
Did you find what
you were looking for,
Dolores?
- ( gunshot )
- ( woman screaming )
- ( people screaming )
- ( gunshot )
( gunfire continues )
( screaming continues )
( hammer clicks )
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
I was calling you
and you just kept going.
Where are we?
We're here, together.
Then, when are we?
Is this... now?
( crying )
Am I going mad?
Are you real?
Of course I'm real.
I can't tell anymore.
It's like I'm...
trapped in a dream or...
a memory
from a life long ago.
One minute, I'm here
with you, and the next--
This place
isn't good for you.
You're trapped
in memories, bad ones.
( bell tolling )
This is what Arnold wants.
He wants me to remember.
Whoever Arnold is,
he's not here now.
I am.
I'm gonna get you
out of here.
( crickets chirping )
Dolores:
I was certain
that was the place.
Arnold would
meet me there.
He'd help.
Hey.
We gotta get you
closer to Sweetwater.
This far out,
it's like you--
you start
to break down
or something.
( hoofbeats approaching )
( horse neighing )
Dolores:
Union scouting party?
Maybe they can take us back.
Soldiers:
Hyah! Yah!
Whoa, whoa, easy, now.
Whoa.
Logan:
Well, well, well.
( sighs )
Billy.
I've been looking
for you for days.
Man, are you two fucked.
( exhales )
This shouldn't make
you uncomfortable.
It's the circle of life,
or the approximation of it.
Even the dead
fulfill a purpose.
You'll do.
What are you uploading?
35 years of vitally
important data.
It's more information
than any single drive
could hold.
A host's brain,
however,
especially once
it's been emptied out,
like this poor schmuck,
is quite capacious.
This data
that you're uploading,
is it the hosts' codes?
As of this moment,
that doesn't concern you.
What does concern you
is giving him
a semblance of a personality
and getting him
on the train,
out of the park.
How am I supposed
to do that?
You're a writer.
Make up a story.
Have fun programming.
Remember, brevity is
the soul of wit.
Stubbs:
Bernard.
Look, I, uh...
I know you and I
haven't always seen
eye to eye,
but I thought
the decision
to remove you
was shortsighted,
so I'm glad
to see you back at work.
With that said,
no one could blame you
if you wanted to take
a personal day.
I find the work
reassuring.
Sometimes
the best salve
is routine.
Nothing routine
about today, though.
I know this must be
difficult for you.
I'm sorry,
I don't understand.
Forgive the intrusion,
and you were both
very discreet,
but it's my job
to know these things.
I just wanted
to offer my support.
I'm afraid you have
the wrong idea.
I respected Theresa,
and what happened to her
was tragic,
but to be honest,
I barely knew her.
If you don't mind,
I should get back to work.
Of course.
I know you're shorthanded.
Speaking of which,
have you heard
from Elsie Hughes?
I left word with her
this morning
to notify her
about Theresa,
but she never
got back to me.
I'm sure she's just
enjoying her time off.
Yeah.
( crickets chirping )
Angela:
Wyatt's men...
they kept whispering.
They said this world
didn't belong
to the old settlers
or the new.
That it belonged to something
that had yet to come,
that it belonged to him.
You remember.
Man in Black:
You two seem to have
found yourselves
in the same
new narrative.
They say
in this country...
the only people who survive
are men of conviction.
Mine is to save Dolores
or die trying.
Wyatt's is to claim
this earth
or raze it
to the ground.
But yours--
yours has always been
a mystery to me.
For all the time
we've spent together,
I still have no idea
who the hell you really are.
But happily,
in your convalescence,
I've had time to consider
the best way to make you talk.
- Dolores...
- ( groans )
I remember.
You took her.
You hurt her.
You're actually
remembering.
Where is she?
- Tell me!
- You really are
an idiot, Teddy.
You think Dolores
drops that can for you?
You just hand her over
to guys like me.
You're the worst of them.
A glorified pimp.
( groans )
- I'm gonna kill you slowly.
- No, you aren't.
The rules of this place
hold you back.
But I know
how to change them.
You speak like
you own this world.
Not just this one.
You want to know
who I am?
Who I really am?
I'm a god.
Titan of industry.
Philanthropist.
Family man,
married to
a beautiful woman,
father to
a beautiful daughter.
I'm the good guy, Teddy.
Then, last year,
my wife took
the wrong pills.
Fell asleep in the bath.
Tragic accident.
30 years of marriage
vanished.
How do you say it?
"Like a deep
and distant dream."
Then, at the funeral,
I tried to console
my daughter.
She pushed me away,
told me that
my wife's death
was no accident...
that she killed herself
because of me.
Emily said
that every day with me
had been sheer terror.
At any point,
I could blow up
or collapse
like some dark star or...
Did you hurt them, too?
Never.
They never saw anything
like the man I am in here.
But she knew anyway.
She said if I stacked up
all my good deeds,
it was just an elegant wall
I built to hide
what's inside
from everyone,
and from myself.
I had to prove her wrong,
so I came back here.
Because that's what
this place does, right?
Reveals your true self.
But that time,
I didn't join one
of Ford's stories,
I-- I created my own.
A test.
A very simple one.
I found a woman,
an ordinary homesteader
and her daughter.
( chatter )
Better cool them off
before they move
- from gambling
and whoring to--
- Have fun with that.
I'm finally
getting out of here.
The house is yours.
Man in Black:
I wanted to see
if I had it in me
to do something
truly evil.
To see what
I was really made of.
Maeve?
Sure you can't
stick around?
- Maeve?
- Man: Whoa!
Gunslinger in there
has got an appetite
for a double dip--
- I'm sure you can
find another--
- ( gunshot )
- ( woman screams )
( gunfire continues )
( hammer clicks )
Man in Black:
I killed her and her daughter
just to see what I felt.
Then, just when
I thought it was done...
the woman refused to die.
( gasping )
You're a fucking animal.
Well, an animal
would've felt something.
I felt... nothing.
And then something
miraculous happened.
In all my years
coming here,
I had never seen
anything like it.
She was alive,
truly alive,
if only for a moment.
And that was when the maze
revealed itself to me.
The maze.
What's that damn pattern
have to do with this?
Everything.
In Ford's game, even if I go
to the outer edges,
you can't kill me.
You can't even leave
a lasting mark.
But there's
a deeper game here, Teddy.
Arnold's game.
And that game...
cuts deep.
( rifle cocks )
( whispers )
( people screaming )
( gunfire continues )
Woman: We're having some kind
of behavioral problem
with the madam.
She's not responding,
and the other hosts
have been unable
to intercept.
I've authorized a tag team
to retrieve her.
Good.
( screaming and gunfire
continue )
( Maeve screaming )
My baby!
( screaming continues )
Sir, she won't respond
to verbal commands.
- We can't shut her down.
- Leave us now.
Clear the floor.
That's enough, Maeve.
That's enough.
My baby.
He killed her.
- He took her from me.
- I don't understand.
She's not responding
to anything.
Her cognition's
fragmented.
He killed her.
He killed her, my baby.
He took her from me.
- ( sobbing continues )
- ( music playing )
( music continues )
There.
That's better.
An old trick
from an old friend.
You need not suffer,
Maeve.
I'll take it from you.
No.
No, no, no, please.
This pain...
it's all
I have left of her.
Please.
There.
Give yourself now
to a deep, dreamless slumber.
Perhaps a fresh start,
a new role for you.
And tomorrow,
this will be simply
a distant dream.
( beeps )
We located her.
Behavior wants her down
for immediate diagnostic.
You think
I lack conviction?
Wyatt didn't burn
my world down.
Didn't have to.
I left it all behind
for this one.
The maze is all
that matters now,
and besting Wyatt
is the last step
in unlocking it,
to having what both
our sorry lives lack--
meaning.
To giving our choices
consequence...
even if it kills us.
Kill him.
Give him
what he wants.
He's tied,
unarmed.
So was the little girl
he killed.
He's worse
than Wyatt's men.
I can't.
These things take time.
But we haven't
got much left.
Perhaps I can help you.
( gasps )
You've been gone
a long while, Theodore.
It's time you came back
to the fold.
Wyatt will need you soon.
( music playing )