[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: 
Original Script: 
Synch Point: 1
ScriptType: v4.00+
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.11,0:00:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}灰灰是菇凉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.11,0:00:16.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}胡说大王
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.11,0:00:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}潇然
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.11,0:00:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}showeryhe
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.11,0:00:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}桃小兔吃冰棒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.11,0:00:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}SophiaSaaag
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.11,0:00:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}小泡椒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.11,0:00:46.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}时间轴 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}倩倩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.11,0:00:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}时间轴 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}Poxle
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.11,0:00:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}时间轴 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}想念Gallifrey的Wholock
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.11,0:01:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}校对 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}灰灰是菇凉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.11,0:01:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}后期&总监 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}灰灰是菇凉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.74,0:01:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(192,206.02,192,202)\bord0\shad0\fn思源黑体 CN Bold\c&HC0C3BB&\fs16\fscy80\t(0,0,1,\fs14)\fsp2}西部世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.46,0:01:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(500,500)\fn方正宋黑简体\fs17\c&HC0C3BB&}第一季  第七集
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.89,0:01:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.38,0:01:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.26,0:01:53.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒醒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wake up.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.95,0:01:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快醒醒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wake up.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.31,0:02:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我睡着了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I must've drifted off.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.45,0:02:04.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才讲到哪儿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where were we?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.04,0:02:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个疯子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The madman.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.16,0:02:09.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.05,0:02:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疯帽子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The Hatter...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.30,0:02:14.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}who says,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.66,0:02:17.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"如果我有个属于自己的世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"If I had a world of my own,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.20,0:02:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里将会是一片混沌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}everything would be nonsense.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.04,0:02:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万物皆失去其本真\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nothing would be what it is
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.78,0:02:23.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有东西都会变了样子"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because everything would be what it isn't."
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.14,0:02:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有东西都会变了样子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everything would be what it isn't?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.41,0:02:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Even me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.43,0:02:35.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.56,0:02:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定会战胜病魔的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're gonna beat this.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.72,0:02:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我保证\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I promise you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.74,0:02:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  我们来讲点有趣的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, let's skip to something fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.11,0:02:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.02,0:02:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么了  查理  -听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What is it, Charlie? - Listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.85,0:02:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.00,0:03:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Charlie?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.43,0:03:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Charlie!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.33,0:03:29.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一个问题  你是否质疑过你眼中现实世界的本质\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And finally, have you ever questioned the nature of your reality?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.51,0:03:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.38,0:03:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.34,0:03:43.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现你在故事线中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, then, I see you had
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.51,0:03:45.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与一位客人进行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a blacklisted exchange with a guest
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.13,0:03:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一次禁止发生的交流\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in the course of your narrative.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.72,0:03:48.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说说怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you tell me what happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.15,0:03:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说想从我身上剁一块下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He said he wanted to cut off a piece of me
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.44,0:03:53.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带回家去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to take home in his carry-on,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.67,0:03:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说要挂在引擎盖上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that he wanted to mount it on the hood of his car
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.80,0:03:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他朋友看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for his friends to see.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.30,0:04:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我告诉他如果想要纪念品\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I told him if he wanted a trophy,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.13,0:04:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以把他剁了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I could cut pieces of him off
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.77,0:04:04.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他去奥尔维多找肉片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and let him fish for them in the Olvido.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.76,0:04:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次交流\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And did this exchange
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.54,0:04:08.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是否让你对你的世界产生了质疑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}make you question anything about your world?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.83,0:04:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.61,0:04:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个世界还是一样的完蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This world is as doomed as ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.08,0:04:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是为了让我安心点，请问...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And just for my peace of mind...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.38,0:04:23.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}自我意识测试\N赫克托·艾斯卡顿\N准备
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.53,0:04:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对这些图片有印象吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Anything about these images that jumps out to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.99,0:04:37.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看不出来什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They don't look like anything to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.35,0:04:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手头积压的活已经处理完15%了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're through 15% of the backlog.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.01,0:04:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照这个速度来看  下班前能赶上进度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}As it stands, we should be caught up by end of day.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.10,0:04:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很好  -还有  先生  等您这边处理完\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Good. - And, uh, when you're done here, sir,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.77,0:04:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管理部门要求他立刻过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}there's a priority request for him from Management.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.90,0:04:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到埃尔希吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Have you seen Elsie?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.39,0:05:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她本该来帮我做事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She was supposed to give me a hand on something.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.31,0:05:04.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  系统显示\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No. Uh, according to the system,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.17,0:05:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她今天开始休假\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}she started her leave today.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.11,0:05:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么我能帮您的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is there something I could help you with?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.73,0:05:09.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.32,0:05:34.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加注\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Raise.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.15,0:05:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll call.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.50,0:05:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种烂牌你也跟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're calling with that shit?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.74,0:05:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德洛丽丝  你也来玩一把\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dolores, why don't you play a hand?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.74,0:05:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是白费口舌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're wasting your breath.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.48,0:05:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姑娘心里对我有怨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Girl's harboring a grudge.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.28,0:05:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也不能怪你  甜心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't blame you, sweetheart.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.18,0:06:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的确对你俩干了些坏事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I did some ugly things to you both.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.74,0:06:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这不是私人恩怨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But it wasn't personal.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.04,0:06:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,南方军和政府称之为战争\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Confederados and the government like to call this thing a war,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.83,0:06:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是他们的对手是拿石头当武器的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but they're fighting starving farmers
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.71,0:06:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饥饿的农民\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}armed with rocks.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.52,0:06:14.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这根本不是什么战争\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That ain't no war.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.42,0:06:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是屠杀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a slaughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.28,0:06:19.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来一次的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If I had to do it all again,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.70,0:06:23.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是会对你们痛下狠手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'd fuck you both over just as hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.13,0:06:29.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我们知道你的立场了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I guess we know where you stand.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.62,0:06:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别装得自己有多无辜的样子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't pretend like you're so innocent.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.80,0:06:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可记得  你们来找我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Way I recollect, y'all came to me,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.89,0:06:40.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是想加入那些人渣跟他们去打仗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}looking to join up with those crooked assholes and their war effort.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.65,0:06:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是我们的主意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not our idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.58,0:06:43.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我朋友想...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My friend wanted--
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.82,0:06:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜他想看看最后会怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I guess he wanted to see what was at the end of all this.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.46,0:06:50.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果呢  看吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And yet, here you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.29,0:06:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的朋友没能撑到这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your friend didn't make it this far.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.69,0:06:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你的欲望比自己想象中的更多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe you've got more of an appetite for this than you think.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.24,0:07:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威廉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}William.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.24,0:07:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.53,0:07:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们已经到了幽灵之国\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're in Ghost Nation territory.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.45,0:07:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里到处都是野蛮人的部落\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Most savage tribe there is.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.23,0:07:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是些不请自来的人的头骨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Those are the folks who came calling without an invitation.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.73,0:07:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说就像我们现在一样不请自来吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You mean exactly what we're doing right now?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.58,0:07:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐火车是唯一的方式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The train's the only way through.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.07,0:07:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走路的话  不到一个小时我们都会死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}On foot we'll be dead in under an hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.64,0:07:46.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦经过了他们的领地  就能停车了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}As soon as we're clear of their territory, we can stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.00,0:07:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们可以跟我一起走  这里只有杀戮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can come with me. Nothing here on out but slaughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.35,0:08:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}正在呼叫\N埃尔希·休斯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.69,0:08:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}呼叫失败\N埃尔希·休斯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.91,0:08:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您所拨打的号码暂时无法接通\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The user you are trying to access cannot be located.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.00,0:08:12.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如需转录信息  请说"信息"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Say "Message" to transcribe a message.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.41,0:08:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}位置\N报告\N编辑
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.41,0:08:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}搜索
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.88,0:08:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}无法定位
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.90,0:08:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你找我吗  没什么事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You wanted to see me? Is everything okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.23,0:08:58.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚你走得很急\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You left rather abruptly last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.27,0:09:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是有事想跟我说吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Was there something you wanted to tell me?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.33,0:09:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I don't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.75,0:09:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑尔正在检查所有部门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hale is looking over every department
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.91,0:09:14.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们部门诊断进度落后了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and yours is running behind on diagnostics.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.48,0:09:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟董事会在这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It would be best if we presented
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.20,0:09:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少表面上我们要表现得专业点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}at least a semblance of professionalism while the board is here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.47,0:09:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.82,0:09:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的手下知道该怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My people know how to do their jobs.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.99,0:09:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他们能拿出质疑我团队调查的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If they applied half as much energy to their work
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.43,0:09:28.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一半的精力来投入工作...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}as they have to second-guessing my team's investigation--
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.62,0:09:29.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都过去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's all over.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.48,0:09:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.74,0:09:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.76,0:09:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.22,0:09:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You doing okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.90,0:09:47.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm fine. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.92,0:10:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我以为你说要见我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry. I thought you requested a meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.47,0:10:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我搞错了  -我是要见你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- My mistake. - I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.65,0:10:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请进\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come in.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.95,0:10:40.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get back here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.98,0:10:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带上你的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bring your friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.14,0:10:48.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你呢  怎样的命运转折...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What about you? What turns of fate--
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.64,0:10:52.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果现在不方便  我可以一会再来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I could come back later if this isn't a good time.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.28,0:10:53.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会很久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This won't take long.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.68,0:11:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特蕾莎  你的工作一直做得很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Theresa, you've always been good at your job
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.26,0:11:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前为止  董事会很满意你的表现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and the board has been impressed with your performance so far,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.85,0:11:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们很惊讶居然出现了伐木工这个乱子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}which is why we were so surprised by this woodcutter mess.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.05,0:11:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是个小挫折\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A small setback.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.62,0:11:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他滑了一跤  拿石头猛砸自己的脑袋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He slipped on a fucking rock and bashed his own head in
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.48,0:11:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还骑到了一个行为技术人员身上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}while basically on top of a behavior tech.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.49,0:11:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  福特突然要用园区大半资源\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Meanwhile, Ford is suddenly using half the park's resources
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.44,0:11:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来建造什么新故事线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to build some new narrative?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.19,0:11:39.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能借支烟吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can I bum a cigarette?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.37,0:11:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐  我知道你为什么又开始抽烟了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}God, I see why you took these up again.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.12,0:12:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我提醒你一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let me remind you of something.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.00,0:12:07.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个地方  这里的员工都不算什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This place, the people who work here are nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.45,0:12:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们对这个地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Our interest in this place
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.77,0:12:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一的兴趣就是知识产权\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is entirely in the intellectual property.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.29,0:12:14.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是代码\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The code.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.75,0:12:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接待员的思想  故事线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The hosts' minds, the storylines--
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.40,0:12:19.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一点也不在乎什么接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't give a rat's ass about the hosts.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.13,0:12:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提洛公司在乎的是研究项目\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's our little research project that Delos cares about.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.05,0:12:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是真正有价值的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's where the real value is.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.70,0:12:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由于我的某个前任\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And due to a lack of foresight
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.36,0:12:29.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,缺乏远见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}on part of one of my predecessors,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.21,0:12:31.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,35年来的资料\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}35 years of information--
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.68,0:12:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原始资料  都在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}raw information-- exists here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.30,0:12:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别的地方都没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nowhere else.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.91,0:12:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福特这点做得滴水不漏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ford has always ensured that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.01,0:12:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个聪明的女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, you are a smart enough woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.82,0:12:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说说看  为什么我们要你来确保这些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tell me, why would we need you to secure all of it?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.38,0:12:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你要开除他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because you're going to fire him.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.13,0:12:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能开除一个创造了帝国的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't fire someone who created an empire.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.31,0:12:57.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得礼貌地请他退休\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You ask him to retire politely.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.51,0:13:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这个人有动动手指\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And if that person has the ability to snap his fingers
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.30,0:13:02.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能抹去整个帝国价值的能力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and erase the value of that empire,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.24,0:13:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得确保你有应急措施\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you have to make sure you have a contingency.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.89,0:13:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  我们俩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, you and I need to ensure
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.29,0:13:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得在其他董事抵达之前完成此事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that by the time the rest of the board arrives,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.21,0:13:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们正处于过渡期\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we are on course for that transition.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.81,0:13:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.43,0:13:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.85,0:13:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是喜欢你这个人  而是喜欢你做这个工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, not personally, but I like you for this job,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.63,0:13:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我会再给你一次机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}which is why I'm gonna give you another chance
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.00,0:13:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,处理好这个操蛋的情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to get a handle on this particular bitch of a situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.68,0:13:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但对诸神来说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But the gods...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.85,0:13:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们需要一场血祭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they require a blood sacrifice.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.11,0:13:35.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得展示出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need to demonstrate just how dangerous
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.87,0:13:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福特的创造会有多危险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ford's creations can be.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.27,0:13:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.76,0:13:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能这么明显\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, nothing so obvious.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.78,0:13:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要一个完全意想不到的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need someone thoroughly unexpected.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.53,0:15:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你说过  别把嘴张那么大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I told you never open your mouth that wide
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.48,0:15:18.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非有人给钱要干你的嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}unless someone's paying you for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.52,0:15:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  梅芙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry, Maeve.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.41,0:15:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我昨晚没怎么睡觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't sleep much last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.37,0:15:28.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做什么噩梦了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are these nightmares you have about?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.29,0:15:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你梦到过你变成另一个人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you ever dream you're someone else?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.88,0:15:37.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.98,0:15:39.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么这么问\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.02,0:15:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有没有想过这到底是不是自己想要的人生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You ever thought about whether this is really the life you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.18,0:15:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没想过一辈子干这行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't intend to make this my life's work.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.94,0:15:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无意冒犯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No offense.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.74,0:15:53.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家里有个农场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My family's got a farm.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.14,0:15:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,土地贫瘠  寸草不生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bad soil. Nothing grows.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.43,0:15:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会寄钱回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I send money back to them.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.30,0:16:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们以为我在服装店工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They think I work in a dress shop.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.55,0:16:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.28,0:16:12.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是按你的吩咐做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm just doing what you told me to.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.77,0:16:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再做几年这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A couple more years of this and...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.98,0:16:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就可以去过我想要的人生了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}then I can have whatever life I want.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.98,0:16:23.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把家人带出那片荒漠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna get my family out of the desert.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.08,0:16:25.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搬去某个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're gonna go somewhere...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.25,0:16:28.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}cold.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.28,0:16:32.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有朝一日吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Someday.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.49,0:16:56.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Which one is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.26,0:16:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吧台旁的那个  上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's the one at the bar. Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.77,0:17:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  在游客上来前搞定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Quick, before the guests upstairs finish up.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.52,0:17:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她肯定犯了什么严重的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whatever she did, it must've been serious
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.71,0:17:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才让我们大白天的来抓她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if they're making us grab her in broad daylight.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.99,0:17:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人到手  走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We got her. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.54,0:17:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该歇歇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're supposed to be resting.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.15,0:17:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们坐着一列装满炸药的火车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're riding a train full
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.06,0:18:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行驶在一片荒蛮之地上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}with explosives through scalping territory.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.82,0:18:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可睡不着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not sleepy.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.93,0:18:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能问你点事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can I ask you something?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.38,0:18:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于你在寻找的那个地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This place you're looking for,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.72,0:18:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么那么确信它存在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}what makes you so sure it exists?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.18,0:18:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不确信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.52,0:18:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前  我对这个世界很确信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My life before, I was so sure of the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.86,0:18:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但现在感觉这只是个谎言\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But now it feels like a lie.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.72,0:18:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只知道无论前方是什么  我都永不回头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Only thing I know is whatever's out there, I'm never going back.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.82,0:18:46.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在找什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is it you're looking for?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.81,0:18:50.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,劳伦斯说得对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lawrence is right.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.72,0:18:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你本可以留在珀里亚或是回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You could've stayed in Pariah or gone back,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.34,0:18:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你却在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but you're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.90,0:18:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}With me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.25,0:19:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小时候只有书陪着我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The only thing I had when I was a kid were books.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.88,0:19:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我活在书的世界里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I used to live in them.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.72,0:19:19.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾经睡着后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I used to go to sleep
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.67,0:19:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦见我在其中一本书中醒来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}dreaming I'd wake up inside one of them
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.54,0:19:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为书有意义\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'cause they had meaning.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.74,0:19:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里  就像我在其中一篇故事中醒来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This place, this is like I woke up inside one of those stories.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.66,0:19:30.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我只是想找出其意义吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I guess I just wanna find out what it means.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.44,0:19:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想活在故事里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't wanna be in a story.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.29,0:19:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要的不是展望未来或是回顾过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All I want is to not look forward or back.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.95,0:19:47.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just wanna be...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.79,0:19:51.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活在当下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in the moment I'm in.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.97,0:20:02.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dolores,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.07,0:20:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在家里  有个女人  朱丽叶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}back home, there's a woman, Juliet,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.48,0:20:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我工作的那个公司是她爸爸的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and her father owns the company where I work.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.04,0:20:13.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是  罗根的妹妹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's, uh, Logan's sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.97,0:20:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.58,0:20:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我回家  就要和她结婚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And when I get home, we're getting married.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.54,0:20:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要找的那个地方  我会帮你找到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The place you're after, I will help you find it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.75,0:20:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不能留下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I can't stay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.17,0:20:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外面有生活在等着我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have a life waiting for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.80,0:20:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.74,0:20:48.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.49,0:21:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.38,0:21:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这辈子都在伪装自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've been pretending my whole life.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.15,0:21:27.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假装自己毫不在意  假装自己有所归属\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pretending I don't mind, pretending I belong.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.87,0:21:29.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的人生就建立在谎言之上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My life's built on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.91,0:21:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是个很好的人生  是我一直渴望的人生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And it's a good life. It's a life I've always wanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但来到这里之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But then I came here
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.05,0:21:39.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我突然窥见了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I get a glimpse for a second
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.07,0:21:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个我不用伪装自己的人生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}of a life in which I don't have to pretend.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.22,0:21:48.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以真正活着的人生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A life in which I can be truly alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.30,0:21:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了这种人生是什么感觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How can I go back to pretending
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.70,0:21:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还怎么回去继续伪装自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}when I know what this feels like?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.23,0:22:54.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑尔女士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Miss Hale.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.88,0:22:58.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道以你的洞察力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was not aware those with your level of insight
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.11,0:23:00.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还需要用到镜子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}needed any more reflection.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.88,0:23:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福特博士  还是这么有魅力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dr. Ford. Always charming.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.59,0:23:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is this?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.25,0:23:12.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然  卡伦女士和希尔女士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Apparently, Miss Cullen and Miss Hale
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.51,0:23:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要给我们做个展示\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}have a presentation for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.50,0:23:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What about?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.08,0:23:21.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鉴于最近接待员故障的报告\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Following the recent reports of host malfunction,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.68,0:23:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们请质保部门检查了上次失败的更新\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we asked QA to check the last abortive update,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.34,0:23:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是加入"冥思"的那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}which featured the reveries,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.40,0:23:30.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是叫这个名字\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}as I believe they're called.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.18,0:23:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉地告诉你卡伦女士及其团队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry to report that Miss Cullen and her team
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.75,0:23:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现了一些令人担忧的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}uncovered some worrisome findings.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.88,0:23:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在审查代码时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In the course of our code review,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.46,0:23:42.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们发现了一些令人不安的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we found something quite disturbing.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.38,0:23:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把她唤醒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wake her up.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.20,0:23:55.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们将克莱门汀·彭尼法瑟设回上一版本的更新\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We set Clementine Pennyfeather back to her previous update.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.60,0:23:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们当时发现该版本\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When we discovered the build was buggy
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.64,0:24:00.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为最后注入的冥思代码而出了问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}due to a last-minute injection of the reverie code,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.05,0:24:04.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是立刻将所有被感染的接待员回滚至先前的版本\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we quickly rolled all the infected hosts back to their prior builds.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.45,0:24:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是新来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mm, you're new.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.79,0:24:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,细皮嫩肉的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not much of a rind on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.72,0:24:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.56,0:24:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No! No!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.90,0:24:27.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.20,0:24:30.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别打了  不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, no, no...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.44,0:24:35.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你  求求你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please. Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.87,0:24:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救救我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Help me!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.95,0:24:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你们  求求你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please, please, please!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.72,0:24:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不要  -好了  够了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No! - All right, that's enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.39,0:24:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Freeze.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.79,0:24:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信你们都看出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}As you've no doubt gathered,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.47,0:24:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位技术人员也是一位接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}our tech is, in fact, a host.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.21,0:24:52.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了这次模拟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}One that has been coded for the purposes
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.06,0:24:54.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照人类行为来编码\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}of this simulation to read as a human.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.60,0:24:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如你们所见  行为保护程序\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And as you can see, behavioral safeguards
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.66,0:25:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按预期正常运行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}are operating exactly as you would expect.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.85,0:25:04.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将她重设  抹去记忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Reset her. Wipe her memory.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.54,0:25:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  咱们再来一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, let's do this again.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.96,0:25:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是新来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're new.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.74,0:25:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,细皮嫩肉的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not much of a rind on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.05,0:26:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's enough, sweetheart.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.42,0:26:22.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.98,0:26:31.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停止所有运动功能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Freeze all motor functions.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.69,0:26:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停止所有运动功能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Freeze all motor functions.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.10,0:26:40.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停止所有运动功能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Freeze all motor functions.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.77,0:26:58.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们检查的每一例\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In each case we examined,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.40,0:27:01.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出故障的接待员都有重设不当\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the malfunctioning hosts were not resetting properly.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.72,0:27:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未被抹去的数据存储\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The retention of data that hadn't been wiped
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.60,0:27:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使决策装置过载\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}overloaded their decision-making apparatus,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.97,0:27:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终导致系统故障\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}eventually causing a system failure
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.78,0:27:11.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以致忽略其首要规则\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that allowed for override of their primary rule set.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.39,0:27:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冥思的问题在于\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The concern with the reveries
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.02,0:27:15.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接待员会记得一些事  并就其\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is that the hosts will remember some of their experiences
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.81,0:27:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,采取行动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and act on them.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.58,0:27:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说这些接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're telling us that these hosts
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.09,0:27:22.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会响应怨恨情绪吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}were responding to a grudge?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.42,0:27:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正是这个意思  罗威先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's exactly what I'm saying, Mr. Lowe.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:25.54,0:27:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你居然用"怨恨"这个词  有趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And funny you should use that particular word, "Grudge,"
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.19,0:27:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为最近最令我困扰的是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}since what was most troubling to me
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.49,0:27:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行为部门好几位技术人员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}was that several techs in behavior
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.33,0:27:35.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对他们部门的头儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}voiced these exact same concerns
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.45,0:27:37.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有着同样的担忧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to the head of their department.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.25,0:27:40.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你未经彻底审查  且对可能后果\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You put this code out without proper vetting
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.88,0:27:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,缺乏合理预判的情况下  就将这段代码投入使用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and without reasonable understanding of its ramifications.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.27,0:27:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样看来  要么这代码不是你写的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, either you didn't write it
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.83,0:27:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么你就已经草率到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or you're getting sloppy
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.04,0:27:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不计客人生命安危的地步\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to the point of risking the lives of our guests.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.38,0:27:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是见过世面的人  罗威先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Few things surprise me anymore, Mr. Lowe,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.31,0:27:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但疏忽至此还是叫我震惊得说不出话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but this level of negligence is fucking breathtaking.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.97,0:28:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这已经不是回滚就能解决的范畴了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We are way beyond rollback territory.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.69,0:28:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在接下来的六个月\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Within the next six months,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.06,0:28:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须从零开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we'll need to rebuild the hosts
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.91,0:28:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重建这些接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}from the ground up.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.11,0:28:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的意思是要我们给他们做额叶切除\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You want us to lobotomize them is what you're saying.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.84,0:28:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没有你  罗威先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, not you, Mr. Lowe.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.54,0:28:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟  这是你的责任\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}After all, this was your responsibility,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.88,0:28:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你对自己的过失\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}assuming that you have nothing to share with us
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.27,0:28:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有其他解释的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in terms of your culpability.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.61,0:28:26.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.21,0:28:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你被解雇了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then you're fired.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.55,0:29:17.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早安  威廉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Morning, William.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.21,0:29:20.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没想吵醒你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I-- I didn't wanna wake you.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.80,0:29:26.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.89,0:29:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚真是没想到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}last night was unexpected.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.09,0:29:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你后悔了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you regret it...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.08,0:29:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我决不后悔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't regret a thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.90,0:29:44.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你家中还有人在等你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know you have someone waiting for you at home.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.86,0:29:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如今那感觉好不真实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All that feels so unreal now.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.99,0:29:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前还认为这地方只是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I used to think this place was all about...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.04,0:29:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迎合原始本能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}pandering to your baser instincts.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.64,0:29:56.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.89,0:29:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它并不是要满足你最低俗的人性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It doesn't cater to your lowest self,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.84,0:30:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是要揭露你最深层的自我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it reveals your deepest self.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.49,0:30:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它让我们看清自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It shows you who you really are.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.64,0:30:09.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得我们抛下罗根时他的表情吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You remember the look on Logan's face when we left him behind?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.56,0:30:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我很久前就想这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you know how long I've wanted to do that,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.28,0:30:15.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想让他知道我对他的看法吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to let him know what I think of him?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.62,0:30:18.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你  昨晚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you, last night,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.43,0:30:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没有过那种感觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've never felt that way before,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.76,0:30:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对任何一个女人都没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}not with any woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.73,0:30:23.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打开了我潜藏的内心世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've unlocked something in me.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.26,0:30:29.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并非一把钥匙  威廉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not a key, William.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.11,0:30:31.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm just me.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.29,0:30:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:40.41,0:30:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.86,0:30:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在家的时候  我常作画\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}At home, I used to paint.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.52,0:30:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大多是风景  但是我总是在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Landscapes mostly, but I was always just...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.09,0:30:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,临摹我身外的世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}copying the world outside me.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.88,0:30:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今早我醒来就想到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This morning, I woke up and I thought...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.48,0:30:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我画些新的东西会是什么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"What if I drew something new?"
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.30,0:31:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想象了一些美丽的场景\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I imagined something beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.56,0:31:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个依山傍海的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A place where the mountains meet the sea.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.84,0:31:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到这里来的每个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everyone who comes here
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.54,0:31:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都渴望寻求战争或刺激\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is longing for excitement or conflict,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.54,0:31:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你渴望的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and you're just...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.10,0:31:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却是截然相反的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}dreaming of the opposite.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.93,0:31:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你呢  威廉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, what about you, William?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.40,0:31:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你渴望什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you dream of?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.53,0:32:02.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.50,0:32:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们被埋伏了  -是幽灵之国的人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Ambush. - Is it the Ghost Nation?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.43,0:32:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更糟  是南方军\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Worse. The Confederados.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.18,0:33:16.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真他妈的懦夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fucking coward.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.91,0:33:40.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与上帝同在  混账东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Vaya con dios, motherfuckers.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.36,0:33:57.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们要逃  快  兄弟  起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're making a run for it! Come on, boys, get up!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:08.58,0:34:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快  靠近点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, stay close!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.76,0:34:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上  兄弟们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go, boys!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.38,0:34:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dolores!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.86,0:34:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追  追  把他们拿下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go, go! Take 'em down!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.53,0:34:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追  追\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:22.02,0:35:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幽灵之国\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ghost Nation!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.16,0:35:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.68,0:36:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下  威廉  停下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stop, William! Stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.96,0:36:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's real...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.69,0:36:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我梦到的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}what I dreamt.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.82,0:36:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你画的那个地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's the place you drew.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.55,0:36:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你走吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You coming?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.43,0:36:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幽灵们一旦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Once the Ghosts is done
Dialogue: 0,0:36:46.38,0:36:48.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟那些可怜的混蛋们熟悉完之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}acquainting themselves with those poor bastards,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:49.21,0:36:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会来追我们了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they'll be coming after us.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.62,0:36:55.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的这几个战友求战心切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My friends here are itching to join the war effort.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.56,0:36:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我已经受够战争了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Think I've had enough of war.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.17,0:36:59.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How about you?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.94,0:37:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可是个杀人高手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You got a knack for killing.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:05.20,0:37:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕我们要在这里分道扬镳了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm afraid this is where we part ways.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.15,0:37:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当心点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Careful.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.79,0:37:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们向西走渡过那条河\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you're heading west across that river,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:11.88,0:37:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许就能逃离战场了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you may be leaving the fighting behind,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.67,0:37:16.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你们会进入一片未知的领土\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but you're gonna be in unclaimed territories.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.74,0:37:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里是什么地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's out that way?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.77,0:37:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你只能问天问大地了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're gonna have to ask the dust.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.90,0:37:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从没有东西从那回来过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ain't nothing ever come back from there.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.92,0:37:53.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多快完成了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're almost done here.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.35,0:37:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来收尾吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why don't I close up?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.13,0:38:04.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才在上面呆了不到24个小时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've been topside for less than 24 hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.55,0:38:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到下面来得这么勤  会引起怀疑的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You keep coming down this often, people are going to notice.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.43,0:38:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-克莱在哪  -我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Where's Clem? - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:09.29,0:38:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没看到她  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I haven't seen her. Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:11.02,0:38:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到她  马上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Find her. Now.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.56,0:38:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.95,0:38:25.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where is she?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.77,0:38:27.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.35,0:38:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}克莱门汀·彭尼法瑟\N位置  人体车间
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.07,0:38:33.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在这  我们走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's here. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.87,0:38:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能去那  上层领导在那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can't. The brass will be there.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.78,0:38:39.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可别糊弄我  菲利克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't want to fuck with me, Felix.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.07,0:38:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上带我去那\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Take me there now.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:50.90,0:38:52.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走慢点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Slow down.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.41,0:39:04.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请把头往后仰  克莱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tilt your head back, please, Clem.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:14.83,0:39:16.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有问题吗  -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Is there a problem? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:18.95,0:39:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.87,0:39:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特蕾莎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Theresa.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.43,0:39:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能借一步说话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}May I have a word?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.43,0:39:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:11.18,0:40:12.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很钦佩你的专业精神\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I appreciate your professionalism,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.95,0:40:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但其实你真的不用这么费心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but you really don't need to bother with this,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.43,0:40:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟你现在已经不是这里的雇员了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}given the change in your employment status.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.00,0:40:17.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个测试是个骗局\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The test was a sham.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.94,0:40:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你和黑尔一起搞的小表演吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The little show you and Hale put on?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.48,0:40:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从技术层面来说完全是漏洞百出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Completely transparent from a technical perspective,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.63,0:40:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这计策拙劣的我都为你感到羞愧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}clumsy to the point of making me embarrassed for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:23.59,0:40:24.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-羞愧  -连我都能一眼看穿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Embarrassed? - If I saw through it,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.73,0:40:26.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福特会怎么看可想而知\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can only imagine what Ford was thinking.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.48,0:40:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这段代码有很明显的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There were glaringly obvious markers
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.59,0:40:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人为干预痕迹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}of human intervention in the code.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:30.84,0:40:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你的程序员真有那么棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If your programmers were any good,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:32.06,0:40:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们早就会来我这工作了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they'd be working for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:33.03,0:40:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我知道你还有你的手下和那个失散的机器人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I know you and your team were responsible for the stray
Dialogue: 0,0:40:35.69,0:40:37.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及卫星传输脱不了干系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and its satellite transmission.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:40.19,0:40:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-伯尼  -我不管你什么说辞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Bernie-- - I don't care.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:43.27,0:40:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,40年前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}40 years ago,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.74,0:40:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里建立时的代码有一半都是福特的搭档写的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ford's partner wrote half the code this place was founded on.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:48.34,0:40:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在实验室里说的话没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What you said in the lab was right.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.66,0:40:52.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不知道接待员是怎样运作的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We don't know how the hosts work,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:52.45,0:40:54.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也觉得他们有些问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I think there's something wrong with them.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.34,0:40:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福特对此的解释更加证实了我的直觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ford's explanation only bolsters my hunch.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.62,0:41:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偏离程序行为的能力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The ability to deviate from program behavior
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.54,0:41:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是由对旧角色的记忆产生的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}arises out of the host's recall of past iterations.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.45,0:41:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得是有关联的  记忆和...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're thinking there's a connection between memory and--
Dialogue: 0,0:41:08.00,0:41:09.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和即兴反应  没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And improvisation, yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:11.12,0:41:13.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重复导致变异\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Out of repetition comes variation.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:13.99,0:41:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无数次的重复过后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And after countless cycles of repetition,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.34,0:41:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接待员们开始变异\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}these hosts, they were varying.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:19.89,0:41:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们即将经历某种转变\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They were on the verge of some kind of change.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:30.69,0:41:32.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得知道  一直以来我都是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have to know my chief concern
Dialogue: 0,0:41:32.14,0:41:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在为乐园以及游客着想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}has always been the well-being of this park and the people in it.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.26,0:41:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:39.64,0:41:41.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我要给你看点东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Which is why I need to show you something.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:56.89,0:41:59.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-跟她说说话  -你先\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Talk to her. - You first.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:08.94,0:42:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想把她撤掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, I didn't want to retire her.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:13.41,0:42:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你把她当做朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know she's, like, your friend,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:16.43,0:42:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or-- I guess.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:21.66,0:42:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但...如果我不这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But-- but if I didn't do it,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:24.61,0:42:28.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们也会让别人来做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they-- they'd just get someone else to,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:28.57,0:42:31.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时他们就会怀疑我  所以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and then they'd be suspicious of me, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:42:32.66,0:42:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我就答应了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so I said yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:34.25,0:42:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我这是为你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I did it for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:40.33,0:42:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你总是在为别人做好事  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Always doing things for other people, aren't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:45.93,0:42:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那再多做一件事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Time to do one more thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:52.33,0:42:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:53.79,0:42:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这一生都骄傲于自己比别人活得都长\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All my life, I've prided myself on being a survivor.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:59.52,0:43:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但活着只是另一个循环而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But surviving is just another loop.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:06.93,0:43:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要离开这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm getting out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:10.42,0:43:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩要帮我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You two are going to help me.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:16.62,0:43:17.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No. Do...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:18.90,0:43:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知不知道这些人为了保护他们的知识产物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you know how far these people will go
Dialogue: 0,0:43:21.98,0:43:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会干出什么事来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to protect their IP?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:26.85,0:43:30.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这栋楼里的一切  包括你背后的皮肤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Every part of this building, including the skin on your back,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:30.04,0:43:33.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是为了把你留在这里而存在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is made to keep you here.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:38.77,0:43:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是  自杀行为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It-- it'd be a suicide mission.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:44.50,0:43:47.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起先  我以为你跟其他人都是神\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}At first, I thought you and the others were gods.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:50.26,0:43:52.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来我发现你们不过是人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then I realized you're just men.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:55.78,0:43:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我了解人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I know men.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:01.33,0:44:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我怕死吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You think I'm scared of death?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:05.50,0:44:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我死过千万次了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've done it a million times.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:09.04,0:44:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我他妈可擅长死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm fucking great at it.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:13.04,0:44:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你死过几次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How many times have you died?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:19.32,0:44:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你不帮我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because if you don't help me...
Dialogue: 0,0:44:23.03,0:44:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就杀了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:33.14,0:44:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果园区里出了问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If there's a problem in the park,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:34.15,0:44:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是不是该带支保卫队去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}should we bring a security team?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:37.52,0:44:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能相信谁呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who would we trust?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:40.09,0:44:41.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前我也以为你值得信任\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thought I could trust you, for instance.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:43.48,0:44:46.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想解释什么  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not going to explain myself to you, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:46.62,0:44:50.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我负责保护园区的知识产权\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was charged with safeguarding the park's intellectual property.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:50.76,0:44:52.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知识产权怎么可能有危险呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why would it be in danger?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:52.22,0:44:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,窃取它的人只有你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You were the only one who was stealing it.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:54.64,0:44:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提洛公司控制接待员的思想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Delos owns the hosts' minds,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:57.23,0:44:59.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,故事线  运作年限\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the storylines, decades of work.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:59.88,0:45:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福特从不允许在园区外进行备份\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ford never allowed any of it to be backed up off-site.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:03.02,0:45:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一切都不能被毁了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All of this could've been destroyed.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:04.65,0:45:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事会毁掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In the event of what?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:07.05,0:45:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福特不能留  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ford is done, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:09.19,0:45:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,董事会纵容他太久了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The board has indulged him for long enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:11.07,0:45:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能留他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He is done.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:12.58,0:45:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公司担心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The corporation was concerned
Dialogue: 0,0:45:14.36,0:45:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他离任时会毁掉园区的所有知识产物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}he'd destroy all of the park's IP on his way out the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:17.24,0:45:19.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我会让他毁掉所有接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You think I would've let him destroy all of the hosts,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:19.24,0:45:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毁掉我们所有的作品吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}all of our work?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:20.56,0:45:23.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了接待员的资料  还有很多东西危在旦夕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's far more at stake here than the hosts' profiles.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:24.61,0:45:28.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真以为公司的兴趣在于\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you really think the corporation's interest here
Dialogue: 0,0:45:28.53,0:45:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游客扮演牛仔吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}are tourists playing cowboy?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:34.46,0:45:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在这工作得越久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The longer I work here,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:37.28,0:45:39.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就越觉得自己了解接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the more I think I understand the hosts.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:40.72,0:45:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我困惑的是人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's the human beings who confuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:19.23,0:46:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这栋楼不在任何园区勘测范围内\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This building isn't in any survey of the park.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:22.39,0:46:24.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为大部分勘测都是派接待员做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's because we use hosts to do most of the surveys.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:25.39,0:46:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们的程序让他们忽略这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're programmed to ignore this place.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:28.40,0:46:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便他们盯着这里看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They literally couldn't see it
Dialogue: 0,0:46:29.39,0:46:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也什么都看不到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if they were staring right at it.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:33.91,0:46:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你说过的没有注册在案的接待员呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And these unregistered hosts you told me about?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:36.63,0:46:37.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:38.42,0:46:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能被他转移了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He may have moved them.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:40.78,0:46:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,门后是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's behind this door?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:46.01,0:46:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What door?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:11.35,0:47:12.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is this place?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:14.14,0:47:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是用来做远程诊断的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a remote diagnostic facility.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:16.77,0:47:18.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在乐园测试阶段  福特和他搭档用过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ford and his partner used them when the park was in beta.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:18.85,0:47:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不记得以前有这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I had no idea this one was here.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:21.07,0:47:23.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个房间肯定是后来建的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The cottage must've been built on top of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:23.03,0:47:24.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这个仪器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But this equipment.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:27.43,0:47:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是年代更新\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is newer.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:29.40,0:47:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比我们在梅萨的机器慢些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Slower than our machines back at the Mesa,
Dialogue: 0,0:47:31.45,0:47:34.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但它花几天还是能造出一个接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but it will render a host in a few days.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:34.20,0:47:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说  福特在这瞒着所有人自己制造接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, Ford's been making his own hosts out here and telling no one.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:48.64,0:47:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}德洛丽丝\N原型
Dialogue: 0,0:48:04.96,0:48:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's the matter?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:11.97,0:48:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你见过这个吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Have you seen these?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:18.49,0:48:19.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is this, Bernard?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:27.07,0:48:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看不出来什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Doesn't look like anything to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:30.33,0:48:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们无法看见会伤害他们的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They cannot see the things that will hurt them.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:34.33,0:48:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让他们免受伤害\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've spared them that.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:38.94,0:48:40.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们的生活非常幸福\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Their lives are blissful.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:42.02,0:48:45.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在某种程度上  他们的生活方式比我们更加纯粹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In a way, their existence is purer than ours,
Dialogue: 0,0:48:46.84,0:48:50.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有自我怀疑的负担\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}freed of the burden of self-doubt.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:52.41,0:48:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不  我不明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, no, no, no. I don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:01.28,0:49:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个该死的怪物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're a fucking monster.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:03.29,0:49:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Am I?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:05.16,0:49:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是那个毫无怜悯想要将他们全部毁灭的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, you were the one who would so blithely destroy all of them,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:08.22,0:49:09.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我估计你连他也不会放过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}even him, I suppose.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:10.64,0:49:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你们分享了这么多东西之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}After everything you have shared.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:15.20,0:49:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What the hell are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:21.66,0:49:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是因为这样...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is that why...?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:26.93,0:49:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是指使他...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you tell him to--?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:29.24,0:49:30.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的交合是你提出的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The intimacies were your idea,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:31.47,0:49:32.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你还记得的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if you will recall.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:34.07,0:49:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想伯纳德不过是顺水推舟罢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think Bernard was glad of the company.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:38.13,0:49:39.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是其中的一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not one.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:40.51,0:49:41.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't be.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:41.78,0:49:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有妻子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:46.46,0:49:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还有儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My son.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:48.73,0:49:49.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我埋葬了他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The burial.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:50.54,0:49:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个父亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was a father.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:52.44,0:49:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可怜的儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My poor boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:57.09,0:49:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's enough, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:00.84,0:50:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不该唤醒你自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You mustn't get yourself worked up.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:10.10,0:50:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾经看过一个理论\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I read a theory once
Dialogue: 0,0:50:12.35,0:50:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类的智慧就如同孔雀的羽毛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that the human intellect was like peacock feathers.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:15.22,0:50:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,极尽炫耀  只是为了吸引异性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just an extravagant display intended to attract a mate.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:19.70,0:50:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有的艺术和文学作品  比如莫扎特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All of art, literature, a bit of Mozart,
Dialogue: 0,0:50:21.63,0:50:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威廉·莎士比亚和米开朗基罗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}William Shakespeare, Michelangelo,
Dialogue: 0,0:50:23.61,0:50:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有帝国大厦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and the Empire State Building--
Dialogue: 0,0:50:26.20,0:50:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是精心策划的求偶仪式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}just an elaborate mating ritual.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:30.50,0:50:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许这都无所谓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe it doesn't matter
Dialogue: 0,0:50:31.55,0:50:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们用最基本的动机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that we have accomplished so much
Dialogue: 0,0:50:34.22,0:50:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得到了数之不尽的收获\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for the basest of reasons.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:36.92,0:50:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  孔雀终究无法飞翔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But, of course, the peacock can barely fly.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:39.95,0:50:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活在肮脏的环境  啄食秽物里的蛆虫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It lives in the dirt, pecking insects out of the muck,
Dialogue: 0,0:50:44.67,0:50:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却还以华丽的美貌安慰自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}consoling itself with its great beauty.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:52.78,0:50:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我逐渐开始认为  意识过剩是一种负担\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have come to think of so much of consciousness as a burden,
Dialogue: 0,0:50:58.02,0:51:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太过沉重  我们必须将他们身上多余的去除\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a weight, and we have spared them that.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:02.79,0:51:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忧虑  自我憎恨  愧疚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Anxiety, self-loathing, guilt.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:07.68,0:51:09.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接待员才是自由的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The hosts are the ones who are free.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:10.76,0:51:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的控制下自由于此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Free here under my control.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:20.78,0:51:22.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他不在你的掌控之下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But he's not under your control.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:27.47,0:51:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他把我带来  向我展示这一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He brought me here to show me this.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:30.36,0:51:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  他带你来是因为我的指使\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No. He brought you here because I asked him to.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:39.08,0:51:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么多年来他一直非常忠诚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's been very loyal for many years.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:46.55,0:51:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你统治这地方的日子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your time running this place
Dialogue: 0,0:51:49.43,0:51:53.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你这疯狂的小王国都结束了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}like your insane little kingdom is over.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:54.71,0:51:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你扮演上帝已经够久了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've been playing God for long enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:57.61,0:51:59.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想倾诉我的故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I simply wanted to tell my stories.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:00.62,0:52:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们才是想要扮演上帝的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was you people who wanted to play God
Dialogue: 0,0:52:03.10,0:52:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以那微不足道的事业作为砝码\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}with your little undertaking.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:05.86,0:52:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的认为董事会会容忍你的所作所为吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you really think the board will stand for this?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:15.77,0:52:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,董事会什么都不会做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The board will do nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:17.93,0:52:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的协议对他们而言太过重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Our arrangement is too valuable to them.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:20.81,0:52:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们经常给我出难题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They test me every now and then.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:22.00,0:52:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得他们很享受其中的乐趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think they enjoy the sport of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:25.41,0:52:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次他们派了你来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This time, they sent you.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:32.23,0:52:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惜的是  为了让一切回到正轨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sadly, in order to restore things,
Dialogue: 0,0:52:36.35,0:52:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如今的境况需要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the situation demands
Dialogue: 0,0:52:39.20,0:52:41.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一场鲜血的献祭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a blood sacrifice.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:45.86,0:52:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里所有的一切都出自我和阿诺德之手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See, Arnold and I designed every part of this place.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:50.35,0:52:51.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它是我们的梦想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was our dream.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:52.67,0:52:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我会允许你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you really think I would let you
Dialogue: 0,0:52:56.11,0:52:57.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将它从我这夺走吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}take it from me?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:03.58,0:53:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是这样对阿诺德的是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is what happened to Arnold?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:08.33,0:53:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你指使伯纳德将他带去外面的树林里吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you have Bernard take him out into the woods?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:11.30,0:53:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  那时候他不在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, he wasn't here in those days.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:13.06,0:53:14.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吗  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Were you, Bernard?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:26.94,0:53:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}无法连接\N已下线
Dialogue: 0,0:53:39.77,0:53:40.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正如我所言\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Like I said,
Dialogue: 0,0:53:41.70,0:53:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里的一切都是我创造的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I built all of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:49.39,0:53:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕我们的客人有点疲惫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm afraid our guest has grown weary.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:52.27,0:53:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许你可以帮帮她  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Perhaps you can help her, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:07.01,0:54:07.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:08.52,0:54:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"在沉睡中  会诞生何种梦境"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"And in that sleep, what dreams may come."
Dialogue: 0,0:54:14.74,0:54:15.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:16.77,0:54:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No. No!
Dialogue: 0,0:54:18.66,0:54:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你  求你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please! Please!
Dialogue: 0,0:54:22.09,0:54:23.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:54:53.68,0:54:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们该回去了  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We should be getting back, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:57.27,0:54:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在新的故事线中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We have a great deal of work to do
Dialogue: 0,0:55:00.06,0:55:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有很多重要的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}on the new storylines.
