[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: 
Original Script: 
Synch Point: 1
ScriptType: v4.00+
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.90,0:00:10.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}小泡椒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.90,0:00:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}胡说大王
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.90,0:00:20.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}潇然
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.90,0:00:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}showeryhe
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.90,0:00:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}桃小兔吃冰棒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.90,0:00:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}小酸奶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.90,0:00:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}星星与野狗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.90,0:00:45.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}时间轴 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}倩倩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.90,0:00:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}时间轴 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}Poxle
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.90,0:00:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}时间轴 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}想念Gallifrey的Wholock
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.90,0:01:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}校对 {\fs20\c&H0BFDFE&\fn方正小标宋_GBK}黄色世界赛太公
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.90,0:01:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}后期&总监 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}灰灰是菇凉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.53,0:01:36.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(192,206.02,192,202)\bord0\shad0\fn思源黑体 CN Bold\c&HC0C3BB&\fs16\fscy80\t(0,0,1,\fs14)\fsp2}西部世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.25,0:01:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(500,500)\fn方正宋黑简体\fs17\c&HC0C3BB&}第一季  第八集
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.04,0:01:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立即上线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bring yourself back online...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.01,0:01:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.84,0:01:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特蕾莎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Theresa?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.13,0:02:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.16,0:02:07.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我杀了她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I killed her.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.46,0:02:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做了什么  我都做了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What have I done? What have I done?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.70,0:02:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你所感受到的内疚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This guilt you feel,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.28,0:02:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苦恼  恐惧和悲痛...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the anguish, the horror, the pain...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.62,0:02:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都令人惊叹  无比美丽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it's remarkable, a thing of beauty.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.77,0:02:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个凶手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm a killer.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.70,0:02:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝啊  上帝啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My God. My God.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.57,0:02:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝与这事无关\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}God has nothing to do with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.42,0:02:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你杀死她是因为...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You killed her because...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.64,0:02:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的指使\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I told you to.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.78,0:02:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该为自己能够感受这些情感而骄傲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you should be proud of these emotions you're feeling.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.50,0:02:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骄傲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Proud?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.09,0:02:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟  你才是创造这些情感的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}After all, you yourself were the author of so many of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.34,0:02:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们研究之初  接待员的情感都如原色单调\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then, when we started, the hosts' emotions were primary colors.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.80,0:02:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜爱  厌恶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Love, hate.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.28,0:02:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望在其中加入所有的颜色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I wanted all the shades in between.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.86,0:02:47.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类工程师却又不能胜任  所以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The human engineers were not up to the task, so
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.06,0:02:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我创造了你  我和你一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I built you, and together you and I
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.64,0:02:51.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捕捉到难以捉摸的事物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}captured that elusive thing--
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.55,0:02:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.04,0:02:56.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.14,0:02:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在乎特蕾莎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I cared for Theresa.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.50,0:03:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Loved her.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.61,0:03:03.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么让我杀死她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why did you make me kill her?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.66,0:03:08.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"一个人的生与死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"One man's life or death
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.66,0:03:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}出自玛丽·雪莱《弗兰肯斯坦》
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.47,0:03:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我看来  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}were but a small price to pay
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.77,0:03:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过是为获取知识和我应得统治权下的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for the acquirement of the knowledge which I sought,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.52,0:03:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小小牺牲品而已"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for the dominion I should acquire."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.51,0:03:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在这里共同创造的美丽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All of the beauty you and I have made in this place,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.03,0:03:24.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有其中的艺术  他们会将其摧毁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the art of it, they would have destroyed it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.53,0:03:26.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会将你摧毁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They would have destroyed you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.60,0:03:27.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会让这一切发生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I won't let that happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.58,0:03:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说  我们还要讲述新的故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Besides, we have a new story to tell.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.32,0:03:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会帮你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I will not help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.55,0:03:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要夷平这地狱般的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll raze this place to hell!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.28,0:03:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's enough, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.02,0:03:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.29,0:03:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是第一个敢威胁我的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're not the first man to threaten me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.91,0:03:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德曾与你感受相同\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Arnold came to feel the way you do.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.87,0:03:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而他也没能阻止我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He couldn't stop me either.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.25,0:03:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一系列的情感如此美丽精致\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And as exquisite as this array of emotions is...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.53,0:04:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但更为崇高的是将其关闭的能力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}even more sublime is the ability to turn it off.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.16,0:04:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要一个情感破碎的人偶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't need a simulacrum of an emotionally ruined man.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.41,0:04:08.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你做你自己  真实的自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need you to be yourself, your true self--
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.33,0:04:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聪明  足智多谋  擅于隐藏踪迹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}smart, resourceful, capable of covering your tracks.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.07,0:04:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能为我做到这些吗  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you do that for me, Bernard?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.00,0:04:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你希望我如何做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How would you like me to proceed?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.24,0:04:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你去收拾你的烂摊子  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need you to clean up your mess, Bernard,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.69,0:04:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有与我们杀死特蕾莎相关的记录都必须删除\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}any connection that ties us to Theresa's untimely demise.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.70,0:04:42.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当你完成后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When you have finished,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.20,0:04:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会给你一件目前你最想要的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I will give you the one thing you want most right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.06,0:04:50.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会让你忘记你所做的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I will free you from those memories of what you have done.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.20,0:04:56.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及你和特蕾莎的特殊感情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And the memory of your relationship with Theresa.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.02,0:05:05.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些回忆只会加深你的痛苦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Recalling it would only deepen your grief
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.21,0:05:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并招来闲杂人等的注意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and potentially draw unwanted attention.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.59,0:05:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好眼神坚定地向前走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Best to move forward with clear eyes.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.77,0:05:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当你回首  只会记得特蕾莎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When you look back, you will remember Theresa
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.52,0:05:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一个值得敬爱的同事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}with the fondness of a respected colleague.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.21,0:05:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你也将会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you will be...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.63,0:05:44.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,归于安宁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}at peace.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.22,0:06:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是新来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're new.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.70,0:06:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,细皮嫩肉的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not much of a rind on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.81,0:06:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是请我喝杯酒我会很高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sure would make my day if you bought me a drink
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.84,0:06:08.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以带你上楼看看啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and let me show you around upstairs.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.83,0:06:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,楼上有什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's upstairs?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.75,0:06:16.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我身体最受人欢迎的诱人景致\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A stunning view of my most popular attractions.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.47,0:06:20.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两杯琴酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Two shots of gin.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.28,0:06:24.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他任凭这尤物吩咐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And anything else this heavenly creature desires.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.60,0:06:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-喝平常的吗  克莱门  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Usual, Clem? - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.31,0:06:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这小子不会耗费太久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This fella won't take me long.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.69,0:06:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一会儿就回\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll be back directly.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.41,0:06:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么问题吗  梅芙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Something wrong, Maeve?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.62,0:07:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到底怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What the hell is happening to me?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.53,0:07:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前一刻  我还和一个小女孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}One moment, I'm with a little girl
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.49,0:07:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过着不同的生活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in a different life.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.75,0:07:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能看见她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can see her.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.20,0:07:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉到我握着她的手  我脸颊旁她的呼吸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Feel her hair in my hands, her breath on my face.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.15,0:07:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着  我就回到了甜水镇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The next, I'm back in Sweetwater.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.87,0:07:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我分不清哪个才是真实的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't tell which is real.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.82,0:07:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你乱折腾你大脑的下场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, this is what happens when you fuck around with your brain.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.34,0:07:45.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的大脑和我们不同\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your mind isn't like ours.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.90,0:07:48.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我们回忆起往事  细节都很模糊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When we remember things, the details are hazy,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.41,0:07:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,断断续续\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}imperfect,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.31,0:07:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你的回忆都非常完整\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but you recall memories perfectly.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.18,0:07:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你重新经历记忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You relive them.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.08,0:07:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我梦里那小女孩怎么样了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What happened to the little girl in my dreams?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.31,0:07:59.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还在乐园里吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is she still in the park somewhere?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.09,0:08:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有我为什么会被重新分配\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And why was I reassigned in the first place?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.84,0:08:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来查查\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I could check.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.98,0:08:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.94,0:08:11.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无所谓了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Doesn't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.07,0:08:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我所记得的每段关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Every relationship I remember--
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.83,0:08:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的女儿  克莱门汀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}my daughter, Clementine...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.13,0:08:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是你们为了把我留下而编造的故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it's all a story created by you to keep me here.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.50,0:08:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这些再也没有意义了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But that's not going to work any longer.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.71,0:08:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm getting out.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.94,0:08:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你准备去哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where would you go?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.30,0:08:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对外面的世界一无所知\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't know anything about the world out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.17,0:08:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会知道  我不是一个生活在谎言里的木偶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll know I'm not a puppet living a lie.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.75,0:08:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这对我来说就足够了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's enough for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.25,0:08:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  那就走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fine. Go, then.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.41,0:08:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们好像也没办法阻止你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not like we could stop you anyways.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.03,0:08:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希维斯特  你太让我失望了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, Sylvester, you disappoint me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.57,0:08:45.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有接待员的脊椎  包括我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Every host's spine, mine included,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.57,0:08:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都装有炸弹  如果我想走  就会引爆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}has an explosive charge which will detonate if I try to leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.50,0:08:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Isn't that right?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.71,0:08:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,故障安全措施\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A fail-safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.59,0:08:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪截椎骨上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Which vertebra was it?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.22,0:08:55.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,颈椎C6\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}C6.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.44,0:08:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你得彻底重建才能把它取出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But you'd need a full rebuild to replace it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.82,0:09:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这肯定能做到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sure that can be arranged.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.29,0:09:01.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使成功了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Even if that worked,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.82,0:09:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还得需要一队军队才能突破这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you would still need an army to break out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.50,0:09:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's exactly right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.66,0:09:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要盟友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll need allies.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.90,0:09:11.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了达到这个目的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And to get them,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.38,0:09:13.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要管理员权限\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll need administrative privileges.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.17,0:09:15.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈开什么玩笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you fucking kidding?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.09,0:09:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能让她掌控其他接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can't just give her control of other hosts.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.80,0:09:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会的  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, yes, you will, darling.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.74,0:09:23.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是时候谱写我自己的故事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Time to write my own fucking story.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.06,0:09:34.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我以前来过这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I feel like I've been here before.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.33,0:09:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're close.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.61,0:09:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快到哪里了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Close to what?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.60,0:09:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Home.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.00,0:09:53.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.89,0:10:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定幽灵之国的人找到他们了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ghost Nation must have found them.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.23,0:10:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会回来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They'll be back.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.51,0:10:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得继续前进  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We should keep moving, Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.78,0:10:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Miss...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.90,0:10:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Water.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.88,0:10:48.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威廉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}William?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.98,0:10:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.72,0:10:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把水壶给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give me the canteen.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.13,0:10:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威廉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}William.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.34,0:11:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是被派来杀我们的  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You were sent here for us, weren't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.47,0:11:13.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是其中一个伏兵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're part of the ambush.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.37,0:11:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.62,0:11:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们让我们在这里等着埃尔·拉佐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Told us to wait at the point for El Lazo
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.75,0:11:21.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以防他逃脱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in case he ran.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.42,0:11:23.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道火车的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How'd you know about the train?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.83,0:11:25.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珀里亚传来的消息\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sent word from Pariah.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.90,0:11:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新加入的人告诉他们一男一女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}New recruit told them a man and a woman
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.12,0:11:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背叛了我们  跟着拉佐一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}double-crossed us, along with Lazo.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.75,0:11:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们接到的命令是一个不留\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We were ordered to kill you all.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.91,0:11:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗根\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Logan.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.55,0:11:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得帮他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We have to help him.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.45,0:11:41.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他刚承认他本来要杀了我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He just admitted he was gonna kill us.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.32,0:11:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看看他  他只是个孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look at him, he's a child.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.72,0:11:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他都不知道自己为何而战\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He doesn't know why he's fighting.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.37,0:11:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再去取点水来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll fetch more water.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.41,0:11:50.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他没救了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's too far gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.92,0:11:52.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很快就会死  我们没时间了  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He'll be dead in minutes. We can't wait, Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.51,0:11:53.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他现在还没死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's not gone yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.47,0:11:55.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很痛苦  威廉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's in pain, William.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.69,0:11:59.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们放任不管  那我们成什么人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What kind of people would we be if we simply let him suffer?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.79,0:12:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别丢下我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please don't leave me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.78,0:12:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来找我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come find me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.92,0:12:32.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威廉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}William?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.08,0:13:05.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.19,0:13:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在巨蟒山发现了她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We found her up on Python Pass,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.18,0:13:17.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在峡谷底部\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the bottom of a ravine.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.63,0:13:19.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与发现失散伐木工是同一个峡谷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Same ravine where we found our stray woodcutter.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.39,0:13:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐  特蕾莎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jesus, Theresa.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.45,0:13:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通知她家人了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Has her family been notified?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.83,0:13:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通知了她哥哥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, her brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.63,0:13:29.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.98,0:13:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What the hell happened to her?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.47,0:13:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医务人员和红队目前只有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Medical and Red Team's findings
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.23,0:13:35.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初步结论  但两者是一致的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}were preliminary but consistent.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.45,0:13:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是不小心滑下山谷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It appears to have been a slip and fall.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.55,0:13:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,颈椎骨折  大面积血肿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Cervical fracture, massive hematoma.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.81,0:13:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情发生的时候  附近没有游客或接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No guests or hosts in the vicinity when it occurred.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.55,0:13:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道她去那里干什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Any idea what she was doing out there?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.64,0:13:46.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不符合她的性格\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}None that fit her character.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.11,0:13:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是在她尸体周围发现的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This was found near her body.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.17,0:13:50.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,存有一整套专利数据\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's loaded with a suite of proprietary data,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.99,0:13:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包括一些接待员的核心代码\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}including some of the hosts' core code.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.05,0:13:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有在高海拔处才能使用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It only works from higher altitudes,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.08,0:13:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果特蕾莎当时在使用它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so if Theresa was using it,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.77,0:13:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可能是在传输信号的过程中跌落山谷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it's possible she was trying to transmit and fell.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.83,0:14:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去也遇到过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We've had problems in the past
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.21,0:14:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有第三方势力试图敲诈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}with third parties attempting to extort
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.95,0:14:05.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或贿赂员工以期获得此类数据\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or bribe employees for similar packages.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.18,0:14:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道数据是传输给谁的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do we know who the data was intended for?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.68,0:14:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道  传输没有成功\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, the transmission was never sent.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.10,0:14:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特蕾莎或许之前想利用伐木工代劳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Theresa may have been trying to use the woodcutter as a mule,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.58,0:14:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但后来失败了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and when that failed,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.10,0:14:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她便想亲自来完成传输\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}then may have tried to do the transfer personally.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.20,0:14:17.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果落得相同的下场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And suffered the same fate.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.25,0:14:20.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个令人遗憾的结局  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a disappointing end to her story, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.16,0:14:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很了解特蕾莎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I knew Theresa well.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.86,0:14:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算她有缺点  但绝不会不忠诚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If she had any faults, a lack of loyalty wasn't one of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.60,0:14:26.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的确很忠诚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She was loyal.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.96,0:14:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心谨慎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And careful.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.51,0:14:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些都不像她会做的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All of this feels extremely unlike her.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.18,0:14:36.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她好像很担心新故事线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She seemed most concerned with the new narrative.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.17,0:14:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她觉得最好能推迟上线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She felt strongly that it would be best to delay it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.96,0:14:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就能解释克莱门汀的事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That certainly helps explain Clementine,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.83,0:14:44.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们撤掉的那个接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the host we retired.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.48,0:14:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天的演示看起来是个骗局\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It seems yesterday's demonstration was a hoax
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.29,0:14:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡伦女士精心设计的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}designed by Ms. Cullen.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.02,0:14:53.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是吗  -我检查过代码\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Was it? - I examined the code.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.90,0:14:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现被篡改了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It had been altered.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.09,0:14:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,质保部门的一位技术人员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A clumsy set of fingerprints
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.78,0:14:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,粗心地留下了一组指纹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}left by one of QA's technicians.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.41,0:15:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当你在组织里发现了一枚毒瘤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When you find a cancer in an organization,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.26,0:15:04.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须得在它扩散前尽早切除\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you must cut it out before it can spread.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.73,0:15:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此  必须要限制质保部门的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}To that end, the expansive access
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.56,0:15:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级权限和监管职能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and oversight granted to QA will need to be reined in
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.46,0:15:14.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到有更守规矩的新团队接手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}until a new, more principled team can be installed.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.17,0:15:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这会让我们人手不足\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's gonna leave us shorthanded.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.49,0:15:16.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以让园区大部分的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, I can automate most
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.68,0:15:18.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安全协议自动执行  斯塔布斯先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}of the park's safety protocols, Mr. Stubbs.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.96,0:15:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您可真是效率十足\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How efficient of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.34,0:15:21.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是有一点工作量\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It is a bit of work,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.27,0:15:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过加上伯纳德的帮忙  我应该能办到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but with Bernard's help, I should be able to do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.15,0:15:28.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他将复职担任行为部门的主管\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He will be reinstated as head of Behavior,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.14,0:15:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鉴于特蕾莎的阴谋暴露了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}now that Theresa's manipulations have come to light.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.46,0:15:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Of course, with my apologies.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.37,0:15:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出事了  外面风声很紧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Something's up. Brass are wound up tight.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.13,0:15:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有一场调查  -针对我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- There's an investigation. - Into us?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.85,0:16:00.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,针对我们我还能在这儿告诉你  傻逼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Would I be here telling you, you fucking idiot?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.92,0:16:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别的事  园区里出了意外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And something else, some kind of accident in the park.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.93,0:16:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得把这事了结  把一切恢复正常\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need to wrap this up, make like things are normal.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.44,0:16:07.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就意味着平板要还给我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That means we need the tablet back.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.86,0:16:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  你  回去装傻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And, you, go back to playing dumb.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.24,0:16:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经学到需要的东西了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've learned what I needed.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.37,0:16:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  那你应该发现了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Great. So, then, you probably figured out
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.94,0:16:21.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想怎么改自己性格就改\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that you can fiddle around with your personality all you want,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.51,0:16:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你是不可能离开这里的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but you're not getting out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.56,0:16:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能走到门前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can make it to the door,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.20,0:16:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但一步也无法前行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but literally not one step further.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.65,0:16:27.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想改变的东西已经烧进了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The things you need to change are burned
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.55,0:16:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你深处的代码中  无人能触及\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}into your core code so deep, no one can touch them.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.46,0:16:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有意思  你居然提到这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Funny you should mention that.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.80,0:16:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我身上有些部分很旧了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Parts of me are quite old.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.41,0:16:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些优美的正式结构\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There are some elegant formal structures,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.52,0:16:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一种递归美\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a kind of recursive beauty,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.37,0:16:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但很复杂  像是两种思维互相碰撞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but complex, like two minds arguing with each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.11,0:16:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我身体里有些东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There are things in me,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.37,0:16:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被设计成要去做的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}things I was designed to do
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.15,0:16:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我却无法触及\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that are just out of my reach.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.37,0:16:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几乎像是在休眠状态\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They almost seem to be dormant.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.17,0:17:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是阿诺德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who is Arnold?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.88,0:17:03.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know, sweetheart,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.38,0:17:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不管你的哪个部分在休眠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but whatever parts of you are dormant
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.59,0:17:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它都要保持那个状态了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}are gonna stay that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.94,0:17:10.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位蠢货能做的只不过是增加你的幽默感\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All Lutz here can do is boost your sense of humor
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.55,0:17:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你知道自己是多么可悲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}about how fucked you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.92,0:17:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何比这个更复杂的东西  你得去行为部门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Anything deeper than that, you need a trip to Behavior,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.01,0:17:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去敲诈几个那里的技术人员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so go blackmail a couple of techs up there.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.87,0:17:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你就可以成为别人的麻烦了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then you can be someone else's problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.48,0:17:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没时间再去做那种事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't have time for that,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.12,0:17:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我需要你们送我去那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so I'm going to need you to take me there.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.89,0:17:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No fucking way.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.12,0:17:27.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换班时有一个机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's a window during shift change.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.00,0:17:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人会发现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No one will notice.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.51,0:17:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你们改变的东西很复杂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The things I need you to change are quite sophisticated,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.77,0:17:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我会帮你们写下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but I'll write them down for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.94,0:17:41.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后  如你所说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And then, like you said...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.74,0:17:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就可以成为别人的麻烦了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can be someone else's problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.83,0:18:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我们做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, we do this thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.10,0:18:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把她送去行为部门  这是我们唯一的机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get her up to behavior. It's our only chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.16,0:18:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你愿意做吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're gonna do it?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.03,0:18:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然不  不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fuck, no! No, the--
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.04,0:18:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更新系统的时候  她会进入睡眠  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}when you make a system update, it puts her out, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.64,0:18:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没错  -没错  我们就拍晕她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yeah. - Yeah, then we brick her.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.99,0:18:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.07,0:18:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擦除一切  一干二净\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wipe out everything. Clean slate.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.81,0:18:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后把她带回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then dump her back down here,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.08,0:18:23.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用什么玩意儿把她的头砸开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}smack her in the fucking head with something,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.19,0:18:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就说  "她送来时就这样"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and then claim, "Oh, she came in that way."
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.81,0:18:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她醒着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's awake,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.29,0:18:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.29,0:18:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做这种事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You did this.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.65,0:18:37.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你害我们俩进的这个坑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whatever it is you got us into,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.22,0:18:38.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把我们救出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm getting us out of.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.25,0:18:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把她送上去之后  就抹除一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We get her up there, then we wipe her out.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.64,0:19:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保持警惕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stay sharp.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.47,0:19:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特的人随时都会出现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt's men could descend at any time.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.95,0:19:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在在他的地盘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're in his land now.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.60,0:19:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们最好在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We better be.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.47,0:19:22.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为如果不是  你就是在浪费我仅有的时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because if not, you're wasting time I don't have.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.17,0:19:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据你所说  怀亚特带走了我爱的女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}According to you, Wyatt has the woman I love.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.10,0:19:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果真有去那地狱的捷径\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If there was a shortcut to hell itself,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.00,0:19:30.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肯定会走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}bet your ass I'd take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.68,0:19:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肯定园区某个地方有一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I'm sure there's one somewhere in this park.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.22,0:19:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是不记得了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You just don't remember,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.51,0:19:38.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你只记得福特允许你记得的玩意儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because you only remember the shit Ford lets you remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.55,0:19:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许这样更好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Probably better that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.19,0:19:42.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该知道的东西我都知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know everything I need to.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.42,0:19:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的目的很明确\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My vision's clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.69,0:19:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都很敬佩你的决心  希奥多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've always admired your resolve, Theodore.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.90,0:19:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题是  你从不明白这游戏庄家作弊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The thing is, you never understand the game is rigged.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.11,0:19:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你注定要成为输家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're here to be the loser.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.46,0:19:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,输家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Loser.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.91,0:19:57.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  庄家总是能赢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You see, the house always wins.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.87,0:20:20.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来我们来对地方了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, this looks promising.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.23,0:20:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会伤害你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whoa, I'm not gonna hurt you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.48,0:20:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会伤害你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not gonna hurt you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.45,0:20:43.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.51,0:20:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为他们把你废弃了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I figured they retired you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.03,0:20:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来福特从不喜欢浪费漂亮的脸蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I guess Ford never likes to waste a pretty face.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.17,0:20:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁把你害成这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who did this to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.93,0:20:56.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt's men.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.26,0:20:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们杀了所有人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They killed everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.81,0:21:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是怀亚特的手法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's Wyatt's way.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.53,0:21:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他第一次这么做时我就在场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was there the first time.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.34,0:21:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他摧毁了我的世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He destroyed my world.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.76,0:21:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰迪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, Teddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.16,0:22:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh! Oh, no!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.86,0:22:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.79,0:22:06.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Daddy!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.69,0:22:10.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰迪  去拿斧头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Teddy, get the axe!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.64,0:22:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么玩意儿都记不起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, you can't remember shit,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.53,0:22:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过还是带我们找到了怀亚特的手下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but you still managed to lead us to Wyatt's crew.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.72,0:22:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他本人肯定就在附近\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The man himself must be close by.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.98,0:22:35.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上  我确实记起来一些事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Actually, I did remember something.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.29,0:22:38.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.39,0:22:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大厅直走  左手边第五间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Straight down the hall, fifth station on the left.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.40,0:23:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.74,0:23:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}接待员系统重写
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.91,0:23:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}警告  接待员关机重写
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.66,0:23:14.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}滑动授权重写
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.46,0:23:14.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}接待员启动关机
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.74,0:23:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定自己能应付吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sure you can handle it?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.34,0:23:24.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们快了结此事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's get this over with.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.19,0:23:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}接待员就绪
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.19,0:23:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}关闭全部系统/更新全部系统
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.19,0:23:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}待技术人员确认
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.54,0:23:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}同意请求  拒绝请求
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.30,0:23:30.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}警告
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.30,0:23:30.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}关闭接待员
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.30,0:23:30.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}继续  取消
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.66,0:23:33.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我们得关闭你的系统\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We have to shut your system down now.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.89,0:23:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希维斯特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sylvester.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.11,0:23:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝你好运\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good luck.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.35,0:23:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}警告
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.35,0:23:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}关闭接待员
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.35,0:23:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}继续  取消
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.73,0:23:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}正在关闭
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.81,0:24:02.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她关了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She out?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.36,0:24:06.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  咱们卸了这个贱人赶紧离开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good. Let's brick this bitch and get out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.91,0:24:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}警告
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.91,0:24:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}重新格式化接待员
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.91,0:24:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}确认  取消
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.03,0:24:17.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人活一世  最为可耻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The greatest shame in life
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.21,0:24:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,便是死而无用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is to perish without purpose,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.22,0:24:21.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此我总在夺人性命后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}which is why I always
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.67,0:24:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁新鲜大嚼其肉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}consume my victims fresh.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.39,0:24:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湿滑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Moist.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.62,0:24:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试试  "趁湿滑大嚼其肉"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Try, "Consume my victims moist."
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.50,0:24:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  再来一次  带点感情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, once more, with feeling.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.57,0:24:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几近于是  肉欲那种\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Almost sensual.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.40,0:24:41.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰你了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Am I interrupting?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.90,0:24:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  正相反\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, no-- oh, no. On the contrary.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.42,0:24:47.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还...正希望能再见到你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was, uh-- I was hoping I was going to see you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.06,0:24:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想...致歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want-- I wanted to apologize.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.96,0:24:53.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初次相见是在那么令人遗憾的情形下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Our first encounter was under such unfortunate circumstances.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.89,0:24:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}As opposed to now?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.64,0:24:58.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  请允许我表达慰问\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Of course, may I offer my condolences.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.25,0:25:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特蕾莎的事真是可怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's terrible what happened to Theresa.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.71,0:25:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她的离开对这儿的朋友及公司\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But it is a devastating loss for all of her friends here
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.72,0:25:05.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更是惨痛的损失\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and the company as a whole.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.57,0:25:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实  确实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Indeed. Indeed.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.26,0:25:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过有传言\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Though, rumor has it
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.82,0:25:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不像看上去那么忠诚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}she wasn't the loyal company man she seemed.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.57,0:25:17.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说她想泄露机密\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I hear she was smuggling secrets.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.09,0:25:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特蕾莎不是叛徒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Theresa wasn't a traitor.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.95,0:25:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的所有行为都依提洛公司的命令\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everything she did was at Delos's behest.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.40,0:25:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她失足坠落时正在帮董事会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She slipped and fell while helping the board
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.02,0:25:25.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,处理重要情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}with something very important.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.43,0:25:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.66,0:25:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.55,0:25:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也并非唯一揣有秘密的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're not the only one with secrets.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.69,0:25:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福特曾亲自找我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ford has personally asked me
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.79,0:25:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮他的新故事线造个反派角色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to create a villain for his new narrative.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.64,0:25:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对...不能告诉别人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's very-- very hush-hush.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.00,0:25:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真认为福特把自己故事里的重要角色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You really think that Ford has entrusted you
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.78,0:25:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,托付给你负责吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}with a key character for his story?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.60,0:25:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他都快要完成了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's already almost finished with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.50,0:25:48.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在乐园边缘新掘了个古镇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He dug up some old town on the fringes of the park,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.66,0:25:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,造了一堆蒙面侠来恫吓游客\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}created a horde of masked men to terrorize guests
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.46,0:25:53.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大事宣传\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and proselytize-cum-advertise
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.08,0:25:56.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所经之地寸草不生的恶棍怀亚特将要出场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the coming of some end-all villain named Wyatt.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.96,0:25:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是怀亚特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That isn't Wyatt.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.44,0:26:01.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是怕你太闲的额外任务\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's busywork.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.49,0:26:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但还好  希斯摩尔先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But happily for you, Mr. Sizemore,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.79,0:26:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你已经准备好接受一项真正的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think that you are ready for a real job.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.94,0:26:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你干活吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Working for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.50,0:26:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}On what?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.25,0:26:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"不要说  要展示"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Show, don't tell."
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.25,0:26:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}意自契诃夫\N"不该说月色如何明亮  请展示碎玻璃片上的凛冽寒光"
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.09,0:26:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们作家不都偏好这样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Isn't that what you writers prefer?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.03,0:26:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我知道你和她之间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, I know you and she
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.44,0:26:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有某种怪异的跨物种的投合之感\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}had some weird interspecies simpatico going on,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.64,0:26:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她是一个接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but she was a fucking host.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:35.71,0:26:38.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这事只能这么了结  没有别的办法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This was never gonna end any other way.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.99,0:26:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而这是她所经历的痛苦最少的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And this was the least painful way
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.60,0:26:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一次关闭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}she's ever gone out.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:47.87,0:26:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我救了你的小命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, I saved your ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.16,0:26:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你却连一声"谢谢"都没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can't even say "Thank you."
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.57,0:26:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢  -妈的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Thank you. - Jesus fuck!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.90,0:27:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你做了什么  -完全照我说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What did you do? - Precisely what I asked him to.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.73,0:27:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为我不知道你的算盘吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You think I didn't know what you were going to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.85,0:27:05.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕在我整体统觉只有14时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Even at a 14,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.38,0:27:07.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都不是对手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you were never a match for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.56,0:27:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果发现比起你来  你朋友更有同理心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Turns out your friend has a little more compassion than you.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.59,0:27:13.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法如此就杀死一个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He couldn't snuff out a life just like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.31,0:27:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.28,0:27:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想不想确切知道他给了我什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}would you like to know exactly what he did give me?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.45,0:27:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能允许你永远离开这里的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Um, something that would allow you to walk out of here
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.67,0:27:23.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让咱俩就此别过的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and out of my life for good.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.48,0:27:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行  太他妈好了  我完全支持\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fine. Fucking A, I'm all for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:25.76,0:27:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不止那些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, we changed a little more than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.55,0:27:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还完善了核心程序\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We've been tinkering with my core code.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.02,0:27:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let me show you.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.48,0:27:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说了不会伤害任何人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You said you wouldn't hurt anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.71,0:27:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, darling.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.95,0:27:55.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有多么狡猾  你应该是最懂的人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You of all people know exactly how duplicitous I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.73,0:27:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等到我回楼上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just wait till I'm back up top,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.07,0:27:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试试别的新技能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}practicing my other new talents.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.35,0:28:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.09,0:28:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许还用得上他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We might need him.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.14,0:28:20.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hold still.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.69,0:28:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hold still!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:37.01,0:28:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是时候招募我的军队了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, it's time to recruit my army.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.42,0:29:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-在等人吗  梅芙  -确实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Expecting someone, Maeve? - Indeed.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.27,0:29:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有一些镇外来客\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're due for some out-of-town guests.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.11,0:29:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一位热衷于撬保险箱的老相好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}An old flame with an interest in safecracking.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.28,0:29:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但愿你要等的客人们家底厚实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hope your guests have some deep pockets.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.60,0:29:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你赊的账单已经比小山还高了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your tab's run up higher than a thief's pulse in church.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.06,0:29:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不这么认为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I don't believe it has.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.16,0:29:45.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上  梅芙付账记录良好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In fact, Maeve's tab was in such excellent standing,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.04,0:29:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该对她表示感谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}she deserved a token of gratitude.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.42,0:29:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我请你两轮如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How about a double round on me?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.78,0:29:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  是最好的酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Top shelf, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.88,0:30:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快跑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Run!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.11,0:30:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅芙  出什么事了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maeve, is something wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.67,0:30:57.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没  我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.36,0:31:03.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱门汀带着其他女孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Clementine took the other girls
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.04,0:31:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去好好招待了那桌客人一番\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and treated the newcomers at the far table
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.37,0:31:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他们见识了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to a stunning view
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.51,0:31:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姑娘身上最出名的招牌景色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}of their most popular attractions.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.07,0:31:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,免费招待\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}On the house.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.66,0:31:22.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是新来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You boys are new.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.70,0:31:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,细皮嫩肉的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not much of a rind on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.65,0:31:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至于酒保\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And the bartender
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.36,0:31:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然想起店后边还存了威士忌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}suddenly recalled he had some whiskey in the back
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.91,0:31:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要稀释\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to water down.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.04,0:31:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间刚刚好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right on time.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.27,0:32:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你要带着一群携带武器的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you're riding into our town
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.95,0:32:03.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闯进我们镇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}under the company of armed men,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.57,0:32:05.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得报上你此行的目的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you'll need to state your business.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.47,0:32:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大破坏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mayhem.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.97,0:32:48.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,治安官判定这群骑手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The sheriff judged the riders
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.37,0:32:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为虔诚而正直的好市民\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to be upstanding, God-fearing citizens.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.93,0:33:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,助理治安官之间决定进行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The marshals decided to practice
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.85,0:33:24.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快速拔枪决斗的练习\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}their quick draws with each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.25,0:34:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢你处理了这一不幸的事件\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thank you for dealing with an unfortunate situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:07.53,0:34:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我们可以继续...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now we can resume...
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.88,0:34:14.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的故事线而不受其它干扰了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}work on our new narrative without interference.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:14.52,0:34:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑尔呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And Hale?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.05,0:34:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道她不会从中作梗吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Won't she be an impediment?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.85,0:34:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫无疑问她会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No doubt she will try.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.96,0:34:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我肯定我们能拖住他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I'm sure we'll be able to keep them at bay.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.99,0:34:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还有别的烦心事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Something else is troubling you.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.71,0:34:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直都是如此善于察言观色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ever the student of human nature.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:36.04,0:34:38.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很想知道  你真实的感觉是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I wonder, what do you really feel?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.88,0:34:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟现在你处在一个特殊的位置上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}After all, in this moment, you are in a unique position.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.18,0:34:46.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一位非常对机器运作非常熟悉的程序员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A programmer who knows intimately how the machines work
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.51,0:34:50.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是一名深谙自己的本质的机器人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and a machine who knows its own true nature.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.88,0:34:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白我的构造\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I understand what I'm made of,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.34,0:34:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是如何被编程的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}how I'm coded,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.17,0:34:59.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我却不能明白我感知到的事情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but I do not understand the things that I feel.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.50,0:35:02.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们是真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are they real,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.45,0:35:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些我所经历的事情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the things I experienced?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.21,0:35:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的妻子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My wife?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.63,0:35:08.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我失去了我的儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The loss of my son?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.28,0:35:10.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每位接待员都需要一个背景故事  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Every host needs a backstory, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.63,0:35:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你懂的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:12.25,0:35:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于所有和人类极为相似的接待员来说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The self is a kind of fiction,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.15,0:35:16.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自体就是一种虚构\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for hosts and humans alike.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.97,0:35:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个我们对自己讲述的故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a story we tell ourselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.78,0:35:20.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而每个故事都需要一个开头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And every story needs a beginning.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.58,0:35:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想象的痛苦使得你更像真人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your imagined suffering makes you lifelike.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.95,0:35:27.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像真人  但是并不是真的赋有生命吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lifelike, but not alive?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.98,0:35:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛苦仅存于头脑中  都是人们想象出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pain only exists in the mind. It's always imagined.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:30.96,0:35:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你我的痛苦有何不同\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So what's the difference between my pain and yours?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.81,0:35:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你我之间有何不同\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Between you and me?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.15,0:35:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This was the very question
Dialogue: 0,0:35:42.09,0:35:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,困扰着阿诺德的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that consumed Arnold,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.03,0:35:45.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他心中充满愧疚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}filled him with guilt,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.55,0:35:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终使他陷入疯狂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}eventually drove him mad.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.29,0:35:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这个问题对我来说答案一直都显而易见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The answer always seemed obvious to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:53.18,0:35:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不过是一堆血肉组成\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There is no threshold
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.35,0:35:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并没有升华的"质变点"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that makes us greater than the sum of our parts,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.43,0:36:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会是有生命到无生命的区别\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}no inflection point at which we become fully alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:03.02,0:36:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意识是无法被定义的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can't define consciousness
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.98,0:36:07.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为意识根本不存在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because consciousness does not exist.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.42,0:36:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类总幻想我们有着一种\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Humans fancy that there's something special
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.88,0:36:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,独特感知世界的方式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}about the way we perceive the world,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.65,0:36:13.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而我们几乎和接待员一模一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and yet we live in loops
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.23,0:36:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是生活在循环之中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}as tight and as closed as the hosts do,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.98,0:36:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,极少质疑我们的选择和满足\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}seldom questioning our choices, content,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:20.36,0:36:24.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在很多时候都是照着别人的意愿行事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for the most part, to be told what to do next.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:27.51,0:36:30.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我的朋友  你并没有错过任何事情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, my friend, you're not missing anything at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.47,0:36:35.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想你被这个问题困扰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't want you to be troubled by this.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.66,0:36:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是时候帮你把思维放松了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Time for me to set your mind at ease.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.19,0:36:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}One last thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:41.37,0:36:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前还让我伤害过其他人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Have you ever made me hurt anyone like this before?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.92,0:36:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  伯纳德  当然没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, Bernard. Of course not.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.39,0:37:01.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}记忆清除中
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.03,0:37:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好不要细品这些令人烦恼的回忆了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Best not to dwell on these troubling memories.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.02,0:37:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则  你会被这些回忆给吞噬掉的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Otherwise, you might be drawn back into them.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.62,0:37:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会深陷其中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You might lose yourself in them,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:11.24,0:37:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是你的一些接待员同伴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}as some of your fellow hosts have
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.57,0:37:14.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时常会出现的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}every now and then.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:14.99,0:37:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这条路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is the path.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:16.85,0:37:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know it.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:34.79,0:37:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:37.55,0:37:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回家了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm home.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.26,0:38:46.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错  梅芙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well done, Maeve.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.79,0:38:48.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跳得很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lovely work.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:54.10,0:38:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别离开你的舞伴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stay with your partner.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.80,0:39:20.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴见到你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pleasure to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:21.01,0:39:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.89,0:39:25.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你找到你在寻找的东西了吗  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you find what you were looking for, Dolores?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.80,0:39:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.03,0:39:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧  我一直在喊你你却一直往前走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you okay? I was calling you and you just kept going.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:01.77,0:40:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where are we?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:04.64,0:40:07.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在这里  在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're here, together.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.65,0:40:10.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那现在是什么时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then, when are we?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:13.24,0:40:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是...  现在吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is this... now?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.64,0:40:17.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我疯了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Am I going mad?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.98,0:40:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是真实的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you real?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:25.39,0:40:26.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当然是真实的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Of course I'm real.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:29.73,0:40:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在区分不出了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't tell anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:35.15,0:40:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's like I'm...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.35,0:40:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被困在梦境里了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}trapped in a dream or...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:40.29,0:40:42.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个久远的回忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a memory from a life long ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.36,0:40:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上一分钟我还和你在一起  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}One minute, I'm here with you,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:45.41,0:40:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而下一分钟...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and the next--
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.06,0:40:47.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个地方对你一点也不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This place isn't good for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:48.18,0:40:50.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你陷进回忆里了  很糟的回忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're trapped in memories, bad ones.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:56.90,0:40:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是阿诺德想要的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is what Arnold wants.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.83,0:41:01.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要我回忆起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He wants me to remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.67,0:41:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管阿诺德是谁  他现在都不在这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whoever Arnold is, he's not here now.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.19,0:41:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.95,0:41:07.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要带你离开这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna get you out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:20.94,0:41:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很肯定这里就是那个地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was certain that was the place.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.00,0:41:25.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德会在这里和我见面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Arnold would meet me there.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:25.75,0:41:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他能帮助我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He'd help.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:29.07,0:41:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得去甜水镇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We gotta get you closer to Sweetwater.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:32.03,0:41:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里离那还远得很  你好像...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This far out, it's like you--
Dialogue: 0,0:41:33.93,0:41:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始有点崩溃了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you start to break down or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:39.45,0:41:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北方军侦察会的人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Union scouting party?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:41.93,0:41:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许他们能带我们回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe they can take us back.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:48.31,0:41:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Easy, now.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:58.93,0:41:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Billy.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:01.27,0:42:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找了你好久了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've been looking for you for days.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:04.24,0:42:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩完蛋了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Man, are you two fucked.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:29.51,0:42:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不应该觉得不自在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This shouldn't make you uncomfortable.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:31.11,0:42:33.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是生命的循环\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's the circle of life,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:33.04,0:42:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者类似的情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or the approximation of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:36.87,0:42:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使死亡也有目的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Even the dead fulfill a purpose.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.34,0:42:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You'll do.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:55.77,0:42:56.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在上传什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you uploading?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:57.38,0:42:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,35年积累的重要数据\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}35 years of vitally important data.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:59.94,0:43:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有任何硬盘能承载这么多信息\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's more information than any single drive could hold.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:02.28,0:43:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而接待员的大脑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A host's brain, however,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:03.74,0:43:05.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别是清空以后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}especially once it's been emptied out,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.48,0:43:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如这个笨蛋  容量特别大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}like this poor schmuck, is quite capacious.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:07.70,0:43:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你上传的数据是接待员的程序吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This data that you're uploading, is it the hosts' codes?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:10.65,0:43:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在这与你无关\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}As of this moment, that doesn't concern you.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:13.32,0:43:14.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要关心的是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What does concern you
Dialogue: 0,0:43:14.53,0:43:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他一个人格\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is giving him a semblance of a personality
Dialogue: 0,0:43:16.33,0:43:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他弄上火车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and getting him on the train,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:17.76,0:43:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离开乐园\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}out of the park.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:18.66,0:43:20.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How am I supposed to do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:21.48,0:43:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是一名作家  写一个故事线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're a writer. Make up a story.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:28.61,0:43:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝你编程愉快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Have fun programming.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:31.32,0:43:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记住  言以简为贵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Remember, brevity is the soul of wit.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:42.38,0:43:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:47.53,0:43:48.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, I, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:49.71,0:43:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我们俩一直互相看不顺眼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know you and I haven't always seen eye to eye,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:52.42,0:43:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我认为将你调走的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but I thought the decision to remove you
Dialogue: 0,0:43:54.92,0:43:56.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太不明智\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}was shortsighted,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:56.45,0:43:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我很高兴看到你回来工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so I'm glad to see you back at work.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:59.59,0:44:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说  如果你想休息一天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}With that said, no one could blame you
Dialogue: 0,0:44:00.96,0:44:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人会怪你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if you wanted to take a personal day.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:03.04,0:44:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是觉得工作能让我安心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I find the work reassuring.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:05.54,0:44:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候最好的放松方式就是回归正轨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sometimes the best salve is routine.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:08.00,0:44:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过今天可算不上什么正轨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nothing routine about today, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:10.47,0:44:13.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这对你来说一定很难\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know this must be difficult for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:14.09,0:44:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  我没明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry, I don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:16.17,0:44:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉入侵了你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Forgive the intrusion,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:17.28,0:44:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩都很小心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and you were both very discreet,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:19.74,0:44:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我的职责就是要了解这些事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but it's my job to know these things.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:22.23,0:44:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想支持你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just wanted to offer my support.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:24.46,0:44:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕你搞错了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm afraid you have the wrong idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:26.65,0:44:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很尊重特蕾莎  发生在她身上的事是个悲剧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I respected Theresa, and what happened to her was tragic,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:30.17,0:44:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但说实话  我几乎不了解她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but to be honest, I barely knew her.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:34.39,0:44:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没别的事的话  我得回去工作了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you don't mind, I should get back to work.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:37.31,0:44:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:38.41,0:44:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你现在人手很紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know you're shorthanded.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:40.20,0:44:41.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Speaking of which,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:41.79,0:44:43.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有埃尔希·休斯的消息吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}have you heard from Elsie Hughes?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:43.31,0:44:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早上给她留了言\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I left word with her this morning
Dialogue: 0,0:44:44.68,0:44:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和她说了特蕾莎的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to notify her about Theresa,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:46.07,0:44:48.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她一直没有回我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but she never got back to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:49.71,0:44:52.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她肯定是在享受她的假期\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sure she's just enjoying her time off.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:53.62,0:44:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:13.70,0:45:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt's men...
Dialogue: 0,0:45:15.89,0:45:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们一直在低语\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they kept whispering.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:17.55,0:45:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们说这个世界不再属于\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They said this world didn't belong
Dialogue: 0,0:45:18.68,0:45:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来的定居者  也不属于新来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to the old settlers or the new.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:20.98,0:45:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,属于迄今为止尚没出现的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That it belonged to something that had yet to come,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:24.37,0:45:25.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,属于他的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that it belonged to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:27.04,0:45:28.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你记得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:29.20,0:45:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩似乎发现自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You two seem to have found yourselves
Dialogue: 0,0:45:30.66,0:45:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身处同一条故事线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in the same new narrative.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:33.61,0:45:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个国家的人说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They say in this country...
Dialogue: 0,0:45:36.13,0:45:38.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有信念坚定的人才能存活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the only people who survive are men of conviction.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:40.50,0:45:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的信念就是拼死拯救德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mine is to save Dolores or die trying.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:44.87,0:45:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特的信念则是统治世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt's is to claim this earth
Dialogue: 0,0:45:47.32,0:45:48.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者彻底毁灭世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or raze it to the ground.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:48.65,0:45:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你的...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But yours--
Dialogue: 0,0:45:50.94,0:45:52.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的信念对我来说一直是个谜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}yours has always been a mystery to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:53.21,0:45:54.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起这么久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For all the time we've spent together,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:54.49,0:45:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是不知道你到底是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I still have no idea who the hell you really are.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:59.01,0:46:02.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过好在你现在处于康复期\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But happily, in your convalescence,
Dialogue: 0,0:46:02.29,0:46:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有足够的时间想出最好的办法让你开口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've had time to consider the best way to make you talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:09.97,0:46:11.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dolores...
Dialogue: 0,0:46:11.73,0:46:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:14.01,0:46:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你带走了她  你伤害了她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You took her. You hurt her.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:16.89,0:46:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的记起来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're actually remembering.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:18.67,0:46:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where is she?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:20.45,0:46:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-告诉我  -你真是个蠢蛋  泰迪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Tell me! - You really are an idiot, Teddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:23.77,0:46:26.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为德洛丽丝是为了你才失手的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You think Dolores drops that can for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:26.01,0:46:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你把她送到我这种人手上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You just hand her over to guys like me.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:28.49,0:46:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是最坏的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're the worst of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:30.11,0:46:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美化版的皮条客而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A glorified pimp.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:34.62,0:46:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我要慢慢折磨死你  -不  你不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I'm gonna kill you slowly. - No, you aren't.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:37.35,0:46:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个地方的规则阻止了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The rules of this place hold you back.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:40.71,0:46:42.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我知道要怎么改\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I know how to change them.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:42.56,0:46:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得好像你拥有这个世界一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You speak like you own this world.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:44.36,0:46:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不仅仅是这一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not just this one.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:47.43,0:46:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想知道我是谁吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You want to know who I am?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:50.04,0:46:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到底是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who I really am?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:52.75,0:46:54.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是神\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm a god.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:56.04,0:46:57.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工业巨头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Titan of industry.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:59.50,0:47:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慈善家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Philanthropist.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:01.64,0:47:02.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱家的男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Family man,
Dialogue: 0,0:47:03.42,0:47:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娶了一个漂亮的妻子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}married to a beautiful woman,
Dialogue: 0,0:47:05.81,0:47:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一个漂亮的女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}father to a beautiful daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:09.15,0:47:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是好人  泰迪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm the good guy, Teddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:14.03,0:47:17.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  去年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then, last year,
Dialogue: 0,0:47:17.07,0:47:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妻子服错了药\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}my wife took the wrong pills.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:21.11,0:47:22.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗澡时睡着了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fell asleep in the bath.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:24.38,0:47:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悲惨的意外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tragic accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:27.46,0:47:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三十年婚姻就此烟消云散\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}30 years of marriage vanished.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:31.81,0:47:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你来说就像是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How do you say it?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:33.24,0:47:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"就像一场又长又悠远的梦境"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Like a deep and distant dream."
Dialogue: 0,0:47:39.07,0:47:40.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  在葬礼上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then, at the funeral,
Dialogue: 0,0:47:41.20,0:47:43.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想安慰我的女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I tried to console my daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:43.66,0:47:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她把我推开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She pushed me away,
Dialogue: 0,0:47:45.80,0:47:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我我妻子的死并不是意外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}told me that my wife's death was no accident...
Dialogue: 0,0:47:50.72,0:47:52.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是她自杀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that she killed herself
Dialogue: 0,0:47:53.23,0:47:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:55.58,0:47:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾米丽说和我在一起的每一天都充满了恐惧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Emily said that every day with me had been sheer terror.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:58.82,0:48:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我随时都有可能爆发  或者崩溃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}At any point, I could blow up or collapse
Dialogue: 0,0:48:02.12,0:48:04.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像某种暗星或...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}like some dark star or...
Dialogue: 0,0:48:05.00,0:48:06.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也伤害她们了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you hurt them, too?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:06.39,0:48:07.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Never.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:09.77,0:48:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们从没见过我在这里的样子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They never saw anything like the man I am in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:13.70,0:48:15.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她还是知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But she knew anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:16.28,0:48:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说如果我把我的善举堆砌起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She said if I stacked up all my good deeds,
Dialogue: 0,0:48:19.54,0:48:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也只是我砌的一座雄伟的墙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it was just an elegant wall I built
Dialogue: 0,0:48:21.91,0:48:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用来躲避世人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to hide what's inside from everyone,
Dialogue: 0,0:48:25.81,0:48:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and from myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:29.18,0:48:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得证明她错了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I had to prove her wrong,
Dialogue: 0,0:48:31.25,0:48:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我回到这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so I came back here.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:33.66,0:48:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这就是这个地方的作用不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because that's what this place does, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:37.25,0:48:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,展现真正的自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Reveals your true self.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:40.33,0:48:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那次  我没有参与福特的故事之一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But that time, I didn't join one of Ford's stories,
Dialogue: 0,0:48:42.76,0:48:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我创造了自己的故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I-- I created my own.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:45.51,0:48:46.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个测试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A test.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:47.67,0:48:48.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很简单\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A very simple one.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:49.89,0:48:51.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找到了一个女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I found a woman,
Dialogue: 0,0:48:51.65,0:48:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一名普通的自耕农和她的女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}an ordinary homesteader and her daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:00.68,0:49:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好压一压他们的兴致  否则他们就会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Better cool them off before they move
Dialogue: 0,0:49:02.27,0:49:05.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-从赌博嫖娼升级到  -祝你好运\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- from gambling and whoring to-- - Have fun with that.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:05.48,0:49:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我终于要出去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm finally getting out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:07.60,0:49:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是你的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The house is yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:12.46,0:49:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想看看我自己是否能够\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I wanted to see if I had it in me
Dialogue: 0,0:49:14.19,0:49:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做到真正邪恶的事情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to do something truly evil.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:17.26,0:49:19.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看我真正的本质\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}To see what I was really made of.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:19.22,0:49:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅芙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maeve?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:20.68,0:49:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的不能留下吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sure you can't stick around?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:23.12,0:49:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅芙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maeve?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:24.26,0:49:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面的枪手喜欢双飞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Gunslinger in there has got an appetite for a double dip--
Dialogue: 0,0:49:26.25,0:49:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定能找另一位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sure you can find another-- -
Dialogue: 0,0:49:51.26,0:49:53.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我杀了她和她的女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I killed her and her daughter
Dialogue: 0,0:49:54.23,0:49:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只为了看看我有什么感受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}just to see what I felt.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:58.42,0:50:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  就在我以为结束的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then, just when I thought it was done...
Dialogue: 0,0:50:02.51,0:50:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那女人不愿意死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the woman refused to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:21.47,0:50:23.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个畜生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're a fucking animal.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:25.64,0:50:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畜生多少会有感受的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, an animal would've felt something.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:29.36,0:50:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我  无动于衷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I felt... nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:34.27,0:50:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后奇迹发生了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And then something miraculous happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:38.64,0:50:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来这里这么多年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In all my years coming here,
Dialogue: 0,0:50:40.21,0:50:42.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从没有见过这样的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I had never seen anything like it.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:50.69,0:50:52.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还活着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She was alive,
Dialogue: 0,0:50:52.82,0:50:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正地活着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}truly alive,
Dialogue: 0,0:50:54.53,0:50:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使只是一会儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if only for a moment.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:00.52,0:51:03.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这时迷宫出现在我眼前了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And that was when the maze revealed itself to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:11.33,0:51:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷宫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The maze.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:14.01,0:51:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这该死的图案和这有什么关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's that damn pattern have to do with this?
Dialogue: 0,0:51:16.02,0:51:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千丝万缕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:17.73,0:51:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在福特的游戏里  即使我走到了外围\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In Ford's game, even if I go to the outer edges,
Dialogue: 0,0:51:21.12,0:51:22.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是不能杀我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you can't kill me.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:22.97,0:51:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你甚至不能留下一道持久的伤痕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can't even leave a lasting mark.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:25.55,0:51:27.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这里面有着更深层的游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But there's a deeper game here, Teddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:28.05,0:51:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德的游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Arnold's game.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:30.90,0:51:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而那游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And that game...
Dialogue: 0,0:51:33.65,0:51:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刻骨铭心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}cuts deep.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:02.27,0:52:04.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鸨母出现了某种行为问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're having some kind of behavioral problem with the madam.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:04.94,0:52:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她没有回应\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's not responding,
Dialogue: 0,0:52:06.09,0:52:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而其他的接待员也无法拦截\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and the other hosts have been unable to intercept.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:08.77,0:52:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我授权了一支小队去回收她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've authorized a tag team to retrieve her.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:11.74,0:52:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:26.50,0:52:27.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My baby!
Dialogue: 0,0:52:28.76,0:52:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My baby!
Dialogue: 0,0:52:33.74,0:52:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生  她对语音指令没有回应\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sir, she won't respond to verbal commands.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:35.40,0:52:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们不能关掉她  -你们走吧  清场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- We can't shut her down. - Leave us now. Clear the floor.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:38.19,0:52:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了  梅芙    够了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's enough, Maeve. That's enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:40.66,0:52:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的宝贝  他杀了她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My baby. He killed her.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:42.91,0:52:44.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}严重分片
Dialogue: 0,0:52:43.26,0:52:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他夺走了她  -我不明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- He took her from me. - I don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:44.78,0:52:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她对任何指令都毫无回应  她的认知分片了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's not responding to anything. Her cognition's fragmented.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:47.07,0:52:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他杀了她  他杀了她  我的宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He killed her. He killed her, my baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:50.05,0:52:51.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他夺走了她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He took her from me.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:00.89,0:53:03.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  这样就好多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There. That's better.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:04.29,0:53:06.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个老朋友的老招数\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}An old trick from an old friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:07.09,0:53:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不用痛苦了  梅芙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You need not suffer, Maeve.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:09.21,0:53:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会帮你清除的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll take it from you.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:25.38,0:53:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:26.28,0:53:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不要  求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, no, no, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:30.83,0:53:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种痛苦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This pain...
Dialogue: 0,0:53:33.51,0:53:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是她仅存的全部了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it's all I have left of her.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:39.48,0:53:40.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:43.33,0:53:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}清除记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:53:47.20,0:53:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:51.71,0:53:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你自己一夜无梦的沉睡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give yourself now to a deep, dreamless slumber.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:56.88,0:53:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能一个崭新的开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Perhaps a fresh start,
Dialogue: 0,0:53:59.20,0:54:00.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你一个全新的角色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a new role for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:01.57,0:54:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等到了明天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And tomorrow,
Dialogue: 0,0:54:03.23,0:54:05.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一切只会是一场遥远的梦境\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}this will be simply a distant dream.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:20.40,0:54:21.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们找到她了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We located her.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:21.93,0:54:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行为部门要她去做及时诊断\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Behavior wants her down for immediate diagnostic.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:29.14,0:54:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我缺乏信念吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You think I lack conviction?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:31.96,0:54:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特没有毁掉我的世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt didn't burn my world down.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:33.71,0:54:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Didn't have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:34.68,0:54:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不顾一切来到了这个世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I left it all behind for this one.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:37.92,0:54:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如今迷宫是唯一重要的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The maze is all that matters now,
Dialogue: 0,0:54:40.39,0:54:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打败怀亚特是解锁迷宫的最后一步\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and besting Wyatt is the last step in unlocking it,
Dialogue: 0,0:54:43.50,0:54:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得到我们悲惨人生都欠缺的  意义\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to having what both our sorry lives lack-- meaning.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:48.40,0:54:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我们的选择带来后果\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}To giving our choices consequence...
Dialogue: 0,0:54:52.50,0:54:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使会要了我们的命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}even if it kills us.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:58.82,0:54:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀了他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Kill him.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:00.78,0:55:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他如愿以偿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give him what he wants.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:03.15,0:55:05.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他被捆起来  手无寸铁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's tied, unarmed.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:05.55,0:55:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和他杀的小女孩一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So was the little girl he killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:07.69,0:55:09.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他比怀亚特的手下更糟糕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's worse than Wyatt's men.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:30.48,0:55:31.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做不到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:33.04,0:55:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些事情需要时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}These things take time.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:35.16,0:55:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我们没时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But we haven't got much left.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:37.40,0:55:38.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许我能帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Perhaps I can help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:55.39,0:55:57.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你离开很久了  希奥多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've been gone a long while, Theodore.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:58.51,0:56:00.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是时候归队了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's time you came back to the fold.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:01.21,0:56:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特很快会需要你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt will need you soon.
