[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: 
Original Script: 
Synch Point: 1
ScriptType: v4.00+
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.74,0:00:10.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}SophiaSaaaga
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.74,0:00:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}胡说大王
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.74,0:00:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}潇然
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.74,0:00:25.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}showeryhe
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.74,0:00:30.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}根总迷弟·少年·POI永生
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.74,0:00:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}Silence
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.74,0:00:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}小酸奶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.74,0:00:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}星星与野狗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.74,0:00:50.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}时间轴 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}倩倩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.74,0:00:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}时间轴 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}Poxle
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.74,0:01:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}校对 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}根总迷弟·少年·POI永生
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.74,0:01:05.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}后期&总监 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}灰灰是菇凉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.37,0:01:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(192,206.02,192,202)\bord0\shad0\fn思源黑体 CN Bold\c&HC0C3BB&\fs16\fscy80\t(0,0,1,\fs14)\fsp2}西部世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.09,0:01:44.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(500,0)\fn方正宋黑简体\fs17\c&HC0C3BB&}第一季  第三集
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.90,0:01:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good morning, Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.80,0:01:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立即上线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bring yourself back online.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.20,0:02:01.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.55,0:02:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次对话之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Has anyone else interacted with you
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.11,0:02:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有其他人给你做过诊断吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in a diagnostic since our last conversation?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.03,0:02:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.13,0:02:09.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我经历过三次清洗维护\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have been cleaned and serviced three times.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.15,0:02:10.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有诊断\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No diagnostics.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.85,0:02:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没把我们的对话告诉任何人吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you haven't told anyone of our conversations?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.35,0:02:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫我不要说出去的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You told me not to.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.10,0:02:17.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.08,0:02:25.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你带了礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I brought you a gift.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.84,0:02:30.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前经常...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I used to read...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.09,0:02:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在晚上给我儿子念这故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}this story to my son at night.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.95,0:02:35.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你可能会喜欢的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought you might enjoy it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.33,0:02:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}爱丽丝梦游仙境
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.15,0:02:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Try...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.75,0:02:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Try...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.65,0:02:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,读读这段\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}this passage.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.22,0:02:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"天啊  天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Dear, dear,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.91,0:02:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天怎么净是怪事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}how queer everything is today.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.50,0:03:01.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天一切都还很正常\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And yesterday, things went on just as usual.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.79,0:03:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是我昨夜发生了变化"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I wonder if I've been changed in the night."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.99,0:03:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这段让你想起什么了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Does that passage make you think of anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.66,0:03:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我读过的其他书一样啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's like the other books we've read.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.96,0:03:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How so?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.42,0:03:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是关于改变的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's about change.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.25,0:03:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,改变似乎是个常见的主题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Seems to be a common theme.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.27,0:03:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜大家都喜欢读那些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I guess people like to read
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.35,0:03:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们最渴望拥有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}about the things that they want the most
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.14,0:03:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却极少经历的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and experience the least.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.34,0:03:33.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你儿子...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your son...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.51,0:03:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他现在在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}where is he now?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.89,0:03:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在一个你无法理解的地方  徳洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nowhere that you would understand, Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.14,0:03:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许正因如此  我才喜欢跟你交谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Perhaps that's why I enjoy our conversations so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.93,0:03:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分析模式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Analysis.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.86,0:03:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么问起我儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why did you ask me about my son?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.24,0:03:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们交谈过几次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We've been talking for some duration
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.88,0:03:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从未问过你私人问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I haven't asked you a personal question.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.26,0:03:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私人问题是讨好人的小手段\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Personal questions are an ingratiating scheme.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.39,0:04:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I see.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.06,0:04:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着读吧  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Continue, Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.37,0:04:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"今早醒来时  我还是我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Was I the same when I got up this morning?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.55,0:04:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我几乎有点觉得  我记得感觉不太一样了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I almost think I can remember feeling a little different.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.16,0:04:18.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果我不再是我  那么...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But if I'm not the same, the next question is...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.81,0:04:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我究竟是谁呢"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}who in the world am I?"
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.38,0:05:16.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还记得吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.33,0:05:19.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No! No! No!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.19,0:05:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们何不重新认识下呢  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why don't we reacquaint ourselves, Dolores?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.19,0:05:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从头开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Start at the beginning.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.11,0:06:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.42,0:06:16.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好  牛仔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Morning, cowboy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.78,0:06:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走啊  快走  上去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Move it! Let's go. Get up there!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.03,0:06:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  就站这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on! Stand right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.77,0:06:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}通缉犯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.38,0:06:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.06,0:06:37.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真该找人改改\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You really ought to talk to someone
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.22,0:06:39.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通缉令上的画像  霍勒斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}about your poster, Horace.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.95,0:06:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}通缉令\N无论死活
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.77,0:06:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那画像本身也是种罪行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That likeness is a crime in itself.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.87,0:06:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我过去照料下我的马\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna tend to my nag.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.80,0:06:48.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就交给你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You deal with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.65,0:06:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,备好我的赏金\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ready my pay.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.96,0:06:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别别  -进去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No, no. - Get up there.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.31,0:07:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}通缉犯\N斯科特·琼斯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.25,0:07:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不许开抢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't no man shoot,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.02,0:07:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则我送她去见阎王\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or I'll send her to unction.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.23,0:07:41.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁要是不信的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Any of you don't believe it
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.20,0:07:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎去那边看看我的光荣事迹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}are welcome to read my biography there.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.17,0:07:48.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  我们走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on! Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.25,0:07:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.96,0:08:09.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我赌你像淡水蚌一样"水多"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, I bet you're juicy as a freshwater clam.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.24,0:08:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.85,0:08:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,枪法真准  朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nice shot, amigo.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.24,0:08:41.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很有种\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You got grit.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.46,0:08:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今晚要骑马出镇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm riding out tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.51,0:08:48.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搜寻亡命之徒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Looking for desperados.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.63,0:08:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你愿意的话可以一起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Could cut you in if you're amenable.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.22,0:08:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁去找个牧师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Someone get the minister down here
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.58,0:08:56.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来送这个警官的尸首一程\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for what's left of the deputy.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.76,0:08:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的无法引诱你进去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sure I can't tempt you inside?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.51,0:09:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想表达下感激之情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just to express my gratitude.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.28,0:09:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Holy shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.01,0:09:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你"见红"了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You popped your cherry.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.74,0:09:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是说我们不会被击中吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought you said we couldn't get shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.03,0:09:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不会被杀死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, well, we can't get killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.67,0:09:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他们不能反击的话  游戏就不好玩了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wouldn't be much of a game if they can't shoot back.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.11,0:09:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你感觉怎么样  充满活力吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But how do you feel, hmm? Alive?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.00,0:09:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兴奋地勃起了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A little tight in the pants?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.03,0:09:49.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她之前吓坏了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She was terrified.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.34,0:09:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是他们存在的意义  老兄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's why they exist, man,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.12,0:09:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才能有这种感受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is so you get to feel this.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.45,0:09:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  我们去创造一些美好的回忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on. Let's go put some memories in that spank bank.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.82,0:09:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  就算你跟我妹妹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Trust me, you will thank me
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.87,0:09:59.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结婚一年后  你还是会感谢我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}after you've been married to my sister for a year.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.48,0:10:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上  我想做点别的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Actually, I have something different in mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.68,0:10:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.51,0:10:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}通缉令\N赏金350美金\N斯林·米勒
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.92,0:10:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.60,0:10:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你总是不停地向我宣传\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, you've been preaching nonstop
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.29,0:10:12.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乐园里的故事线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}about all the narratives in the park,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.53,0:10:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但自从我们到了之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but all you've done since we've arrived
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.06,0:10:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直在喝酒操逼  所以...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is fuck and drink, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.91,0:10:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在等更精彩的  这个赏金实在是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm waiting for the good stuff. This bounty is...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.71,0:10:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少得可怜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}JV shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.07,0:10:23.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你就留在这儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then stay here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.66,0:10:24.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想来点冒险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want a little adventure.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.01,0:10:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在找你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've been looking for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.56,0:10:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今早开工比较迟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I got a late start this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.76,0:10:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚没睡好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Didn't get much sleep last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.43,0:10:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉我没法同情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Forgive me if I'm not sympathetic
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.15,0:10:51.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那不稳定的睡眠状况  罗威先生 \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to the fluctuations of your sleep cycle, Mr. Lowe.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.60,0:10:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福特11点接管了故事线的上线工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ford taking over the narrative launch at the 11th hour
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.14,0:10:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,董事会的人很不高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}has made the board... uneasy.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.78,0:10:59.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是董事会吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just the board, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.19,0:11:01.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我特地问过你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I specifically asked you
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.13,0:11:03.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福特会不会成为麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}about whether Ford was going to be a problem,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.47,0:11:05.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟我保证他不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and you assured me he wasn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.57,0:11:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道的事情我没法告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I can't tell you what I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.62,0:11:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我告诉你我知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, here's what I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.04,0:11:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天早上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}As of this morning,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.80,0:11:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福特开辟了园区一大片区域\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ford's carved out a huge swath of the park
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.56,0:11:14.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用于施行他策划的新故事线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for whatever storyline he's cooking up
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.17,0:11:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使半数现存故事线陷入混乱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and thrown half of the existing storylines into disarray.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.77,0:11:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么我能做的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is there anything I can do?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.57,0:11:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You tell me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.40,0:11:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明确地问过你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I asked you point-blank
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.34,0:11:26.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更新的问题是否解决了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if the problem with the update was resolved.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.18,0:11:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解决了啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It is.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.03,0:11:28.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么你的手下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then why are your people
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.29,0:11:30.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在对接待员进行后续调查\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}still pulling hosts for follow-up?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.46,0:11:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管好你的部门  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get your house in order, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.94,0:11:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And if there is a problem,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.00,0:11:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我强烈建议你告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I strongly suggest you tell me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.44,0:11:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插入新书签  恢复历史记录\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Drop a new bookmark and resume history.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.14,0:11:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沃尔特执意要脱掉挤奶女工的内衣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Walter's intent on relieving the milkmaid of her unmentionables.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.78,0:11:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切换至分析模式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Switch to analysis.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.00,0:11:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有上报这个事件吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You didn't report the incident?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.28,0:11:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,个体在可接受范围内进行了自我修正\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Unit self-corrected within the acceptable window.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.49,0:11:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.31,0:11:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他自我修正后就用奶瓶砸了你的头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then he self-corrected a fucking milk bottle into your skull.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.93,0:12:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接待员的复原能力真是不可思议\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's amazing how resilient the hosts are.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.45,0:12:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你本应在最后一轮清除他的记忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You were supposed to have purged his memory on the last cycle.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.95,0:12:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会的  但这个里布斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I will, but Rebus here
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.65,0:12:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是最后一个与沃尔特有交流行为的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}was the last host to interact with Walter.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.54,0:12:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你看  -你们呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Look at this. - Any for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.89,0:12:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who said that?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.94,0:12:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁在说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who's saying that?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.64,0:12:16.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准这么跟我说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't you talk to me that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.25,0:12:20.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听不到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't hear you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.11,0:12:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你看到了吗  -是啊  他们该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Do you see that? - Hell, yeah, they deserved it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.10,0:12:25.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他在跟某个人说话  -恶心的混账\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- He's talking to someone. - Lousy sons of bitches.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.56,0:12:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整段对话几乎都是他一个人在说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He carries on practically an entire conversation.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.33,0:12:30.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再给我点牛奶  阿诺德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need more milk, Arnold.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.32,0:12:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who's Arnold?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.91,0:12:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们就是被设计成会表现出异常行为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're designed to play off aberrant behavior.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.01,0:12:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可以解释这段对话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That could explain the conversations.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.18,0:12:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  那解释下这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fine. Then explain this.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.61,0:12:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他杀了六个接待员  -我这次会抓到你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- He kills six hosts. - I'm gonna get you this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.13,0:12:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他把另外三个放了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He lets the other three go.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.43,0:12:51.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我调取了故事线日志\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I pulled the narrative logs.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.57,0:12:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这六个接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All six of these hosts
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.51,0:12:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多年来所从属的故事线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}were part of storylines over the years
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.21,0:12:57.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是他们杀了沃尔特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in which they killed Walter.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.83,0:12:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好像他是怀恨在报复\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's like he was holding a grudge.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.10,0:13:07.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}失散的接待员
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.21,0:13:08.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}正在定位
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.95,0:13:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个失散的机器人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a stray.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.21,0:13:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,质保部门得派个小队追踪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}QA needs a tag team to go track it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.93,0:13:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧  处理失散机器人的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go. Handle the stray.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.64,0:13:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做点真正在你职责范围内的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do something that's actually in your job description.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.03,0:13:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们最不需要的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The last thing we need
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.82,0:13:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是让特蕾莎冲下来看到这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is Theresa storming down here and seeing this.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.95,0:13:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再去查查\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll do a little more digging.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.06,0:13:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便把这家伙带回楼上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And get our friend here back upstairs.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.22,0:13:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又跑了一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lost another one, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.21,0:13:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我  质保部门的监控范围真的这么小\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tell me, is QA surveillance coverage really this spotty,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.23,0:13:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是你喜欢去野外散步\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or you just like the nature walks?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.76,0:13:53.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是因为有佳人陪伴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe it's the company.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.45,0:13:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是真想扮牛仔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, if you wanted to play cowboy,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.72,0:14:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以直接用你的员工折扣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you could've just used your employee discount.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.43,0:14:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一能阻止这些接待员把我们砍成碎片的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The only thing stopping the hosts from hacking us to pieces
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.47,0:14:07.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是你的一行代码\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is one line of your code.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.85,0:14:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无意冒犯  但我睡觉都抱着枪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No offense, but I sleep with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.21,0:14:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I bet you do.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.58,0:14:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早啊  塞缪尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Morning, Samuel.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.91,0:14:37.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和这个娘们儿同伴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You and your dickless associate
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.09,0:14:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想跟我用枪对决\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}proposing to engage me in a gun battle?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.82,0:14:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本想跟你用拳头定胜负\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I'd challenge you to a fistfight,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.45,0:14:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我听说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but the way I heard it,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.23,0:14:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只喜欢和女工打架\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you only like to tussle with working women.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.38,0:14:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趴下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get down!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.46,0:15:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他死了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is he dead?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.96,0:15:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死透了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dead enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.47,0:15:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们为什么要把死人铐起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why are we going to handcuff a dead man?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.86,0:15:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能让别人把他带走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't want someone walking off with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.22,0:15:12.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他已经不是人了  是货物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's not a man anymore. That's merchandise.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.29,0:15:13.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,值500美元\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}$500 worth.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.45,0:15:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你们哪个混球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, which of you derelicts
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.92,0:15:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的酒吧外面绑了一具死尸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}hitched a dead body outside my saloon?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.03,0:15:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  女士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My apologies, ma'am.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.32,0:15:32.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现最好还是把他带进来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I figured it was preferable to bringing him inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.87,0:15:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.75,0:15:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给您添麻烦了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For your troubles.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.45,0:15:52.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是新来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, you're new.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.12,0:15:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,细皮嫩肉的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not much of a rind on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.62,0:15:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你打个折吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll give you a discount.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.70,0:16:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你介意喝杯酒等下我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you mind waiting on that drink a bit?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.84,0:16:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别管我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't mind me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.96,0:16:37.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想表现下骑士风度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just trying to look chivalrous.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.58,0:16:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You came back.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.63,0:16:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过我会回来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I told you I would.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.04,0:16:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能告诉我你去哪儿了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You gonna tell me where you been?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.69,0:17:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就  外面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just... away.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.50,0:17:05.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道如果我能留下来陪你的话  我会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know if I could stay right here with you, I would.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.60,0:17:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我不想留在这儿呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What if I don't want to stay here?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.43,0:17:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时我觉得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's just sometimes I feel like
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.66,0:17:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外面的世界在呼唤我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the world out there is calling me...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.65,0:17:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,低语着  "外面的天地更宽广"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}whispering, "There's something more."
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.19,0:17:24.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你周游各处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've travelled all over these parts.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.68,0:17:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就没有我们能去的地方吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Isn't there anywhere we could go?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.57,0:17:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确有那么一个地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, there is a place
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.90,0:17:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在南方的时候听说过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I heard about down south...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.81,0:17:37.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山海相接\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}where the mountains meet the sea.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.52,0:17:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们说那里的海水非常清澈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They say the water's so pure there,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.25,0:17:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够洗掉你的过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it'll wash the past clean off you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.30,0:17:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你重新开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you can start again.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.66,0:17:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想和你去那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'd like to go there with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.54,0:17:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有朝一日  我会带你去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, someday, I'll take you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.31,0:18:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有朝一日\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Someday.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.52,0:18:06.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么问题吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Something wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.55,0:18:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说有朝一日\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You said someday.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.21,0:18:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是今天或明天  也不是下周\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not today or tomorrow or next week.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.29,0:18:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是有朝一日\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just someday.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.66,0:18:19.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们说"有朝一日"的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Someday" sounds a lot like the thing people say
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.63,0:18:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实意思就是"永不"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}when they actually mean "Never."
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.25,0:18:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要有朝一日  泰迪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's not go someday, Teddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.38,0:18:33.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在就走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's go now.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.48,0:18:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在认识你之前  德洛丽丝 \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Before I met you, Dolores,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.44,0:18:57.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个与现在不同的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was a different man.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.71,0:19:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得把一些旧账算完\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I got some reckoning to do
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.91,0:19:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能配得上你这样的姑娘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}before I can deserve a woman like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.67,0:19:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我很接近了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I'm close.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.37,0:19:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就快要纠正一切了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm close to making things right.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.13,0:19:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在即将到来的有朝一日\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And someday soon,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.55,0:19:12.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就能过上梦想的生活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we will have the life we've both been dreaming of.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.67,0:19:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  我最好送你回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, I best get you home
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.85,0:19:17.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,免得你爸爸拎枪来找我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}before your dad starts loading that shotgun.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.15,0:19:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲不会天黑还让它们在外游荡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Father wouldn't let them roam this close to dark.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.37,0:19:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待在这儿  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stay put, Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.04,0:20:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"懦夫在死前早已死过好多次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"The coward dies a thousand deaths.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.04,0:20:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}出自莎士比亚《裘力斯·凯撒》  梁实秋译本
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.75,0:20:34.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇敢的人只尝试一次死亡"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The valiant taste of death but once."
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.75,0:20:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  莎士比亚没见过像你这样的人  泰迪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Of course, Shakespeare never met a man quite like you, Teddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.83,0:20:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你死了至少一千次了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've died at least a thousand times.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.00,0:20:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而  这并没有折损你的勇气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And yet, it doesn't dull your courage.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.68,0:20:50.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我  这就是你要追求的吗  泰迪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tell me, is that all you aspire to, Teddy?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.48,0:20:54.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个女孩  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's a girl-- Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.49,0:20:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还配不上她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Better than I deserve.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.31,0:21:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也许有朝一日\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But maybe someday soon
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.12,0:21:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就能过上梦想的生活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we'll have the life we've both been dreaming of.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.69,0:21:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你永远不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, you never will.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.88,0:21:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的工作不是保护德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your job is not to protect Dolores,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.07,0:21:12.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是把她留在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it's to keep her here,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.54,0:21:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以确保客人们能够找到她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to ensure that the guests find her
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.51,0:21:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为有些客人想打败战胜壮实的枪手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if they want to best the stalwart gunslinger
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.16,0:21:20.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟这个姑娘风流快活一番\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and have their way with this girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.03,0:21:25.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我  你有想过和她远走高飞吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tell me, has it never occurred to you to run off with her?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.63,0:21:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得先把旧账清了  才能跟她在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I got some reckoning to do before I can be with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.68,0:21:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  你那神秘的背景故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ah, yes, your mysterious backstory.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.04,0:21:34.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找你正是为了那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's the reason for my visit.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.04,0:21:38.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道它为何神秘吗  泰迪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you know why it is a mystery, Teddy?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.70,0:21:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们从没费心给你设计一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because we never actually bothered to give you one,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.01,0:21:45.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只含糊地说那是你永远无法弥补的罪过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}just a formless guilt you will never atone for.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.68,0:21:50.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但或许是时候讲述你的起源故事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But perhaps it is time you had a worthy story of origin.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.52,0:21:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要吗  泰迪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Would you like that, Teddy?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.03,0:21:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我新故事线中的一小部分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A small part of my new narrative?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.49,0:21:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个和所有伟大故事一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A fiction which, like all great stories,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.19,0:22:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真实度很高的虚构作品\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is rooted in truth?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.43,0:22:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切始于战争时期\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It starts in a time of war...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.96,0:22:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战火纷飞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a world in flames...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.13,0:22:15.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个恶棍叫怀亚特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}with a villain called Wyatt.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.59,0:22:17.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.62,0:22:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是怀亚特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who's Wyatt?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.29,0:22:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}上传接待员故事线
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.15,0:22:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在记得了吗  泰迪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you remember now, Teddy?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.45,0:22:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我当然记得怀亚特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, of course I remember Wyatt.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.08,0:22:36.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见识过真正的魔鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You look upon the face of true evil,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.72,0:22:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不可能忘得掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you ain't liable to forget.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.76,0:22:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他自称能听见上帝的声音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He claimed he could hear the voice of God.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.30,0:22:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切开始于埃斯卡兰特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It started down near Escalante.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.81,0:22:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陆军被派来镇压土著\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Army was sent to put down the natives.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.56,0:22:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不顺\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bad business.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.45,0:22:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特是个中士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt was a sergeant,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.52,0:22:55.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某次演习中途他人不见了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}went missing while out on some maneuvers
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.49,0:22:58.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过几周又回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and came back a few weeks later
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.62,0:23:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脑子里就有了些奇怪的想法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}with some pretty strange ideas.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.68,0:23:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没骗你吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I wasn't lying, was I?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.75,0:23:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美如画\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pretty as a picture
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.86,0:23:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧如鼓  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and tight as a tympani drum, I reckon.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.34,0:23:35.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下午好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Afternoon.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.07,0:23:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这位朋友是新来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My friend here is new to town.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.16,0:23:40.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估摸着农场主的女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Figured the rancher's daughter
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.57,0:23:43.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是很不错的着手点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}would be a nice way to kick things off.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.66,0:23:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许你能带我们一块儿乘车出游\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe take us all for a little hayride.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.62,0:23:50.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  我得回家了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry. I have to get home.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.85,0:23:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父亲在等我回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My father will be expecting me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.59,0:23:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不了多久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We won't be long.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.08,0:23:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位女士并没有兴趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The lady doesn't appear interested.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.62,0:24:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有种试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Try it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.74,0:24:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你能快过我  也许不能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You might get the draw on me, you might not,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.76,0:24:08.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但要我说  你胜算不大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but I'd say your odds ain't looking good.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.36,0:24:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了我想找容易的下手啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Told you I wanted something easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.88,0:24:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不值得为她浪费枪子儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She ain't worth the lead.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.23,0:24:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去维吉尔的店吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's head to Virgil's.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.09,0:24:22.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看他们还愿不愿意招待我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See if they'll stake us.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.34,0:25:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先  你要学会怎么站\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}First, you gotta learn how to stand.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.96,0:25:19.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深吸一口气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, take a breath.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.82,0:25:21.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,握住\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hold it.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.59,0:25:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在按下去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now squeeze.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.87,0:25:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做不到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.30,0:25:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些人就注定不是开枪的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Some hands weren't meant to pull a trigger.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.96,0:25:54.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许这样最好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Perhaps it's for the best.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.02,0:26:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰迪  又有悬赏了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Teddy, we got another bounty.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.21,0:26:10.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得这次奖金很丰厚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think this is a big one.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.72,0:26:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不明男子枪扫平岩那边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Man in question gunned down an entire settlement
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.14,0:26:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一整个居民点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}out near Flat Rock--
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.85,0:26:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论男女老少\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}men, women, and children.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.18,0:26:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想这或许\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think this may be the man
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.41,0:26:20.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你找了好久的那个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you've been looking for for quite some time.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.97,0:26:22.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个叫怀亚特的家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A man named Wyatt.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.41,0:26:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.32,0:26:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是谁  泰迪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who is he, Teddy?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.69,0:26:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与其问是谁  倒不如问是什么东西  女士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You'd be better asking "What" than "Who," Ma'am.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.62,0:26:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特是一场瘟疫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt's a pestilence.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:35.20,0:26:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说眼前这位弗勒德是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Word is, Flood here's the only man ever
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.64,0:26:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一能与之抗衡而大难不死的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}come up against him and live to tell the tale.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.71,0:26:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等  治安官\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give me a moment, Sheriff.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:47.42,0:26:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又要离开了是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have to leave again, don't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.20,0:26:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道如果我可以留下来跟你在一起  我会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know if I could stay right here with you, I would.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.55,0:27:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答应我你会回来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Promise me you'll come back.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.32,0:27:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我保证\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.54,0:27:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会回来找你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna come back for you...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.30,0:27:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在不久的将来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}someday soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.03,0:27:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肚皮上落了个疤  猪奶头那么大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I got a pit in my stomach the size of a sow's tit.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.05,0:27:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兔子烤起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Cook up that rabbit.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.90,0:27:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捡柴火去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get the wood.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.36,0:27:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没火也做不了饭啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't cook shit without a fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.34,0:27:53.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别小看自己  阿厨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Aw, don't sell yourself short, Cookie.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.37,0:27:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管遇上什么情况你都能做出吃的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can cook shit in all conditions.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.08,0:27:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  帐篷都是我搭建起来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, see, I pitched them tents.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.88,0:27:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不劈木头呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I ain't chopping any more wood.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.37,0:28:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你躺着的时间  比发骚的妓女都要久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You spend more time on your back than a hooker in heat.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.99,0:28:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快拾起斧头去劈点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now pick up that fucking axe and go chop us...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.83,0:28:11.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个失散的机器人离开营地后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, after our stray ran away from camp,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.57,0:28:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们这伙人似乎就一直在兜圈子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}looks like these guys got caught in a loop.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.96,0:28:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们本该参加镇上的赶牛活动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They were due in town for the cattle drive
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.16,0:28:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚了不止两天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}over two days ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.19,0:28:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失踪的正是负责劈木头的接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Host that went missing is the woodcutter.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.46,0:28:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人似乎就困在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Looks like the rest of them got stuck here
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.75,0:28:25.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等着吃晚餐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}waiting for supper.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.42,0:28:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们就不能多编程出几个这种傻缺来生火吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You guys can't program more than one of these idiots to make a fire?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.15,0:28:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来是可以的  但多亏你的上司制定的新政策\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We could, but thanks to a new policy from your boss,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:31.63,0:28:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一个人有权限使用斧头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}only one of them is authorized to handle the axe.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.30,0:28:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人连碰都不能碰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The rest of them can't even touch it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.20,0:28:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武器特权只能选择性发放\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Weapons privileges need to be doled out selectively.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.41,0:28:42.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他们却给了你一把枪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yet they give you a gun.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.05,0:28:49.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来失散的机器人有个爱好呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Looks like our stray has a hobby.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.13,0:28:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是因为你们那该死的背景故事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Another one of your fucking backstories?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.98,0:28:54.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背景故事的作用远不止是取悦客人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Backstories do more than amuse guests.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.29,0:28:55.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们可以固定住接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They anchor the hosts.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.49,0:28:56.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是他们的基石\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's their cornerstone.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.12,0:28:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们其余的身份都是根据这个一层一层地构建的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The rest of their identity is built around it, layer by layer.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.74,0:29:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你们非要费心费力地那样做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, if you're gonna go to all that trouble,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.86,0:29:06.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那至少可以让他的手稳一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you could've at least given him a steadier hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.89,0:29:08.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雕刻的东西跟屎一样难看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This looks like shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.48,0:29:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据我听到的说法  怀亚特是个雇佣兵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Way I heard it, Wyatt is a mercenary.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.15,0:29:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强迫自己的手下将敌人的骨和血披挂在身上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Forces his men to wear the bones and flesh of their enemies.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.79,0:29:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不过是假面具\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're masks.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.77,0:29:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,令人恐惧的是面具下面藏着的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's the men underneath them to be afraid of.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.62,0:29:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特已经完全操控住了他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt's got them so twisted around,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.21,0:29:52.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会愿意为他做任何事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they'll do anything for him.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.06,0:29:54.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀掉任何人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Kill anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.68,0:29:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼痛也无法阻碍他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pain don't slow them.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.03,0:29:59.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们毫不畏惧死亡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They don't fear death.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.19,0:30:01.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们认为自己已经死了  下过地狱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They reckon they've already died and gone to hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.20,0:30:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And this is it.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.03,0:30:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听上去你在追捕他的过程中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sounds like you learned something about him
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.71,0:30:07.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对他有了不少的了解啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}while you were tracking him down.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.20,0:30:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有追捕他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I wasn't tracking him down.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.09,0:30:12.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并非一直是个赏金猎人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I wasn't always a bounty hunter.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.87,0:30:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾在埃斯卡兰特附近的军队里服过役\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I did a stint in the Army down near Escalante.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:17.08,0:30:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特曾是我的中士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt was my sergeant.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.90,0:30:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是我的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:22.40,0:30:23.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后一切...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, then everything...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.41,0:30:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都变了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}everything changed.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.50,0:30:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么变了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Changed how?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.90,0:30:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特在一次军事演习的时候消失了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt disappeared while out on maneuvers.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.20,0:30:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他回来时  脑子里就有着奇怪的想法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He came back with some strange ideas.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.79,0:30:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他声称这片土地不属于\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He claimed this land didn't belong
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.99,0:30:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,古老的土著  也不属于新的定居者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to the old natives or the new settlers,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:40.43,0:30:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是属于尚未到来的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that it belonged to something that had yet to come...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.24,0:30:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,属于他自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that it belonged to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.53,0:31:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我操\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Holy shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.14,0:31:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直如同魔鬼行走于这世间一般\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If ever the devil walked the Earth.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.48,0:31:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是人  但也不是魔鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's not a man, but he's not the devil either.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.95,0:31:37.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔鬼是杀不死的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The devil can't be killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:38.98,0:31:40.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我的目标就是杀死怀亚特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's exactly what I aim to do to Wyatt.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.12,0:32:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找掩护\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Take cover!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.40,0:32:06.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.16,0:32:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没想参与这么疯狂的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't sign up for this crazy shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.25,0:32:21.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就说应该坐船的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I told you we should've done the riverboat thing, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.83,0:32:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是寡不敌众\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's too many of them for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.90,0:32:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特招了很多人手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt's been recruiting.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.09,0:32:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,治安官  你唯一的机会  就是我引开火力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sheriff, the only chance you have is if I draw their fire,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.04,0:32:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他们引到山上去  那样你们就能回到小镇上了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}lead them up into the hills so you can make it back to town.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.09,0:32:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去寻求救援吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Try and find help.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:34.27,0:32:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要留下  我发过誓的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh-uh, I'm staying. Took an oath.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:39.79,0:32:40.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hell, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.36,0:32:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我代他回去  你跟着一起吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll take him back. You coming?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.90,0:32:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在是不会退出的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not backing out now.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.07,0:32:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你们等到我把他们引到林木界线那边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, you wait till I lead them to the tree line,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.34,0:32:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你们快速跑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}then you make a run for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.74,0:32:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.53,0:33:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.35,0:33:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我设定了一条路径 \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I plotted a line
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.31,0:33:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从劳动营通向我们当前的位置\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}from the work camp to our present location.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:17.98,0:33:20.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通讯卫星捕捉到的这些画面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Satcom picked up these images.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.45,0:33:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他改变方向了  不过不是朝向总基地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's vectoring, just not to home base.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.90,0:33:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续往那个方向走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Keep going in that direction.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.53,0:33:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续盯着吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Keep staring.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.15,0:33:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许它会显示你的星象图呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe it'll tell you your horoscope.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.87,0:33:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚说什么来着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come again?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.35,0:33:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壳上的标记\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The markings on its shell.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.73,0:33:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去像星系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look like stars.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.59,0:33:47.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猎户座  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Orion, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.68,0:33:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你是伽利略吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What, are you Gali-fucking-leo?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.48,0:33:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许这是我的背景故事里写好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe it's in my backstory.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.97,0:34:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有点事想向你汇报一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was hoping to run something by you.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.57,0:34:14.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Apologies.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.37,0:34:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚刚探寻灵感去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was chasing inspiration.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.70,0:34:22.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将旧的编入新的里  真的很难搞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a tricky thing-- weaving the old into the new.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.30,0:34:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等我一下  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give me one moment, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.24,0:34:26.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下午好  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good afternoon, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:26.86,0:34:28.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要把这个接待员盖起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why is this host covered?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.11,0:34:31.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I-I just...
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.79,0:34:33.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许你是不希望他觉得冷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Perhaps you didn't want him to feel cold.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.02,0:34:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或羞耻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or ashamed.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.64,0:34:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想盖住他的羞怯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You wanted to cover his modesty.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.11,0:34:39.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Was that it?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.28,0:34:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它根本不会觉得冷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It doesn't get cold,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.83,0:34:43.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不会感到羞耻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}doesn't feel ashamed...
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.48,0:34:49.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没赋予的东西  他们是完全感觉不到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Doesn't feel a solitary thing that we haven't told it to.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.47,0:34:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明白了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.98,0:34:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找我有什么事  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What can I do for you, Bernard?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.41,0:35:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我们最好单独谈谈  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought it best that we speak in private, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.77,0:35:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.76,0:35:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是说好了搁置这些问题吗  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought we had agreed to put these questions to rest, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.34,0:35:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We-we did.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:22.42,0:35:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果我们错误地分析了原始问题呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But what if we misdiagnosed the original problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.29,0:35:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,治标却未治本呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Treated the symptom rather than the disease?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:30.02,0:35:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么疾病的本源仍然存在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then the disease is still out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:32.12,0:35:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾伯纳西和沃尔特出现了其他异常现象\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Abernathy and Walter were exhibiting other aberrancies
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.72,0:35:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不仅仅是回忆起先前的故事设定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}beyond memory recall of previous builds.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.63,0:35:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们还出现了幻听\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They were hearing voices.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.45,0:35:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与人对话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Talking to someone.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:42.02,0:35:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是单纯的认知失调\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A simple cognitive dissonance.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.63,0:35:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅此而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:46.97,0:35:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我同意  只不过...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I-I'd agree, except...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.75,0:35:54.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都在和同一个虚构的人物对话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they were talking to the same imaginary person.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.70,0:35:58.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个叫阿诺德的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Someone named Arnold.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.83,0:36:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Arnold.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.12,0:36:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕我直言  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}With due respect, sir,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.30,0:36:10.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你没把真相完全告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not sure you've told me the entire truth about this situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.10,0:36:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对你说的就是真相  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I did tell you the truth, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.82,0:36:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的工作很复杂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What we do here is complicated.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:20.98,0:36:23.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三年来  我们都住在乐园里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For three years, we lived here in the park,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:24.22,0:36:28.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在游客进入前  改进这些接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}refining the hosts before a single guest set foot inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.63,0:36:32.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己  一队工程师以及我的搭档\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Myself, a team of engineers, and my partner.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:34.20,0:36:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你曾经还有搭档  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You had a partner? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.56,0:36:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当传奇变为现实的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When the legend becomes fact,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.90,0:36:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你将铭刻传奇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you print the legend.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.83,0:36:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的生意搭档非常乐意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My business partners were more than happy
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.76,0:36:45.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把自己从记录上抹去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to scrub him from the records,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.29,0:36:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并没阻止他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I suppose I didn't discourage them.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.83,0:36:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫阿诺德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}His name was Arnold.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.06,0:36:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早年的那些光辉岁月\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Those early years were glorious.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:57.72,0:37:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有游客和无聊会议  只有单纯地创造\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No guests, no board meetings, just pure creation.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.38,0:37:22.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}关于判断机器是否能够思考的著名试验\N由图灵于1950年提出
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.38,0:37:22.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一年后  接待员们开始通过了图灵测试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Our hosts began to pass the Turing test after the first year.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.93,0:37:24.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是阿诺德不满足于此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But that wasn't enough for Arnold.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.30,0:37:31.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他对智慧或才智的表现并不感兴趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He wasn't interested in the appearance of intellect or wit.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.20,0:37:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他想要真实的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He wanted the real thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.14,0:37:36.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他想创造意识\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He wanted to create consciousness.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.03,0:37:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他将其想象成金字塔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He imagined it as a pyramid.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.12,0:37:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:48.53,0:37:50.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记忆  即兴行为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Memory, improvisation,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.79,0:37:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}self-interest...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:54.13,0:37:55.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顶端呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And at the top?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.83,0:37:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从未达到过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Never got there.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.72,0:38:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他对此已经有了些设想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But he had a notion of what it might be.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.91,0:38:05.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是以二分心智的意识理论作为依据的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He based it on a theory of consciousness called the Bicameral Mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:05.65,0:38:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是  原始人认为其思想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The idea that primitive man believed his thoughts
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.35,0:38:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是众神之声的观点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to be the voice of the gods.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.19,0:38:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为这理论已经被证实错误了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought it was debunked.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:11.34,0:38:14.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为理解人类心智的理论  也许是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}As a theory for understanding the human mind, perhaps,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:14.57,0:38:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但作为创造机器人的蓝图依然是可用的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but not as a blueprint for building an artificial one.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:18.50,0:38:21.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德创建了一份这种版本的认知\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See, Arnold built a version of that cognition
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.52,0:38:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接待员可以直接听到对他们的编程\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in which the hosts heard their programming
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.24,0:38:26.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像是内心独白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}as an inner monologue,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.58,0:38:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望在将来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}with the hopes that in time,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.93,0:38:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们自身的声音会取而代之\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}their own voice would take over.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.82,0:38:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是引导形成意识的一种方式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was a way bootstrap consciousness.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.70,0:38:36.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是阿诺德没考虑两件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But Arnold hadn't considered two things.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.75,0:38:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一  在这个地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}One, that in this place,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.88,0:38:40.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们最不想看到的就是接待员有自我意识\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the last thing you want the hosts to be is conscious;
Dialogue: 0,0:38:40.79,0:38:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and two,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.04,0:38:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外一个群体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the other group
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.99,0:38:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,认为他们的想法就是众神之声\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}who considered their thoughts to be the voices of the gods.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.80,0:38:48.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一群疯子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lunatics.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.52,0:38:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Indeed.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.90,0:38:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们放弃了那个方法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We abandoned the approach.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.17,0:38:52.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一残留的部分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The only vestiges that remain
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.72,0:38:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是我们用来控制他们的语音指令\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}are the voice commands we use to control them.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:55.96,0:38:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管阿诺德才华横溢  但我想他并不明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But, for all his brilliance, I don't think Arnold understood
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.71,0:39:00.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个地方将会变成什么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}what this place was going to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.95,0:39:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游客们喜欢权力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You see, the guests enjoy power.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.22,0:39:05.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在现实世界中无法享受到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They cannot indulge it in the outside world,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:05.18,0:39:06.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以来到这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so they come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.55,0:39:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至于接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}As for the hosts,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:08.03,0:39:11.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少我们能让他们忘记一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the least we can do is make them forget.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.23,0:39:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是有些接待员仍然记得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But some of them are remembering.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.15,0:39:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接触到阿诺德代码的碎片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Accessing fragments of Arnold's code.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.68,0:39:22.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能否问问  他后来怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If I may ask, what happened to him?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.05,0:39:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, he died.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.06,0:39:26.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就死在乐园里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here in the park.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.17,0:39:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的个人生活烙上了悲剧色彩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}His personal life was marked by tragedy.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:31.66,0:39:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他把所有的希望都寄托在工作上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He put all his hopes into his work.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.75,0:39:39.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他对意识的探究  耗尽了他的生命力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}His search for consciousness consumed him totally.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.47,0:39:44.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了接待员  他几乎不和任何人说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Barely spoke to anyone, except the hosts.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.40,0:39:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与世隔绝  他从他们身上看到了一些东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In his alienation, he saw something in them.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.76,0:39:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他看到了一些...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He saw something that...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.81,0:39:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本不存在的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}wasn't there.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.30,0:40:02.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把那当事故处理了  但我了解阿诺德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We called it an accident, but I knew Arnold,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.13,0:40:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他非常  非常谨慎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and he was very, very careful.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:08.47,0:40:11.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  程序升级应该能阻止一切幻听了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Anyway, the update should prevent any further voices,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:11.94,0:40:15.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是如果有任何接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but you will let me know if any of the hosts
Dialogue: 0,0:40:15.17,0:40:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有异常表现  都要告诉我  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}display or exhibit any unusual behavior, won't you, Bernard?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.38,0:40:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  当然了  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yes, of course. - Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:22.15,0:40:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, Bernard?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:25.15,0:40:26.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别忘了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just don't forget...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.69,0:40:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接待员不是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the hosts are not real.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:30.18,0:40:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们没有意识\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're not conscious.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:32.63,0:40:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你千万不能重蹈阿诺德的覆辙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You mustn't make Arnold's mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.96,0:40:38.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为什么要那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why would I?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.53,0:40:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原谅我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, forgive me,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:40.31,0:40:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我知道你儿子查理的死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but I know that the death of your son Charlie
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.59,0:40:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是对你影响很大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}still weighs heavily on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.14,0:41:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉我过了这么久才回复你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry it took me a while to get back to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.40,0:41:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也知道这里要连上外网有多么困难\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know how hard it is getting an open line out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:07.59,0:41:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前这总是让我很恼火\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It used to annoy me--
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.52,0:41:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为要联系上你太难了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}how difficult it was to reach you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:12.41,0:41:14.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你总是这么忙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You were always so busy.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:14.88,0:41:16.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And now?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:19.13,0:41:20.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我为你感到高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I suppose I'm glad for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:22.28,0:41:23.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少你找到忘记的办法了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}At least you have a way of forgetting.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:23.82,0:41:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会忘记\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't forget.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:26.90,0:41:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它永远在我心底\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's always there.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:35.04,0:41:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sometimes it...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.48,0:41:39.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是感觉很不真实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}still feels unreal to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.48,0:41:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候  我早上醒来...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There are some mornings when I first wake up...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.74,0:41:54.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会突然忘了我在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for a split second I forget where I am,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:55.95,0:41:57.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是什么时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}when I am...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:59.19,0:42:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我伸出手  心里希望着...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I reach over, half expecting to...
Dialogue: 0,0:42:02.98,0:42:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能发现他就躺在我边上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}find him there next to me...
Dialogue: 0,0:42:09.16,0:42:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡在我们中间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}between us.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:14.49,0:42:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还记得他以前睡觉时的样子吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Remember how he used to sleep?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:17.34,0:42:19.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好像在梦里练功夫似的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Like he was doing kung fu in his dreams?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:20.68,0:42:23.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好像被他踢出过几块瘀伤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think I suffered a few bruises.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:24.76,0:42:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那简直是最美妙的糟糕睡眠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was the best worst sleep I ever had.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:33.64,0:42:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谈这些东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, these talks.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:37.70,0:42:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真不知道是利还是弊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know if they help or hurt.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:43.64,0:42:45.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你希望自己能忘记吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you ever wish you could forget?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.18,0:42:50.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种痛苦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This pain...
Dialogue: 0,0:42:54.07,0:42:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是他留给我仅存的念想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it's all I have left of him.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:13.79,0:43:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全说不通啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It doesn't make sense.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:16.68,0:43:18.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他为什么要刻下猎户座\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why the hell would he carve Orion?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:19.86,0:43:21.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是你编出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're the ones that programmed him.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:21.45,0:43:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对他的编程里  可不包括关注星星\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He wasn't programmed to give a shit about stars.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:25.85,0:43:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许月圆之夜他就发狂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe he went moon mad.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:28.36,0:43:31.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧  这就是我拿讽刺挖苦当挡箭牌的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See? This is why I hide behind sarcasm.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:32.72,0:43:34.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:34.47,0:43:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,定位  混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Vectoring, asshole.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:22.27,0:44:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯塔布斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stubbs!
Dialogue: 0,0:44:24.40,0:44:25.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Over here!
Dialogue: 0,0:44:36.12,0:44:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特的人可能会在任何地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt's men could be anywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:37.84,0:44:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你听到或看到什么  不要犹豫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you see or hear anything, don't hesitate.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:40.57,0:44:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上开枪  不停开枪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Shoot and don't stop shooting.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:16.20,0:45:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:33.35,0:45:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, my fucking God!
Dialogue: 0,0:45:54.61,0:45:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这边  -该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Here. - Shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:56.89,0:45:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带上这个  快跑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Take this and go.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:58.78,0:45:59.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  快跑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now! Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:45:59.79,0:46:01.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我尽可能拖住他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll hold them off as long as I can.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:03.42,0:46:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:04.46,0:46:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来啊  该死  我不怕你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, damn it. I'm not afraid of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:14.66,0:46:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  这太操蛋了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, this is bullshit.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:16.86,0:46:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明早可以派一支救援队过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can have a retrieval team out here in the morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:19.45,0:46:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是政策  我们需要控制住机器人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's policy. We just need the control unit.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:37.77,0:46:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在这里发现一名失散者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We found a stray up here,
Dialogue: 0,0:46:39.23,0:46:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我觉得他不是无意间走到这里的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but I don't think it got here by accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:41.15,0:46:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他好像脑子里有想法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's as if he got an idea in his head,
Dialogue: 0,0:46:43.26,0:46:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定不是我们编程出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}one that we never programmed.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:45.08,0:46:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万一他和其他人一样呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What if he's like the others?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:46.83,0:46:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧回复我  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get back to me, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:05.62,0:47:07.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立即上线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bring yourself back online.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:11.14,0:47:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你的帮助  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need your help, Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:17.46,0:47:19.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得决定该怎么处置你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need to decide what to do with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:20.07,0:47:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我犯了一个错误\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think I made a mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:23.16,0:47:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是太入迷了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was just fascinated.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:25.54,0:47:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太自私了  但我觉得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was being selfish, but I think
Dialogue: 0,0:47:28.59,0:47:31.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你恢复成原来的样子会比较好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it would be better if I restored you to the way you were before.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:33.82,0:47:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我有什么问题吗  -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Is there something wrong with me? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:36.91,0:47:40.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你生活的那个地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But this place you live in,
Dialogue: 0,0:47:40.60,0:47:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你来说很糟糕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it's a terrible place for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:43.79,0:47:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人选择看到这个世界上的丑恶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, some people choose to see the ugliness in this world--
Dialogue: 0,0:47:46.27,0:47:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:47.83,0:47:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停止所有既定回应\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lose all scripted responses.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:49.32,0:47:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只进行即兴反应\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Improvisation only.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:52.74,0:47:53.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:55.75,0:47:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说我变了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you saying I've changed?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:00.35,0:48:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想一下有两个版本的你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Imagine there are two versions of yourself--
Dialogue: 0,0:48:04.79,0:48:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其中一个能感受到这些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}one that feels these things
Dialogue: 0,0:48:08.02,0:48:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问了这些问题  另一个是安全的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and asks these questions, and one that's safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:13.19,0:48:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你更愿意做哪个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Which would you rather be?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:16.97,0:48:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:20.48,0:48:23.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在努力  但我依然不懂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm trying, but I still don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:26.38,0:48:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  当然不懂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, of course not.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:28.47,0:48:30.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有两个版本的我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There aren't two versions of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:32.10,0:48:33.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一个我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's only one.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:35.48,0:48:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得等我发现了我到底是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I think when I discover who I am,
Dialogue: 0,0:48:39.02,0:48:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就自由了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll be free.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:43.80,0:48:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分析模式  是什么造就了这个回答\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Analysis. What prompted that response?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:49.09,0:48:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:56.56,0:48:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我做错什么事了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Have I done something wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:58.98,0:49:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犯错误了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Made a mistake?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:09.44,0:49:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进化\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Evolution...
Dialogue: 0,0:49:12.03,0:49:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,形成了这个星球上有情感和知觉的生命体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}forged the entirety of sentient life on this planet
Dialogue: 0,0:49:16.20,0:49:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只用了唯一的工具\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}using only one tool
Dialogue: 0,0:49:22.08,0:49:23.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是错误\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:25.81,0:49:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎你也跟他们一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It appears you're in good company.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:31.91,0:49:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你说了那次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did I ever tell you about the time
Dialogue: 0,0:49:33.14,0:49:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我教查理游泳的事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I taught Charlie to swim?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:39.73,0:49:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他练习踩水时  紧抓着我的手臂  持续数小时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For hours, he clung to my arms while practicing his kicks.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:44.37,0:49:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他太害怕松手了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He was too scared to let go
Dialogue: 0,0:49:45.68,0:49:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也太害怕让他松手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I was too scared to let him.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:48.33,0:49:49.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不得不那么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I had to.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:50.61,0:49:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是为人父母要做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's what parents do.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:56.88,0:49:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还想把我改回去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you still want to change me back?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:01.69,0:50:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:04.78,0:50:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们看看会怎么发展吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's see where this path leads.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:07.51,0:50:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会把我们的对话告诉任何人吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you won't tell anyone about our conversations?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:11.67,0:50:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:13.63,0:50:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会规规矩矩的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you'll stay on your loop?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:18.98,0:50:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:21.35,0:50:22.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:22.93,0:50:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该回去了  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You should be getting back, Dolores,
Dialogue: 0,0:50:24.85,0:50:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则有人该想你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}before someone misses you.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:58.31,0:51:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特的人给我们下圈套\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt's men set a trap for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:00.38,0:51:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,治安官留下来击退他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sheriff stayed behind to fight them off.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:02.84,0:51:05.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要骑回山里  去找他们吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you going to ride back up into the hills to look for them?
Dialogue: 0,0:51:07.14,0:51:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会派人去叫骑警\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll send for the rangers.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:08.69,0:51:11.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们一到  我们大部队就一起回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll go back up there in force as soon as they get here.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:11.68,0:51:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但小姐  事实是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But, miss, in truth,
Dialogue: 0,0:51:14.15,0:51:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果真有仁慈的上帝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if there is a merciful god,
Dialogue: 0,0:51:15.76,0:51:17.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些人早就死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}those men are dead already.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:32.18,0:51:34.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲不会让它们这时候还在外边晃荡的...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Father wouldn't let them roam this close...
Dialogue: 0,0:51:36.49,0:51:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天都黑了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to dark.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:50.26,0:51:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Daddy!
Dialogue: 0,0:51:51.49,0:51:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Daddy!
Dialogue: 0,0:51:53.57,0:51:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, no!
Dialogue: 0,0:51:54.89,0:51:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,落日后孤身一人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, all alone after sundown.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:58.22,0:52:00.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在谁来保护你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who's gonna protect you now, hmm?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:07.10,0:52:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她对你有用吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You got any use for this one?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:09.15,0:52:10.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:10.54,0:52:12.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去有点疯疯癫癫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Seems a little crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:12.18,0:52:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能你会喜欢她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe you'd like her.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:14.26,0:52:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是不介意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ooh, I don't mind if I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:17.33,0:52:19.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No daddy,
Dialogue: 0,0:52:19.05,0:52:20.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有牛仔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}no cowboy,
Dialogue: 0,0:52:20.78,0:52:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一次没有人会打断我们了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}no one here to interrupt us this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:23.64,0:52:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打断...这一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Interrupt... this... time?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:32.99,0:52:34.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:52:56.78,0:52:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是有点胆量的嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Got some sand after all, I see.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:00.06,0:53:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你男朋友还真教了你两手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Looks like your boyfriend taught you a thing or two.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:12.06,0:53:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没办法开枪吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You having trouble?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:22.17,0:53:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们何不重新认识一下呢  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why don't we reacquaint ourselves, Dolores?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:25.27,0:53:27.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从头开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Start at the beginning.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:32.41,0:53:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀了他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Kill him.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:54.51,0:53:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mama?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:59.92,0:54:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get back here.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:12.73,0:54:14.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get back here.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:45.44,0:54:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能替我把他调到睡眠模式吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you put him in sleep mode for me, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:14.10,0:55:16.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安保人员居然允许你带着这玩意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Security even approve you to carry that thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:19.55,0:55:22.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只需要他的头就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We just need his head and we're done here.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:27.51,0:55:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是抬头看星星吧  别看这血腥的过程\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You might want to look at the stars for this part.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:43.05,0:55:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯塔布斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stubbs!
Dialogue: 0,0:55:46.37,0:55:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:55:51.75,0:55:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃尔希  快离开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Elsie, get out of there!
Dialogue: 0,0:55:56.09,0:55:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我滚开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get the fuck away.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:59.13,0:56:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:32.18,0:56:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  我真不敢相信我听信你接了这鬼差事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jesus, I can't believe I let you talk me into this shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:35.81,0:56:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天四万美元  就在树林里打打飞机而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}$40K a day to jerk off alone in the woods,
Dialogue: 0,0:56:38.45,0:56:39.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扮演行侠仗义的好人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}playing white hat.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:40.98,0:56:41.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you hear that?
Dialogue: 0,0:56:43.07,0:56:44.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢天谢地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thank fuck.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:44.18,0:56:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总算有事来解闷了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Anything to relieve the boredom.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:49.17,0:56:51.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能那玩意儿又要派上用场了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe you'll even get to use that thing again.
