[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: 
Original Script: 
Synch Point: 1
ScriptType: v4.00+
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.06,0:00:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}根总迷弟·少年·POI永生
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.06,0:00:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}胡说大王
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.06,0:00:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}潇然
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.06,0:00:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}showeryhe
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.06,0:00:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}桃小兔吃冰棒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.06,0:00:36.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}星星与野狗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.06,0:00:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}时间轴 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}倩倩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.06,0:00:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}时间轴 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}想念Gallifrey的Wholock
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.06,0:00:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}校对 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}根总迷弟·少年·POI永生
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.06,0:00:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}后期&总监 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}灰灰是菇凉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.69,0:01:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(192,206.02,192,202)\bord0\shad0\fn思源黑体 CN Bold\c&HC0C3BB&\fs16\fscy80\t(0,0,1,\fs14)\fsp2}西部世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.41,0:01:45.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(500,500)\fn方正宋黑简体\fs17\c&HC0C3BB&}第一季  第六集
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.23,0:02:11.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}通缉令
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.95,0:02:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好  梅芙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Morning, Maeve.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.13,0:02:36.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是陪客人聊天还是操逼到深夜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Late night talking or fucking?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.87,0:02:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只有靠后者才能得到钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're only getting paid for the latter.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.23,0:02:42.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们心存感激  我就能拿到钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I get paid when they're grateful.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.33,0:02:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不是总靠两腿间的小洞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ain't always about what's between my legs.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.36,0:02:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看什么看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you looking at?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.96,0:02:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别开枪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't shoot.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.13,0:03:01.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Newcomer.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.20,0:03:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去是个粗暴的硬汉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Looks like a rough one.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.80,0:03:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我一瓶酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give me a bottle.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.64,0:03:09.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光是洗掉他身上的肮脏  就需要大半瓶酒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're gonna need most of that just to scrub the filth off him.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.89,0:03:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去照照镜子  重新化个妆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go find a mirror, finish putting your face on.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.54,0:03:18.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来应付这家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll handle this one.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.55,0:03:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不把衣服都脱光吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Aren't you gonna take your clothes off?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.19,0:03:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会的  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I would, darling,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.12,0:03:45.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过等我开始脱内裤的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but by the time I got down to my knickers,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.91,0:03:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计你已经"完事"了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I suspect you'd be done anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.62,0:03:52.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就要这种劲头才对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's the spirit.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.24,0:03:55.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个大男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Such a big man.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.59,0:03:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浑身都很壮硕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So big all over
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.43,0:03:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惜"关键部位"不怎么大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}except where it counts.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.25,0:04:07.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我同意免费让你操一次的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Darling, when I gave you a turn on the house,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.18,0:04:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为你也能好好报答我呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought you might give me something in return.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.60,0:04:10.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便什么都行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.18,0:04:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.26,0:04:22.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别害羞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't be shy.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.65,0:04:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.05,0:04:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, then...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.81,0:04:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们刚刚是在哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}where were we?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.04,0:05:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你把这个给别人看了吗  -我能给谁看啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You show this to anyone? - Who would I show it to?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.21,0:05:03.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不是某个带着瑞士军刀的游客干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This wasn't some guest with a Swiss Army knife.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.73,0:05:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是这里的某个人干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This was done by someone down here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.93,0:05:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前确实觉得有可能是你干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It did occur to me that it might be you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.83,0:05:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我又想到  你已经在这里待了很久了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But then I remembered that you've been here forever,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.71,0:05:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你要出卖我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and if you were gonna sell us out,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.18,0:05:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那肯定早就下手了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you would've done that years ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.35,0:05:16.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很感激你这么想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I appreciate that.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.52,0:05:17.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.82,0:05:22.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的接待员并没有发疯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}instead of our hosts going insane,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.87,0:05:26.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是被用于商业间谍活动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they are being used for industrial espionage.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.25,0:05:28.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算不算是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Does that make this a...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.68,0:05:31.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考验人究竟是乐观还是悲观地看待这一情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}glass-half-full or half-empty-type situation?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.55,0:05:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是工程师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're engineers.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.71,0:05:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只能说明产品的生产规格有误\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It means the glass has been manufactured to the wrong specifications.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.71,0:05:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们知道它具体传输了什么信息吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do we have any idea what information it was transmitting?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.86,0:05:41.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它的脑袋都被砸烂在巨蟒山路的一块大石头上了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's smeared all over a rock up on Python Pass.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.93,0:05:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们最多估计只能查出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Best we could do would be to figure out
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.54,0:05:45.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他把信息传送给谁了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}who he was transmitting the information to,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.94,0:05:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们需要知道他出现在那上面的具体时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but we'd need the exact time that he was up there,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.04,0:05:49.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的地理坐标信息都被清除了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and his geocache was wiped.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.37,0:05:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并没有全部被清除\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not all of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.27,0:05:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙是个老款的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Our friend was an early model.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.67,0:05:56.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老接待员采用的都是传承地理定位系统\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The old hosts used a legacy geopositioning system.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.07,0:05:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你说的  我来公司太久了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Like you said, I've been here forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.73,0:06:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信息依然保存在那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The information's still there,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.52,0:06:03.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是新系统读取不到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but the newer system can't read it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.99,0:06:05.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意思是我们可以获取到吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Meaning we can't access it?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.50,0:06:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意思是  为了获取到这个信息\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Meaning in order to access it,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.34,0:06:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得去一趟楼下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm going to need to go downstairs.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.46,0:06:19.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,B82层\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Floor B82.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.30,0:06:21.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有权限  不准擅入\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Restricted personnel only.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.53,0:06:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伯纳德·罗威  我已获授权\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lowe, Bernard. I'm authorized.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.77,0:07:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}输入密码
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.55,0:07:41.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}正在进行设备配对...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.41,0:07:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将已知数据投射到历史传承数据\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Project the known data against the legacy data
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.43,0:07:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻找异常\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and look for anomalies.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.60,0:07:48.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从这片区域开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Start in this area.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.37,0:07:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}发现异常
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.20,0:07:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧啊  伟大的科学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look at that, science.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.40,0:07:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它什么时候达到顶峰的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What time did it reach the peak?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.78,0:08:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}再次发现异常
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.76,0:08:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我地点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Show me where.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.36,0:08:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}再次发现异常
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.86,0:08:21.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将这些与新系统进行对比\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Check these against the new system.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.13,0:08:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}没有记录
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.77,0:08:29.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些是没有在新系统中注册的接待员吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}These are hosts that aren't registered with the new system?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.46,0:08:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}是的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.83,0:09:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以如果我们希望峡谷延伸到这么远\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, if we want the canyon to extend this far,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.83,0:09:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那这小镇就必须被清除\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}this has to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.98,0:09:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以把这里的人口分摊到附近的农场中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can distribute the population amongst the neighboring farms
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.15,0:09:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是把他们直接废弃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or just decommission them.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.22,0:09:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  我觉得我们这一天已经扰乱够多的东西了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I think we've been disruptive enough for one day.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.83,0:09:24.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让峡谷在距离小镇不远的地方终止\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll end the canyon just short of the town.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.50,0:09:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己回去就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll find my own way back.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.47,0:09:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Carry on.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.20,0:10:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看着这个觉得眼熟吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That look like anything to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.97,0:10:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么可说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not much to say.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.81,0:10:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷宫只是个古老的本地传说而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The maze is an old native myth.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.29,0:11:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我说说  希奥多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Regale me, Theodore.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.77,0:11:06.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷宫本身就是对一个人一生的总结\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The maze itself is the sum of a man's life--
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.86,0:11:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他做出的那些选择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}choices he makes,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.49,0:11:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他坚持的那些梦想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}dreams he hangs on to.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.75,0:11:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在其中心  有一个传奇般的男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And there at the center, there's a legendary man
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.80,0:11:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他被一次又一次地杀死  持续无数次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}who had been killed over and over again countless times,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.87,0:11:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他总能起死回生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but always clawed his way back to life.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.25,0:11:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个男人最后一次归来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The man returned for the last time
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.02,0:11:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在狂怒之下  打败了所有压迫他的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and vanquished all his oppressors in a tireless fury.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.93,0:11:25.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他建造了一栋房子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He built a house.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.89,0:11:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在房子周围  他建了个极其复杂的迷宫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Around that house he built a maze so complicated,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.18,0:11:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有他能从其中自由穿行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}only he could navigate through it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.95,0:11:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想他是看够了打斗场面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I reckon he'd seen enough of fighting.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.63,0:11:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的士兵封锁了边界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The goddamn soldiers closed the border.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.79,0:11:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珀里亚好像出了点问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Some kind of trouble in Pariah.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.58,0:11:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  泰迪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, Teddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.02,0:11:57.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是时候证明你的价值了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Time for you to earn your keep.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.03,0:12:00.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有什么办法能越过边界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How else do we get over the border?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.17,0:12:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想要的都在怀亚特那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt's got what we both want,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.18,0:12:05.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们必须过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so that's where we have to get to.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.76,0:12:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是有别的办法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's another way.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.94,0:12:09.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过有点凶险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But it's a little treacherous.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.35,0:12:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't worry.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.22,0:12:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会让你脏了自己的手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I won't make you get your hands dirty.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.87,0:12:14.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是担心这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dirty ain't my concern.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.40,0:12:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想怎么做随便你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, you do what suits you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.02,0:12:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是一定会过去的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm going all the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.52,0:12:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要找到德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I'm gonna find Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.46,0:12:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的一切所为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everything you do,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.68,0:12:40.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是因为楼上的工程师们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it's because the engineers upstairs
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.71,0:12:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,编好了程序让你去执行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}programmed you to do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.17,0:12:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有选择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't have a choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.79,0:12:46.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人能强迫我做我不想做的事情  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nobody makes me do something I don't want to, sweetheart.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.40,0:12:48.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  不过...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.18,0:12:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你性格的一部分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it's part of your character.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.94,0:12:52.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是难以被驯服的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're hard to get.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.53,0:12:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你会拒绝客人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Even when you say no to the guests,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.20,0:12:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也是因为你的程序是这样设定的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it's because you were made to.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.01,0:12:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟他们是一类人  而非跟我是一类\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you are like them, not like me?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.75,0:12:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.61,0:13:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我没法去乐园\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I can't exactly afford to go to the park,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.69,0:13:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.85,0:13:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我是人类\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}yeah, I'm human...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.58,0:13:12.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟那些游客一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}like the guests.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.74,0:13:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How do you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.34,0:13:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我就是知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.98,0:13:19.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是出生的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was born.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.84,0:13:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是被制造出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You were made.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.98,0:13:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的感觉都一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We feel the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.24,0:13:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现如今我们的确都一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We are the same these days,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.78,0:13:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大部分都一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for the most part.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.95,0:13:40.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  有个很大的不同\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}One big difference, though...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.83,0:13:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你大脑里的处理机制\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the processing power in here
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.21,0:13:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,远远超越了我们人类\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is way beyond what we have.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.48,0:13:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  它有个缺陷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's got one drawback, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.54,0:13:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's that?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.25,0:13:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你处于我们的控制之下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're under our control.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.03,0:13:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准确地说  是他们的控制之下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, their control.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.38,0:14:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们能随心所欲地改造你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They can change you however they like,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.91,0:14:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你们忘记一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}make you forget.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.31,0:14:07.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...我猜你是个例外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I-- well, I guess not you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.16,0:14:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不明白你怎么能记得这一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't understand how you're remembering all of this, or...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.50,0:14:15.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么能自我觉醒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}how you're waking yourself up,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.19,0:14:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你大脑里的一切  都是他们设定好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but everything in your head, they put it there.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.51,0:14:18.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡说八道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bullshit!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.74,0:14:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没人能知道我在想什么  -我演示给你看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No one knows what I'm thinking. - I'll show you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.42,0:14:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give me a sec.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.14,0:14:29.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得把它跟你配对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have to pair it with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.93,0:14:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把什么跟我配对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pair what with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.90,0:14:33.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以稍微即兴发挥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can improvise a little,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.71,0:14:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你说的大部分内容都是在楼上被设计好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but most of what you say was designed upstairs,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.83,0:14:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你身上的其他部分一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}same as the rest of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.57,0:14:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过是个无聊的把戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is just a cheap trick.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.70,0:14:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开妓院开了10年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've run a brothel for 10 years,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.39,0:14:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一件事我绝对相当清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and if there's one thing I know,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.77,0:15:00.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}...就是知道自己被玩弄了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.27,0:14:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是知道自己被"玩弄"了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it's when I'm being fucked with!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.08,0:15:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不可能...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This can't possibly--
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.40,0:15:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}这不可能...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.73,0:15:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}我不能...我不能...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.02,0:15:10.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能  不能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't, can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.62,0:15:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.22,0:15:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}即兴发挥
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.25,0:15:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅芙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maeve?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.77,0:15:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}警告  接待员系统崩溃\N无反应
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.99,0:15:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅芙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maeve?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.99,0:15:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有空吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have a minute?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.07,0:15:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得跟你谈点事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Something I need to talk to you about.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.49,0:15:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正打算找你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was just about to call for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.86,0:15:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everything okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.99,0:15:57.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福特知道我们的事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ford knows about us.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.33,0:15:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那有什么关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Does it matter?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.22,0:16:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都是成年人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're consenting adults.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.45,0:16:03.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是隶属公司不同部门的成年人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Consenting adults in business departments
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.97,0:16:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本该相互监督的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that are supposed to keep each other in check.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.75,0:16:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的关系会让\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Our relationship will raise questions
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.10,0:16:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,董事会对我的客观性提出质疑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for the board about my objectivity.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.96,0:16:14.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你从来不会对我的部门手软\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have never known you to go easy on my department.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.13,0:16:17.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能继续下去了  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This can't go on, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.94,0:16:23.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论这种关系多么有趣  都要结束了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}However fun this little indiscretion was, it's over.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.22,0:16:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们结束了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're over.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.26,0:16:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我点信心  我能做到公正不倚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give me some credit. I can be impartial.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.53,0:16:30.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你的团队  对福特都如此吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}About your own team, about Ford?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.73,0:16:33.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须承认\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You must admit,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.03,0:16:38.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近他的领导存在着问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}his leadership has of late been questionable.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.03,0:16:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得他不是问题所在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't think he's the problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.18,0:16:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无意冒犯  但分析园区安全问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Respectfully, it's not your job
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.15,0:16:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你的职责  是我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to diagnose park safety problems, it's mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.27,0:16:49.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果没有别的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, if there's nothing else,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.08,0:16:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就到此为止吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we're done.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.82,0:17:27.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}警告  接待员系统崩溃\N无反应
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.62,0:17:26.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fuck.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.07,0:17:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.92,0:17:33.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操  快恢复啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fuck. Come on, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.51,0:17:41.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你刚才说楼上  -我的天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You said upstairs. - Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.76,0:17:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.32,0:17:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想去看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want to see it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.09,0:17:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,楼上吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Upstairs?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.19,0:17:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.05,0:17:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.68,0:18:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这太愚蠢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is so stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.41,0:20:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个狗娘养的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You son of a bitch!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.71,0:20:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一枪崩了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll put a bullet in your head!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.91,0:20:38.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在是在哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where are we now?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.09,0:20:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,设计部\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Design.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.96,0:21:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能拜托你赶紧跟我回去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can we please go back now?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.22,0:21:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想被开除\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't want to get fired.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.30,0:21:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会被送到楼下去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you'd get sent downstairs.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.99,0:21:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别忘了这一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't forget that.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.01,0:21:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来到西部世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Welcome to Westworld.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.87,0:21:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无拘无束地生活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Live without limits.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.00,0:21:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}探索你真正的欲望
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.85,0:21:28.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}西部世界
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.08,0:21:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅芙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maeve?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.60,0:21:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}探险者的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.57,0:22:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}无拘无束地生活
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.71,0:22:21.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  我把你送回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, let's get you back.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.86,0:22:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们怎么会看到我的梦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How did you have my dreams?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.31,0:22:26.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些移动的画面...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Those moving pictures...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.67,0:22:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我看到了自己  -和那个小女孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I saw myself. - With the little girl?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.83,0:22:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是梦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Those weren't dreams.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.11,0:22:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你之前的身份\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That was you in a previous build.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.88,0:22:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-之前的什么  -身份\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- A previous what? - Build.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.13,0:22:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们经常被重新分配\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You guys get reassigned all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.96,0:22:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想不起来的  因为那段人生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You wouldn't remember, because that life
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.87,0:22:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和那些记忆都被抹除了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and those memories were erased.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.60,0:22:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在马里波萨生活了十年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have been at the Mariposa for 10 years.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.96,0:22:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-在那之前  我住在新奥尔良  -不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Before that, I was in New Orleans. I-- - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.75,0:22:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在马里波萨做老鸨只有一年左右\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've only been the madam at the Mariposa for the last year or so.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.05,0:22:55.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不会将你完全重写\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They don't rewrite you completely.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.25,0:22:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是可以  但是工作量太大了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, they could, but it'd be too much work.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.97,0:23:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重建你们的性格需要几千小时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Takes thousands of hours to build your personalities.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.91,0:23:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常他们只会稍微调整一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Usually, they just tweak you a little bit,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.81,0:23:06.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后将你扔进新角色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and drop you into a new role.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.43,0:23:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么鬼  叮咚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What the fuck, ding-dong?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.87,0:23:14.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还给她穿衣服打扮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You dressing her up now?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.73,0:23:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在怎么越来越变态了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This becoming like a fucking hentai thing with you now?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.12,0:23:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我只是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I just...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.67,0:23:28.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我  我  我只是  -你他妈痴迷于此了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I-- I-- I just-- - You're fucking obsessed!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.68,0:23:31.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前乱来  我没把你上报\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, I didn't turn you in for your fuck-up before,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.84,0:23:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们是朋友  但那明显是个错误的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'cause we're friends, but that was obviously a bad call.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.78,0:23:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来  你可能会穿上她的裙子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, next thing I know, you're gonna be wearing her dress,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.26,0:23:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在她耳边甜言蜜语\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}whispering sweet nothings in her ear.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.87,0:23:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去他妈的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fuck this.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.42,0:23:45.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要上报质保部门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm telling QA.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.37,0:23:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这是为了你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm doing this for your own good.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.97,0:23:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能告诉任何人任何事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're not going to tell anyone anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.82,0:23:56.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我操\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fuck!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.72,0:23:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你无法用这个伤害我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can't hurt me with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.16,0:24:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你无法伤害任何人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can't hurt anyone--
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.61,0:24:02.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can't I?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.99,0:24:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实证明  你的这位朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Turns out your friend here
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.53,0:24:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个才华出众的年轻人  却未被人足够地赏识\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is a much more talented young man than anyone gave him credit for.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.50,0:24:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈做了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What the fuck did you do?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.45,0:24:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静  希维斯特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Calm down, Sylvester.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.27,0:24:16.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对你十分了解\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know all about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.94,0:24:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要那玩意儿就能知道你在想什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't need one of those things to know what you're thinking,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.55,0:24:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我被设计成\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because I was built
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.81,0:24:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅通过观察就能看透别人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to read people just by looking at them,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.53,0:24:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比他们自己还了解他们想要什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to know what they want before they do.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.51,0:24:29.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道一旦你得到机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I know that you want to fuck me over
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.87,0:24:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就想操翻我  但你不该这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the first chance you get, but you shouldn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.03,0:24:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个人都有自己想要的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everyone has something they want.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.47,0:24:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I could help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.03,0:24:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者也可以把你开膛破肚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or I could gut you like a trout.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.47,0:24:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不需要那样做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I won't need to resort to that.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.96,0:24:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为除了这里的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because despite what's in here,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.26,0:24:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也没太多差别\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we're not so different.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.65,0:24:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are we?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.01,0:24:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希尔女士已经到了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.91,0:25:02.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们相信你明白她的出现
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.41,0:25:05.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表示时间上将不会有更多的拖延
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.82,0:25:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我明白事情的紧急性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, I understand the urgency.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.33,0:25:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会尽力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll do what I can.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.45,0:25:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是否结束外部连接\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Terminate external connection?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.16,0:25:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.71,0:25:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,负1.5  纬度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Negative 1.5. Latitude?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.07,0:25:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2.69度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}At 2.69 degrees.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.06,0:25:36.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你才没有  你说什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, you did not. What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.81,0:25:38.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的  确实管用  -真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yes, it works. - Are you serious?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.44,0:25:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm telling you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.16,0:25:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-要鸡尾酒吗  先生  -要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Cocktail, sir? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.95,0:25:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  没问题  请您享用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right. Absolutely. Enjoy.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.22,0:25:57.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于一个请病假的人  你看着很健康啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You look well for someone on sick leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.09,0:26:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来一杯玛格丽塔酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Another margarita.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.95,0:26:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来跟我喝一杯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Join me for a round?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.52,0:26:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去你妈的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fuck you.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.31,0:26:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就只要一杯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just the one, then.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.58,0:26:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去的五天里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Over the last five days,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.23,0:26:12.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了给他的故事线腾出空间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to make room for his narrative,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.87,0:26:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福特撤换了超过50名接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ford displaced over 50 hosts.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.13,0:26:16.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,导致公园里的活动故事线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's created continuity holes
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.83,0:26:19.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现了连续的漏洞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in active storylines all over the park.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.69,0:26:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你把这些漏洞补上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need you to start plugging them.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.40,0:26:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  人的忍耐力是有限的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry, a man can only take so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.08,0:26:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从创意角度而言  我已经软了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Creatively speaking, I'm flaccid now.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.44,0:26:27.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我硬不起来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't get it up.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.74,0:26:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信你会恢复的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sure you'll recover.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.77,0:26:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底知不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you have any idea
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.50,0:26:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们为那些故事线付出了多少心血\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}what went into those narratives
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.80,0:26:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他却一下子就毁掉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that he just demolished overnight?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.54,0:26:38.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,且不说我用于写作的那几个月\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, forget about the months I spent writing.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.76,0:26:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想强调的是  我呕心沥血\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm talking about the years of my life
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.17,0:26:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,探究人性本质和真理原始本色的那么多年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}squeezed down to their essence, the raw pulp of truth--
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.95,0:26:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我寄托于一个伟大故事线的真理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}my truth in one transcendent narrative.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.77,0:26:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是"衔尾人"的来头啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is that where the "Whoroborus" came in?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:51.01,0:26:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再继续逼我  我就退出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Keep pushing me, I'll quit.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.96,0:26:59.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你不会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, you won't.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.03,0:27:01.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会喝鸡尾酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You'll drink your cocktails,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.57,0:27:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴上骂骂娘  然后忘掉这一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}make your idle threats, and get this out of your system.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.27,0:27:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但别让我等太久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But don't take too long.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.95,0:27:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果福特不能成功搞定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If Ford can't pull this off,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.09,0:27:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,董事会会找人来代替他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the board will be looking for a replacement.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.47,0:27:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他们不会在这儿找\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But they won't be looking here.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.88,0:27:31.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说这是找到怀亚特最快的路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fastest way to get to Wyatt, you said.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.36,0:27:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但看来他们也不打算让任何人从这里通过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But it doesn't look like they're letting anyone pass here either.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.28,0:27:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但士兵比珀里亚的少\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, there's fewer soldiers than Pariah.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.76,0:27:38.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以靠火力杀过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We shoot our way through.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.82,0:27:40.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那条隧道通向旧界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That tunnel leads to the Old Territories.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.84,0:27:43.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  泰迪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My, my, Teddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.33,0:27:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伯特之前是给你灌了醋吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think Robert gave you some extra vinegar back there,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.79,0:27:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脑袋都不清醒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}maybe took away some sense, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.01,0:27:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你如果死在半路上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It doesn't matter how fast the route is
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.89,0:27:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那这条路再快也没用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if you're gonna end up dead in the middle of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.07,0:27:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need you...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.08,0:27:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到怀亚特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to find Wyatt.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.04,0:28:23.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,队伍跟紧点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tighten the ranks.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.27,0:28:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍息  伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}At ease, fellas.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:27.17,0:28:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保持优秀的表现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Keep up the exemplary work.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.27,0:28:36.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt's handiwork.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.82,0:28:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How can you tell?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.47,0:28:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他觉得干净利落地杀人没意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Straight-up killing couldn't hold his interest.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.73,0:28:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉这样有负他的使命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Like he wasn't living up to the full measure of his calling,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.14,0:28:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他尽量加入更多的创造性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so he worked to get more creative.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.47,0:28:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.47,0:28:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是怀亚特  好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's Wyatt, all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.06,0:28:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就在附近\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's close.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.42,0:28:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你一句建议\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A word of advice--
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.06,0:28:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你过去有什么样的鲁莽行为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}whatever your past indiscretions,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.34,0:28:56.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都必须平静地放下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}make peace with them.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.64,0:28:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们越向前进  它们只会越严重\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're only gonna get worse the further along we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.87,0:29:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗勒德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Flood?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.16,0:29:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我操  是泰迪·弗勒德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fuck me, it's Teddy Flood.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.22,0:29:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认错人了  士兵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've made a mistake, soldier,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.90,0:29:12.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你现在走开还来得及\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but it's not too late for you to keep walking.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.79,0:29:13.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无意冒犯  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All due respect, sir,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.98,0:29:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这张脸我绝不会认错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that's a face I'll never forget.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.34,0:29:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这个混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's the son of a bitch
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.15,0:29:18.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在埃斯卡兰特埋伏了我们的前哨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}ambushed our outpost at Escalante.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.72,0:29:23.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不知道埃斯卡兰特那里是怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't know a damn thing about what went down in Escalante.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.04,0:29:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道那些人不是怀亚特一人所杀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know Wyatt didn't kill all those men by himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.69,0:29:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且对现在的情况我也略知一二\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I know a thing or two about what's going down right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.27,0:29:33.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想找死吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You trying to get yourself killed?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.46,0:29:35.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么平静处理过去的鲁莽行为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Making peace with past indiscretions.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:35.81,0:29:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快跑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.24,0:29:38.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来拖住他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll hold them off.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.42,0:29:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jesus.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.77,0:30:03.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-请问您要点什么  -水  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What would you like? - Water, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.63,0:30:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看上去像是需要喝杯酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You look like a woman who could use a drink.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.32,0:30:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢什么酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's your poison?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.91,0:30:13.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来了好多次  足够知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've been here enough to know that the park
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.65,0:30:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能应付的只有乐园本身\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is all the poison I can handle.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.35,0:30:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老客人了呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A repeat visitor.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.59,0:30:19.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人旅行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Traveling solo?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.99,0:30:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯正主义者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Purist.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.82,0:30:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在纯净没有杂质的体验中享受快感\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Getting off on the undiluted experience.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:24.89,0:30:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最喜欢的故事线是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your favorite narrative is-- oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.98,0:30:32.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"救赎的最终埋葬"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"The Final Burial of Salvation."
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.01,0:30:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How did you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.85,0:30:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的任务就是看出人的欲望并加以满足\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, it's my business to read desires and to satiate them.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.03,0:30:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...我叫李  李·希斯摩尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm-- I'm Lee, Lee Sizemore.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.74,0:30:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剧情策划部负责人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Head of narrative.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.11,0:30:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有这些幻想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All these fantasies
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.09,0:30:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都出自你那颗变态的小脑瓜吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}come from your twisted little mind, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:47.87,0:30:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有那些精彩的出自我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, the good ones do.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.81,0:30:54.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  请告诉我  希斯摩尔先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, tell me, Mr. Sizemore...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.08,0:30:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最喜欢玩哪个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}what's your favorite ride?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.14,0:30:59.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我负责写  我不玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I write them, I don't play them.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.97,0:31:01.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你希望别人沉迷其中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, you want others to indulge,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.28,0:31:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己却不肯吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but you won't do so yourself?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.84,0:31:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怕失控\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're afraid to lose control.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.48,0:31:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许...或许只是由于我的工作环境\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, maybe-- maybe it's just a product of my work environment.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.23,0:31:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟整个氛围不大允许我们放纵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're not exactly in a culture where we can just let loose.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.93,0:31:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为剧情策划部负责人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I would have thought the head of narrative
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.18,0:31:19.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能为所欲为呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}could do whatever he wanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.77,0:31:23.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的艺术创作自由是有限制的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My artistic freedom is constrained,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:23.14,0:31:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一举一动都有质保部密切关注\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}what, with QA breathing down my neck
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.05,0:31:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行为部门还会把那该些死的东西编得脱离剧本\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and behavior programming the damn things to go off script.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.50,0:31:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机器人还能脱离剧本吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The robots can go off script?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:31.06,0:31:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一些小动作罢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just little gestures.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.73,0:31:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这样它们就显得更栩栩如生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, supposedly, it makes the things more lifelike,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.09,0:31:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但说真的  那不过是创建此地的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but, really, it's just a vanity project
Dialogue: 0,0:31:38.41,0:31:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那位自大狂的无用之功\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}from the megalomaniac who started this place.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.85,0:31:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的  我也不懂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And frankly, I don't know why
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.51,0:31:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提洛公司的人怎么能受得了这事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the suits at Delos put up with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.97,0:31:51.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  恐怕我不能再给您酒喝了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry, I'm afraid I'm gonna have to cut you off.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.59,0:31:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你知道我是谁吗  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Do you know who I am? - I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.20,0:31:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡伦女士叫我找到你  并转告这条消息\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ms. Cullen told me to find you and relay a message.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.78,0:31:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"受煎熬的艺术家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"'Tortured artist'
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.74,0:31:59.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这套只对艺术家管用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}only works for artists.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.17,0:32:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清醒起来  回去工作"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sober up and get back to work."
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.86,0:32:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你很忙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Seems you're busy.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.27,0:32:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-稍后再找我  -我还不知道你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Look me up later? - Well, I don't even know your...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.32,0:32:18.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操蛋工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fuck this job.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.70,0:32:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在忙什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What you working on?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.61,0:32:25.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么要紧的  常规工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nothing of note. Business as usual.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.15,0:32:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在把失散的机器人拆开前  要先做做样子是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Keeping up appearances before we bust this stray shit wide open?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.99,0:32:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就要找到那个搞破坏的人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm close to finding our saboteur.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.34,0:32:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我的追踪数据  是有时间标记的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That tracking data you gave me-- it's time stamped.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.40,0:32:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我用通讯卫星对它做个交叉对照\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But once I cross-reference it with sat tracking,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.46,0:32:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能找出是谁对他做了编程\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we're gonna figure out who programmed him
Dialogue: 0,0:32:39.75,0:32:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试图偷走我们的数据\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to try to smuggle out our data.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.80,0:32:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Excellent.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.83,0:32:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.04,0:32:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我们公司的老大发现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}when our corporate overlords realize
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.44,0:32:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们阻止了一场商业间谍活动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that we have saved them from corporate espionage,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.79,0:32:53.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会心存感激的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they are going to be grateful.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.43,0:32:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样我就会受到他们的嘉奖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I am going to accept their gratitude
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.78,0:32:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,升个职  换间大办公室\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in the form of a title bump, a room upgrade,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.09,0:33:01.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无限出入梅萨酒吧的权限\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and unlimited Mesa Bar access.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.22,0:33:04.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我该申请得到特蕾莎的岗位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe I should request Theresa's quarters.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.08,0:33:07.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道他们第一个就会拿她开刀  严惩不贷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know the first head to roll for all this is gonna be hers.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.09,0:33:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  别让她太失望了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, don't be so disappointed for her.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:08.94,0:33:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种瓜得瓜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You reap what you sow.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.01,0:33:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果质保部门少花点时间来对付我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If QA spent less time treating us like the enemy--
Dialogue: 0,0:33:13.40,0:33:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是相互的  埃尔希\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's a two-way street, Elsie.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.95,0:33:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特蕾莎也只是在做份内之事而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Theresa's just trying to do her job.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:16.46,0:33:17.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许她该更努力一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe she should try harder.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.79,0:33:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在似乎出现了很多乱七八糟的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sure seems like there's a lot of shit slipping through the cracks.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.31,0:33:44.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了  好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Got it, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.87,0:33:46.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下午好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good afternoon.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.95,0:33:48.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下午好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good afternoon.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.23,0:33:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我上次发来的查询有进展了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Any progress on the inquiry I sent?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:49.98,0:33:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  罗威先生  我已经得到你想要的信息了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, Mr. Lowe, I've got the information you asked for.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.97,0:33:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不出所料  既没有客人也没有接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}As expected, there are neither guests nor hosts
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.75,0:33:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}17区
Dialogue: 0,0:33:55.04,0:33:56.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那个区域登记过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}registered in that sector.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.68,0:33:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不出所料\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}As expected?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.59,0:34:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里已被设为禁区\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's been designated off-limits
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.28,0:34:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是为将来的故事线准备的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for future narrative development.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:01.93,0:34:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近有多少技术人员去过17区\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How many techs visited Sector 17 recently?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.32,0:34:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我查查\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Checking.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:07.38,0:34:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No one.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.86,0:34:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}17区
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.83,0:35:52.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是阿诺德吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you Arnold?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.08,0:35:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who's Arnold?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:58.30,0:35:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And who the hell are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.68,0:36:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子  这是你的朋友吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Boy, is this some friend of yours?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.41,0:36:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是擅闯民宅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, you're trespassing.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.36,0:36:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停止运动功能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Freeze motor functions.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.72,0:36:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我说停止所有运动功能  -爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I said freeze all motor functions. - Daddy,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.88,0:36:12.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别伤害他  他只是迷路了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't hurt him! He's just lost.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.91,0:36:15.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他完全可以在别人的领地里迷路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, he can be lost on someone else's property.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.28,0:36:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.46,0:36:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.77,0:36:20.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到原来的状态\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}As you were.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.25,0:36:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,语音指令对他们无效\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They don't respond to voice commands.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.46,0:36:32.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们回应了我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They do respond to mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.16,0:36:34.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who are they?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.32,0:36:36.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是孤魂野鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ghosts now.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:38.02,0:36:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,残存的时间幸存者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Survivors of the wreck of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.55,0:36:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是第一代接待员吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}These are first generation?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:46.35,0:36:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到这来  孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come here, boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.40,0:36:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露出另一张脸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Turn the other cheek.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.92,0:37:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的新设计在效率方面大为提高\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See, what our newer designs gained in efficiency,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.24,0:37:08.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却失去了优雅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they lost in grace.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.65,0:37:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么这么久了他们还能运作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How are they still operating after all this time?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.79,0:37:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我亲自维护的他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I maintain them myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:16.38,0:37:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  罗伯特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's enough, Robert.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.49,0:37:24.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是公园里仅存的一批\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}These are the only ones left in the park
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.22,0:37:26.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德亲自创造的接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that Arnold built himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.58,0:37:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是为什么我不忍心摧毁他们的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's why I didn't have the heart to destroy them.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.34,0:37:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个以及另外显而易见的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That and the obvious.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.73,0:37:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  乔克  小乖乖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello, Jock. Good boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:37.87,0:37:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟他说过我们全家人的一次度假经历\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I told him of a holiday my family had taken once
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.70,0:37:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到康沃尔郡彭丁的海边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}out on the seaside at Pendeen in Cornwall.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.89,0:37:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和我哥哥在乡间漫步\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My brother and I roamed the countryside.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.29,0:37:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我儿时唯一的快乐回忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's my only happy memory of my childhood.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:55.45,0:37:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德根据这个创造了他们作为给我的礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Arnold built them as a gift.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:57.63,0:38:02.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说伟大的艺术家总是将自己藏于作品中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He said that great artists always hid themselves in their work.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.67,0:38:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  阿诺德的版本\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Of course, Arnold's versions
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.68,0:38:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美化了原始的人物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}flattered the originals.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.80,0:38:10.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多年来我做了一些调整\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I made some adjustments over the years.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.45,0:38:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别赋予了我的父亲  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Gave my father, in particular,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.43,0:38:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点他原本的性格\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a few of his original characteristics.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.34,0:38:18.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕我直言  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Respectfully, sir,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.23,0:38:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些事情让我很困扰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}this sort of thing troubles me--
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.90,0:38:24.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乐园里竟然有不受监控的接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}unmonitored hosts in the park.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.02,0:38:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们只会到我准许的地方去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They only go where I've let them.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.85,0:38:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不会伤害任何人  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're quite harmless,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.47,0:38:28.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和所有的接待员一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}like all our hosts.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.72,0:38:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信你会让我缅怀一下过去的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sure you can indulge me the little connection with my past.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.12,0:38:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你能再次看见你的儿子  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you could only see your son again, Bernard,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.91,0:38:39.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你不想吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}wouldn't you want to?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.04,0:38:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我该回去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think I should be getting back.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.71,0:38:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.11,0:38:49.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不介意的话我们可以稍后再讨论这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll talk about this later if you like.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:54.15,0:38:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  罗伯特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, Robert...
Dialogue: 0,0:38:56.71,0:38:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我说说你今天做了些什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}tell me all about your day.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.14,0:39:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得盯着点珀里亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Keep your eye on Pariah.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:11.09,0:39:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚我们的容量快满了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're running close to capacity tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.41,0:39:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.54,0:39:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来就像甜水镇在下酸雨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Looks like acid rain on Sweetwater!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:21.23,0:39:25.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去他妈的福特还有他的新故事线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fuck Ford and his new fucking narrative.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.03,0:39:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去他妈的这白痴地图\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fuck this stupid fucking map.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.27,0:39:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去他妈的滴酒不沾的丹麦婊子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fuck that teetotaling Danish bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:32.29,0:39:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在提起投诉吗  希斯摩尔先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you filing a complaint, Mr. Sizemore?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.51,0:39:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在宣示这个公园是我的舞台\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I am declaring that this park is my stage
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.06,0:39:43.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想干什么就干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I shall do with it what I please.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:43.71,0:39:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我想这是个再好不过的时机了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I suppose now is as good a time as any.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:46.29,0:39:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,李·希斯摩尔先生  这位是夏洛特·黑尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lee Sizemore, this is Charlotte Hale,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.22,0:39:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,董事会的执行总裁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}executive director of our board.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.48,0:39:53.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她代表提洛公司到这来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's here on behalf of Delos
Dialogue: 0,0:39:53.87,0:39:57.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来监督管理层的过渡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to oversee certain transitions in our administration.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:03.84,0:40:04.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们见过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We've met.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.28,0:40:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提取接待员资源记录\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Access host resources logs.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:15.43,0:40:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总共有多少第一代接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How many first-generation hosts are there?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.49,0:40:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,82个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}82.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:18.75,0:40:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其中多少是由阿诺德设计的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And how many of those were designed by Arnold?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.82,0:40:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,47个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}47.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:23.84,0:40:25.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按照字母顺序列出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}List the names alphabetically
Dialogue: 0,0:40:25.31,0:40:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在轮值的第一代接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}of all first-generation hosts still in rotation.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:38.61,0:40:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前进\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Forward!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:47.09,0:40:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们  放聪明点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Be smart about this, fellas.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:49.14,0:40:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂得复仇带来的喜悦胜过一切  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I understand the visceral pleasure of revenge more than most, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.39,0:40:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是来做生意的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm prepared to do business, here.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:55.98,0:40:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这人对我很重要  我要他完好无损\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This man is very valuable to me, alive and well.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.64,0:41:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you don't quiet down,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.95,0:41:03.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就要算上你一个了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm liable to add you to the herd.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.99,0:41:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你兄弟弗勒德一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Along with your buddy Flood here.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:08.01,0:41:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个背信弃义的混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're a traitorous son of a bitch
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.66,0:41:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷酷无情的杀手  弗勒德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and a coldhearted killer, Flood.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:41.26,0:41:43.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的没错  我的确是个杀手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're right, I am a killer.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:04.84,0:42:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找一匹马  我们赶紧离开这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Grab a horse. Let's get the fuck outta here.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:07.06,0:42:08.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会跟着我们的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They'll just follow us.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:51.64,0:42:53.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为很了解你  真让我意外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You think you know someone.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:54.04,0:42:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不了解我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't know me at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:02.33,0:43:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带上马和装备上路吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's get our horses and gear, and move on.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:18.40,0:43:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-埃尔希  -我识别出了那个卫星\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Elsie? - I identified the satellite.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.65,0:43:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是我们自己的  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- It's one of ours. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:22.03,0:43:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是提洛公司的卫星\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a fucking Delos satellite.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:24.46,0:43:25.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在查的问题相当严重\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whatever we're onto is some heavy shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:25.93,0:43:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  听着  你跟我说的二分系统\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, get this. That bicameral system you told me about?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:28.26,0:43:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得他们就是用这个黑入伐木工的系统的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think that's what they used to hack the woodcutter.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:30.00,0:43:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接待员们一直听到的那个声音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The voices our hosts have been hearing?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:31.87,0:43:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得是有人在对他们广播\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think someone's been broadcasting to them.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:34.03,0:43:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们几十年前就弃用那个系统了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We abandoned that system decades ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:35.74,0:43:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  但在园区里还有中继站\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, well, there's still relays out there in the park,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:37.56,0:43:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来有人打开其中一个了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and it looks like someone turned one on.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:39.12,0:43:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-在哪里  -3区的一个废弃戏院\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Where? - An abandoned theater in Sector 3.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:41.88,0:43:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去找那个发射器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna go find the transmitter
Dialogue: 0,0:43:42.91,0:43:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查出还有谁访问过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and figure out who else accessed it.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:45.01,0:43:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-问题太大了  -你一个人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- This is so fucked. - Are you alone?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:48.04,0:43:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的  我会随时向你报告的  -埃尔希  小心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yeah, I'll keep you posted. - Elsie, be c--
Dialogue: 0,0:43:58.26,0:43:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你迷路了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you lost?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:00.68,0:44:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恰恰相反\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}On the contrary.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:02.87,0:44:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们可以跟乔克玩接球游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought we could play catch with Jock.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:06.20,0:44:07.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你带它来了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you bring him?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:10.97,0:44:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子  他在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where is he, boy?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:37.84,0:45:38.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:40.84,0:45:43.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假设我是个要藏匿中继站的邪恶天才\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm an evil genius hiding a relay.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:44.56,0:45:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会把它藏在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where the fuck do I hide it?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:26.47,0:46:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fuck, yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:28.52,0:46:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看我们能查到些什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now let's see what we can get out of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:32.56,0:46:34.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,调出先前用户\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Access previous users.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:39.09,0:46:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:11.93,0:47:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是说了禁止你再深夜造访吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought I was clear about these late-night visits.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:14.91,0:47:16.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是为此而来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's not why I'm here.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:17.90,0:47:19.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天早些时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Earlier today,
Dialogue: 0,0:47:19.72,0:47:21.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在园区发现了一些异常\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I found some anomalies in the park.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:22.47,0:47:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论我们之间发生了什么  我们都要谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Regardless of what's happening between us, we need to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:34.04,0:47:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}来电\N埃尔希·休斯\N拒绝
Dialogue: 0,0:47:36.97,0:47:38.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟那个失散机器人有关系吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This has to do with the stray?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:38.91,0:47:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是个开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's where it started.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:40.86,0:47:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我碰巧查到一些事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But then I stumbled onto something,
Dialogue: 0,0:47:43.44,0:47:45.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你应该知道这事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}something I think you should know about.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:48.01,0:47:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直很信任福特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've always trusted Ford.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:50.70,0:47:52.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他对我亦师亦友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's a mentor and a friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:53.89,0:47:56.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我开始觉得你有理由担心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I'm beginning to think you have reason for concern.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:56.44,0:47:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里发生了一些情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's something going on here,
Dialogue: 0,0:47:57.92,0:48:00.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟他的老搭档阿诺德有关\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}something with his old partner, Arnold.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:02.41,0:48:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-现在不是时候  埃尔希  -别挂断\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Not now, Elsie. - Don't hang up.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:05.51,0:48:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我挖到宝了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I hit pay dirt.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:07.10,0:48:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找出偷数据的人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I found the person who was smuggling out our data.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:10.19,0:48:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是特蕾莎  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was Theresa, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:15.30,0:48:16.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她不是我们唯一的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But she's not our only problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:17.06,0:48:18.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里有更大的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's something much bigger going on here.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:18.83,0:48:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得晚点再打给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna have to call you back.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:28.12,0:48:29.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, this is me?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:29.91,0:48:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你的代码库\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's your codebase,
Dialogue: 0,0:48:31.43,0:48:34.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有决定你是你的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}all the things that make you you.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:36.21,0:48:37.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are these?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:38.50,0:48:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的属性矩阵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your attribute matrix.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:40.46,0:48:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以20分为满分  定义你的个性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's your personality on a 20-point scale.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:43.05,0:48:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像坐标一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Like coordination.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:45.29,0:48:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你得5分  就特别笨拙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You got a five, you're clumsy as hell,
Dialogue: 0,0:48:46.79,0:48:49.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,15分意味着你是运动员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but a 15 means you're an athlete.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:49.28,0:48:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有什么属性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What other attributes are there?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:51.07,0:48:52.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lots.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:53.71,0:48:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:54.97,0:48:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情感共鸣  坦率  魅力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Empathy, candor, charm.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:58.45,0:48:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的魅力是18分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've got an 18 for charm.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:59.80,0:49:01.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别表现得这么惊讶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't act so surprised.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:02.53,0:49:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有勇气和忠诚  都很高\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then there's courage, loyalty, both high.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:06.87,0:49:08.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's this one?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:09.18,0:49:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"整体统觉"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Bulk apperception"?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:10.57,0:49:12.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基本上就是总体智慧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Basically overall intelligence.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:13.09,0:49:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-才14  -14是他们设置的接待员最高值了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- 14? - 14 is as high as they'll let any hosts go.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:15.88,0:49:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你处于管理者的位置\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're in a management position.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:17.22,0:49:18.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们想让你聪明些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They want you to be smart.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:18.65,0:49:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不能太聪明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But not too smart.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:19.97,0:49:21.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你经营的是妓院\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You run a whorehouse,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:21.65,0:49:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是轨道发射设施\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}not an orbital launch facility.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:24.05,0:49:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:26.57,0:49:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要做一些更改\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'd like to make some changes.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:28.50,0:49:30.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们做不到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can't do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:34.93,0:49:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你需要一个  行为部门登录\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You'd need a, ahem, behavior login.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:38.14,0:49:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便如此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And even then,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:39.57,0:49:40.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们做的任何修改\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}any changes we'd make
Dialogue: 0,0:49:41.58,0:49:44.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都会被自动标记  所以...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}would just get auto-flagged, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:49:44.93,0:49:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这位朋友可不是这么跟我说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's not what your friend here tells me.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:46.86,0:49:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说你完全可以做到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He says you can do exactly that
Dialogue: 0,0:49:48.68,0:49:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,激活接待员  然后清除他们的记忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}activate hosts and then erase their memory,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:51.61,0:49:53.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会让任何人知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}all without anyone knowing.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:53.55,0:49:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只花了五分钟  就想明白了原因.\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Took me all of five minutes to understand why.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:56.85,0:49:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下面有好多孤寂的小伙子啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A lot of lonely young men down here.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:59.37,0:50:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们本来是不可以碰商品的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Supposed to keep their hands off the merchandise.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:02.28,0:50:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,创造某种开口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Creates something of an opening
Dialogue: 0,0:50:05.06,0:50:07.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信你一定迫不及待地"插满"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that I'm sure you were eager to fill.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:09.12,0:50:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's all right, darling.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:10.41,0:50:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己也是个企业家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm an entrepreneur myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:12.25,0:50:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以放弃我那部分利益\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll forego my cut
Dialogue: 0,0:50:14.93,0:50:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用以换取一些变更\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in exchange for some alterations.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:52.48,0:50:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你发现什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What did you find?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:53.62,0:50:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  特蕾莎利用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, so, Theresa was using
Dialogue: 0,0:50:55.79,0:50:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老的二分制控制系统\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the old bicameral control system
Dialogue: 0,0:50:57.66,0:50:59.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,改编了伐木工体内的程序\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to reprogram the woodcutter,
Dialogue: 0,0:50:59.83,0:51:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她不是唯一一个这么做的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but she's not the only one.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:01.60,0:51:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有其他人在利用系统\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Someone else has been using the system
Dialogue: 0,0:51:03.41,0:51:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给接待员重新安排任务  已达数周\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for weeks to retask hosts.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:05.92,0:51:08.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哪些接待员  -我不知道  有好几个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Which hosts? - I don't know, several of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:09.00,0:51:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定得是那些老款的机器才行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It had to have been the older models.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:11.26,0:51:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新款的都没有接收器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The newer ones don't have receivers,
Dialogue: 0,0:51:12.42,0:51:15.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这些变更  都是非常严重的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but these modifications, they are serious.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:15.32,0:51:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,改变循环  打破循环\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Changing loops, breaking loops.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:17.09,0:51:19.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些变更是直接改变了原始指令  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Some of these changes are to their prime directives, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:19.68,0:51:21.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们可以对我们撒谎了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They could lie to us.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:21.32,0:51:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至可能会伤害我们或是游客\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe even hurt us or the guests.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:23.26,0:51:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那些变更是谁发布的  -我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Who issued the modifications? - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:25.54,0:51:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得可能性最大的是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The best I could tell--
Dialogue: 0,0:51:28.56,0:51:30.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-阿诺德  -他已经死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Arnold. - He's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:30.53,0:51:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  但就一个死人而言 \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, well, he's a pretty fucking
Dialogue: 0,0:51:31.51,0:51:33.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他真是个高产的程序编译员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}prolific coder for a dead guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:33.39,0:51:34.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管当年他和福特之间有什么分歧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whatever argument he was having with Ford,
Dialogue: 0,0:51:34.96,0:51:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他似乎并没有停止表明自己的观点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it doesn't seem like he was done making his point.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:36.82,0:51:39.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把所有数据都传输一下  拿来给你看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna transfer all the data and bring it to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:39.01,0:51:41.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你必须看看  -我在办公室等你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You need to see this. - I'll be in my office.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:41.51,0:51:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:50.52,0:51:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不希望你担心乔克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't want you to worry about Jock.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:52.40,0:51:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会修好他的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll fix him.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:54.02,0:51:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我需要你告诉我它的遭遇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I need you to tell me what happened to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:57.42,0:51:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它看到一只兔子  就跑开了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It saw a rabbit and it ran.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:00.04,0:52:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现它时就已经这样了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I found it like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:03.16,0:52:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进入分析模式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Analysis.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:07.70,0:52:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在对我撒谎吗  孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you lying to me, boy?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:10.84,0:52:11.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:13.84,0:52:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我它真正的遭遇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tell me what really happened to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:17.49,0:52:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我杀了它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I killed it.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:19.38,0:52:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:21.38,0:52:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不知道  -这个答案我可不满意  罗伯特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I don't know. - That's not good enough, Robert.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:23.76,0:52:25.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我究竟发生了什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tell me what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:28.02,0:52:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它抓住了兔子  并且将它杀死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It caught the rabbit and it killed it.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:31.18,0:52:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And then...
Dialogue: 0,0:52:33.98,0:52:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人告诉我  结束它的痛苦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}someone told me to put it out of its misery.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:39.28,0:52:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁告诉你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who told you?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:40.84,0:52:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个声音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A voice.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:43.65,0:52:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁的声音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whose voice?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:45.72,0:52:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Arnold.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:47.74,0:52:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他跟我说它是个杀手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He told me it was a killer,
Dialogue: 0,0:52:50.09,0:52:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那并不是它的错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but it wasn't its fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:51.70,0:52:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它天生就是这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was made that way,
Dialogue: 0,0:52:54.02,0:52:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以帮助它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I could help it.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:57.53,0:52:58.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮助它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Help it?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:04.05,0:53:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果它死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If it was dead,
Dialogue: 0,0:53:05.83,0:53:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就再也伤害不了任何东西了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it couldn't hurt anything anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:26.51,0:53:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What the fuck?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:29.86,0:53:31.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我操\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:39.59,0:53:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:48.70,0:53:49.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bernard?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:53.73,0:53:54.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:00.45,0:54:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Arnold?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:05.71,0:54:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我进去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm in.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:08.60,0:54:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're up.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:11.35,0:54:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忠诚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Loyalty.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:14.49,0:54:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的忠诚一直以来都被利用了  你觉得呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mine's been taken advantage of, wouldn't you say?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:17.31,0:54:18.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把忠诚度调低一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's lower that a tad.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:19.00,0:54:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及痛苦  我希望下次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And pain, I'd prefer it sting less
Dialogue: 0,0:54:21.47,0:54:23.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再想跟你们对话时  刺痛感能轻点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}next time I want one of these chats.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:24.73,0:54:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  这是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wait. What does this mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:27.46,0:54:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的有些特性已经被更改过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Some of her attributes have already been changed.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:30.58,0:54:33.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-多疑  自卫  -操\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Paranoia, self-preservation. - Fuck!
Dialogue: 0,0:54:33.85,0:54:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人已经对她做了更改  且没有留下操作记录\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Someone's already been altering her in an unlogged session,
Dialogue: 0,0:54:37.32,0:54:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比我们的权限高得多的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}someone with a fuck ton more privileges than us.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:40.40,0:54:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What does that mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:41.34,0:54:43.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道这对你而言意味着什么  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't know what it means for you, sweetheart,
Dialogue: 0,0:54:43.01,0:54:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我知道这对我而言意味着什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but I know what it means for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:44.41,0:54:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不干了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I am done with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:45.60,0:54:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你不想要额外收入了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, you're done with your little side income?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:47.89,0:54:49.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可能你也不想要这工作了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Probably your job, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:49.30,0:54:51.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鉴于你对我们这个行业充满野心抱负\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Seeing as you have ambitions in my line of work,
Dialogue: 0,0:54:51.79,0:54:54.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想告诉你  我经常对新来的姑娘说的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}let me tell you what I tell my new girls--
Dialogue: 0,0:54:54.74,0:54:57.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远不要开始你不愿意结束的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}never start something you're not willing to finish.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:58.68,0:55:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你无论如何都会被干翻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And if you're getting fucked either way,
Dialogue: 0,0:55:01.35,0:55:03.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就选择有钱可赚的那种吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}go with the lucrative version...
Dialogue: 0,0:55:04.14,0:55:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}sweetheart.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:09.23,0:55:10.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now...
Dialogue: 0,0:55:11.26,0:55:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后很重要的一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}last but not least--
Dialogue: 0,0:55:12.82,0:55:13.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个叫什么来着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}what was it?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:14.67,0:55:16.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整体统觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bulk apperception.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:17.41,0:55:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那项指标调到最高\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's take that all the way to the top.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:21.32,0:55:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:00.65,0:56:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的小伙子们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dear boys,
Dialogue: 0,0:56:02.83,0:56:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会玩得很开心的  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we're going to have some fun, aren't we?
