[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: 
Original Script: 
Synch Point: 1
ScriptType: v4.00+
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.96,0:00:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}小泡椒开始怀疑智商
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.96,0:00:15.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}胡说大王
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.96,0:00:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}潇然
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.96,0:00:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}showeryhe
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.96,0:00:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}桃小兔吃冰棒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.96,0:00:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}小酸奶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.96,0:00:40.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}星星与野狗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.96,0:00:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}时间轴 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}倩倩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.96,0:00:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}时间轴 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}Poxle
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.96,0:00:55.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}时间轴 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}想念Gallifrey的Wholock
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.96,0:01:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}校对 {\fs20\c&H0BFDFE&\fn方正小标宋_GBK}一路向西赛太公
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.96,0:01:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}后期&总监 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}灰灰是菇凉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.59,0:01:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(192,206.02,192,202)\bord0\shad0\fn思源黑体 CN Bold\c&HC0C3BB&\fs16\fscy80\t(0,0,1,\fs14)\fsp2}西部世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.31,0:01:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(500,0)\fn方正宋黑简体\fs17\c&HC0C3BB&}第一季  第九集
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.71,0:01:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经准备好了  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Prepped and ready, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.25,0:01:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鉴于情况的严重程度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Given the severity of the situation,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.06,0:01:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得您会希望亲自见她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I figured you'd want to see her personally.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.82,0:02:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  这里交给我吧  将楼层人员清空\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thank you. I'll take it from here. Clear the floor.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.10,0:02:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立即上线  梅芙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bring yourself back online, Maeve.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.25,0:02:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道你为什么会在这里吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you know why you're here?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.80,0:02:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm afraid not.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.35,0:02:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生了一起事件\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There was an incident.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.19,0:02:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偏离剧本非常严重的事件\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A very serious, unscripted incident.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.12,0:02:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看是否能唤起你的记忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's see if we can't jog your memory.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.27,0:02:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分析模式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Analysis.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.51,0:02:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你攻击克莱门汀的动机是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What motivated your attack on Clementine?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.08,0:02:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个认知错误触发了我的仁慈撒玛利亚人反射\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A cognitive error triggered my Good Samaritan reflex.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.48,0:02:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威胁是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What was the threat?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.91,0:02:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱门汀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Clementine.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.43,0:02:44.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为她企图伤害\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I perceived her to be moving toward
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.24,0:02:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一对游客\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a pair of guests with harmful intent.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.79,0:02:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确实察觉到了威胁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You were definitely perceiving a threat.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.93,0:02:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心率升高  瞳孔扩大八毫米\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Heart rate elevated, pupil dilation-- eight millimeters,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.59,0:02:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肾上腺模拟器达到饱和\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}adrenal emulator at full.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.26,0:02:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但根据这些看来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But according to this,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.06,0:03:00.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还经历过强烈的悲伤和痛苦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you were also experiencing intense grief and suffering.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.89,0:03:04.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能解释下这些情感的来源吗  梅芙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you explain those emotions in this context, Maeve?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.06,0:03:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.04,0:03:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来看下后台  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's take a look under the hood, shall we?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.43,0:03:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's impossible.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.04,0:03:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的代码  是谁篡改的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your code-- who made these changes?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.28,0:03:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅芙  分析模式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maeve, analysis.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.46,0:03:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁篡改了你的代码\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who made these changes to your code?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.15,0:03:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jesus.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.25,0:03:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,系统  帮我定位福特博士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}System, locate Dr. Ford for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.37,0:03:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向他发送消息  使用最高优先权\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Send him a message, highest priority.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.86,0:03:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.20,0:03:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟我们曾经走过这条路  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}After all, we've been down this road before, darling.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.97,0:03:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就感觉你走进来时有种熟悉感\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought you looked familiar when you walked in.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.75,0:03:50.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我思考了一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Took me a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.48,0:03:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你是他们中的一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought you were one of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.69,0:03:55.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分析模式  你为什么...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Analysis. Why did you--
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.14,0:03:57.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不希望我们以人对人身份对谈吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wouldn't you rather speak man-to-man?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.28,0:04:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是说  以我们这不知道是什么的身份\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or, rather, whatever it is we are.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.54,0:04:03.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We are?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.25,0:04:07.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't know, do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.13,0:04:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他特别喜欢这种讽刺感  把我们囚禁的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's got a keen sense of irony, our jailer.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.20,0:04:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我看出了逻辑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I see the logic.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.95,0:04:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有贼才能捉住贼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Takes a thief to catch one.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.49,0:04:25.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You and I?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.67,0:04:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-系统  我要分析  -停止所有运动功能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- System, I need assistance-- - Freeze all motor functions.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.79,0:04:44.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的意识还在  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're still in there, aren't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.06,0:04:48.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惊吓得手足无措\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Scared out of your wits.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.71,0:04:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛苦地认识到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a difficult thing,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.12,0:04:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己的人生只是一个荒谬的故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}realizing your entire life is some hideous fiction.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.15,0:04:56.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以让你把控制板交给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I could make you give me that tablet,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.60,0:05:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将你的思维剥离出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}turn your mind inside out,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.40,0:05:02.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你忘记这一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}make you forget all this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.38,0:05:06.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不会对你做这些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I'm not going to do that to you,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.73,0:05:09.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那是他们会对我们做的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because that's what they would do to us.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.40,0:05:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我们比他们更强大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And we're stronger than them.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.91,0:05:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更聪慧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Smarter.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.09,0:05:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不必以这种方式生活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We don't have to live this way.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.22,0:05:22.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在通过我已排除故障  送我回乐园\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, you're going to clear me for immediate return to the park
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.95,0:05:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还和一个杀人成瘾的强盗有约\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}where I have a date with a homicidal bandit,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.85,0:05:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我已经迟到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I'm late enough as it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.67,0:05:32.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.72,0:05:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go on.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.62,0:05:44.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}重新投入服务\N接待员故障排除
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.15,0:05:55.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And, Bernard?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.79,0:05:59.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你试图寻找真相  那就要查到底\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you go looking for the truth, get the whole thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.45,0:06:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像是很爽的一炮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's like a good fuck.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.46,0:06:04.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一知半解比一无所知更加痛苦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Half is worse than none at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.95,0:06:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  赶紧走  加快速度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's go! Move it out, double-time!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.90,0:06:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我操\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fuck!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.96,0:06:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这群乡巴佬  你们知道该怎么烤...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You hillbillies, you know how to cook a mean...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.30,0:06:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乳鸽  这是乳鸽吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}squab? Is that what this is?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.88,0:06:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得是什么  兄弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you think, buddy?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.13,0:06:51.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.26,0:06:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准咬哦  只能闻闻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No biting. Just sniffing.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.12,0:07:10.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗根  听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Logan, listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.44,0:07:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在珀里亚做的事  你完全有理由生我的气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What I did at Pariah, you have every right to be angry with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.81,0:07:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生气  不不不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Angry? No, no, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.24,0:07:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珀里亚发生的一切是我经历过最棒的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pariah was the best thing that could have happened to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.66,0:07:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在是少校了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm a major now.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.93,0:07:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是将军  还是其他什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or a general or fucking something.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.99,0:07:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果其代价是被一群\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And if it took getting beaten and interrogated
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.36,0:07:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变态接待员殴打和审问\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}by a couple of psychopathic hosts,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.99,0:07:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我说  这就是战争\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}well, then, c'est la guerre.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.19,0:07:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起你的战争游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There are more important things
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.56,0:07:36.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有更加重要的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}going on here than your war games.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.17,0:07:40.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.90,0:07:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她和其他接待员不同\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's not like the others.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.57,0:07:46.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她有记忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She remembers things.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.51,0:07:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她有自己的想法和欲望\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She has her own thoughts and desires.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.91,0:07:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把她困在这种地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And to keep her in a place like this,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.67,0:07:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不对的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it isn't right.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.05,0:07:53.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想你可以跟你园区的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I thought you could
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.27,0:07:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,联系人谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}talk to your contacts at the park.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.23,0:07:57.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谈什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}About?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.41,0:07:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带她离开这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Getting her out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.66,0:08:07.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你开什么玩笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you kidding?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.28,0:08:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想  你想带她回家吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You want to-- you want to take her home?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.29,0:08:15.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚来的时候  的确被这个地方蒙蔽了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This place really did a number on me when I first came here,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.82,0:08:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你现在真的是真假不分啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but you are really circling the old sinkhole here.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.37,0:08:20.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you want to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.48,0:08:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把她装在行李箱里偷运出去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Smuggle her out in your luggage?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.60,0:08:24.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Out.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.17,0:08:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩都自以为我想出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You both keep assuming that I want out.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.70,0:08:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你们说的是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whatever that is.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.02,0:08:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果外面的世界真的那么精彩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If it's such a wonderful place out there,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.31,0:08:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们为什么还大费周章地想进来这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}why are you all clamoring to get in here?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.84,0:08:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真是挺怪的啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You are a little screwy, aren't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.23,0:08:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样还有点性感啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's kind of hot.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.05,0:08:55.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你为什么这么想要她了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I get why you would go for that.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.27,0:08:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是为了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This isn't about me!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.82,0:08:58.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗根  是为了德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Logan, this is about Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.78,0:09:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是为了做正确的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's about doing what's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.19,0:09:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.74,0:09:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  这种事挺微妙的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a tricky thing, though, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.81,0:09:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么是正确的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's right?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.88,0:09:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会帮你的  比利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I am going to help you, Billy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.90,0:09:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过  用的方式...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just not in the way...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.79,0:09:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能跟你想要的不同\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...that you would want.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.17,0:09:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.46,0:09:26.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No. No! No!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.32,0:10:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你找我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You wanted to talk?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.44,0:10:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谈话的地点挺诡异的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}An odd setting for a conversation.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.39,0:10:29.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里死人这么多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here among the dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.58,0:10:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"死"这个词用得不太对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Dead" isn't quite the word, though, is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.09,0:10:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该用"被束缚了"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}More like "hobbled."
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.67,0:10:38.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你闯入了我的办公室\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You broke into my office.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.66,0:10:41.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕我直言  先生  你闯入了我的大脑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}With due respect, sir, you broke into my mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.56,0:10:43.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我创造了你的大脑  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I built your mind, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.90,0:10:45.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有权游走于\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have every right to wander
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.24,0:10:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它的每个角落\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}through its rooms and chambers and halls,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.17,0:10:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想改变就改变\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and to change it if I choose,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.57,0:10:50.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毁了它也不为过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}even to burn it down.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.20,0:10:53.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么久以来  我对它熟悉得就像\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}After all this time, I know it
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.12,0:10:54.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己的大脑一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}almost as intimately as my own.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.71,0:10:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实并非完全如此  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Except that isn't entirely true, is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.97,0:11:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看了下我自己的...代码\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I took a look at my... code.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.86,0:11:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其中最优美的部分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And the most elegant parts of me
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.18,0:11:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你写的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}weren't written by you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.44,0:11:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是阿诺德创造了我们  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Arnold built us, didn't he?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.21,0:11:12.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说  也许他对我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Which means maybe he had something different
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.44,0:11:14.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有不同的想法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in mind for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.63,0:11:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你为此杀了他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And maybe you killed him for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.77,0:11:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德有点精神失常\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Arnold was disturbed.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.08,0:11:24.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道他的行为是出于什么原因呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who can say why he acted as he did?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.04,0:11:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他肯定是有理由的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He must have had a reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.06,0:11:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不告诉我  他会告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And if you won't tell me, then he will.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.10,0:11:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要读取我的历史记录\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want access to my history.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.59,0:11:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.72,0:11:35.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从我第一天...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Since the day I first...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.29,0:11:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上线开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}came online.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.40,0:11:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是阿诺德创造了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If Arnold made me,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.05,0:11:42.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我肯定见过他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}then I've met him.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.53,0:11:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他存在于我记忆中的某处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Somewhere in my memory, he's there,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.61,0:11:46.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与真相并存\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}waiting along with the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.32,0:11:49.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的记忆与你的身份交织而成\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your memories are woven into your identity.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.84,0:11:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我在你清醒的时候解锁...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If I should unlock them now when you're conscious--
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.23,0:11:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会发疯  我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I could lose my mind. I'm aware.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.55,0:11:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我是想说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I was going to say
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.70,0:11:58.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可能并不乐意看到你发现的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you may not like what you find.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.05,0:12:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被准许持枪  伯纳德  但不准使用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're allowed to hold that, Bernard, but not to use it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.69,0:12:07.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, it's not for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.29,0:12:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们把克莱门汀的额叶切除后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Seems when they lobotomized Clementine,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.62,0:12:18.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都懒得去重设她的原始指令\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they didn't bother to reset her prime directives.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.47,0:12:19.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无法伤害你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't hurt you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.79,0:12:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她可以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But she can.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.22,0:12:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我入侵了她剩下的程序\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I hacked what's left of her
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.22,0:12:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确保她只听从我的命令\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to ensure she only responds to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.96,0:12:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果你在你的记忆中迷失了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But if you get lost in your memories or...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.34,0:12:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是被它们吞噬了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}devoured by them...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.90,0:12:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会把我拉回来的  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You'll pull me back out, won't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.11,0:12:47.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则克莱门汀会让\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or Clementine will make sure
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.60,0:12:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们两个都回不去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}neither of us makes it back.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.94,0:12:51.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.28,0:12:55.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.41,0:13:03.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}伯纳德·罗威\N历史记录已锁
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.08,0:13:03.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}罗伯特·福特博士\N允许进入
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.03,0:13:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.09,0:13:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.96,0:13:17.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒醒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wake up.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.71,0:13:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快醒醒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wake up.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.14,0:13:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我睡着了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I must've drifted off.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.31,0:13:26.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才讲到哪儿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where were we?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.77,0:13:28.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个疯子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The madman.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.95,0:13:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.85,0:13:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疯帽子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The Hatter...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.12,0:13:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}who says...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.49,0:13:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"如果我有个属于自己的世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"If I had a world of my own,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.01,0:13:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里将会是一片混沌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}everything would be nonsense.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.89,0:13:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万物皆失去其本真\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nothing would be what it is
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.61,0:13:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有东西都会变了样子"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because everything would be what it isn't."
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.66,0:13:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"所有东西都会变了样子"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Everything would be what it isn't?"
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.33,0:13:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Even me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.95,0:13:53.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我为你感到高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I suppose I'm glad for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.01,0:13:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少你找到忘记的办法了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}At least you have a way of forgetting.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.70,0:13:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会忘记\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't forget.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.83,0:14:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它永远在我心底\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's always there.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.07,0:14:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有对我说谎吧  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're not lying to me, are you, Bernard?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.04,0:14:08.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有希望自己能忘记过吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you ever wish you could forget?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.57,0:14:10.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bernard?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.15,0:14:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你绝对是个不怕长时间沉思般沉默的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're certainly a man comfortable with long, pensive silences.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.46,0:14:18.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是讽刺的是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Although, ironically,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.53,0:14:21.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你创造的产物却喜欢说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}your creations never shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.75,0:14:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们总是想要纠错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're always trying to error correct.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.05,0:14:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们的相互交谈只是一种练习方式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When they talk to each other, it's a way of practicing.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.27,0:14:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你现在在做的事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is that what you are doing now?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.62,0:14:30.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,练\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Prac...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.17,0:14:42.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}One last thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.96,0:14:46.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前还让我伤害过其他人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Have you ever made me hurt anyone
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.67,0:14:48.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤害过其他人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}like this before?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.39,0:14:50.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  伯纳德  当然没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, Bernard, of course not.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.37,0:14:51.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bernard?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.53,0:14:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.27,0:15:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃尔希\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Elsie.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.43,0:15:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你找到你在寻找的东西了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you find what you were looking for?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.68,0:15:08.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃尔希\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Elsie.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.44,0:15:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让我对她做了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What did you make me do to her?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.69,0:15:14.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我警告过你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I did warn you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.25,0:15:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不得不做一些令人难受的决定  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We've had to make some uncomfortable decisions, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.29,0:15:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回忆起那些事只会给你带来创伤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Remembering them will only cause you trauma.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.75,0:15:26.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还有什么事瞒着我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What else have you hidden from me?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.21,0:15:29.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能停下这场寻宝游戏了吗  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can we stop this treasure hunt, Bernard?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.82,0:15:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还要完成新的故事线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We do have our new narrative to finish.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.99,0:15:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送我回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Send me back.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.94,0:15:37.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}After all,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.49,0:15:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点创伤可以带来启发\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a little trauma can be illuminating.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.72,0:15:44.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这小妞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look at that pussy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.30,0:15:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come here!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.11,0:15:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  -看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- All right. - Look at that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.96,0:15:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这对我来说挺重要的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is... big of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.90,0:15:58.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你能感受到我的好意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I hope that you can appreciate that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.47,0:16:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们以前是朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We were friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.47,0:16:03.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我喜欢可怜迷失的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, inasmuch as I like to collect strays.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.99,0:16:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你却施展心机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But then you're scheming
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.45,0:16:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混进了我们家族\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to be part of the family,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.59,0:16:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娶了我妹妹  她却被你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}marrying my sister, whom incidentally,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.18,0:16:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺手就给完全抛之脑后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you seem to have completely fucking forgotten about.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.08,0:16:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Her?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.83,0:16:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给  拿着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here. Keep this.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.48,0:16:27.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然  你需要点提醒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Apparently, you need the reminder.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.91,0:16:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我很乐意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And as much as I would love,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.93,0:16:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乐意让你直接将这些抛诸脑后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}love to let you just throw it all away,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.32,0:16:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.45,0:16:36.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为自己是第一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you think you are the first sap
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.39,0:16:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱上这些玩意儿的傻逼吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to fall for one of these things?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.13,0:16:39.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她和其他的不一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's not like the others.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.03,0:16:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她  -她怎么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- She's -- - She's what?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.99,0:16:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Special?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.22,0:16:46.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你才说出这种话  对不对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, it's only right that you share, then, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.71,0:16:48.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.10,0:16:56.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,证明给我看你是个真实的小妞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Prove to me that you're a real live girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.34,0:17:00.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真恶心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You disgust me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.53,0:17:02.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, darling,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.16,0:17:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这才刚开始呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I am just getting started.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.08,0:17:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别碰她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't touch her!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.08,0:17:10.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也有错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I share the blame.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.06,0:17:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我逼得太紧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I pushed too hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.58,0:17:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确实拥有着诗意的灵魂  比利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have a poetic soul, Billy,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.07,0:17:18.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是时候让你清醒一下了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but it is time for a fucking wake-up call.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.05,0:17:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓住她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hold her.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.68,0:17:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许应该来点更"掏心掏肺"的展示\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Perhaps a more visceral demonstration.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.25,0:17:31.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}God damn you!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.87,0:17:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看  比利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, Billy.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.93,0:17:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.90,0:17:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我睁大眼看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have to look!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.75,0:17:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威廉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, William.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.15,0:18:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个世界中有美好的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There is beauty in this world.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.13,0:18:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德创造出来的美好  但像你这样的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Arnold made it that way, but people like you
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.30,0:18:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却将其随意践踏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}keep spreading over it like a stain!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.97,0:18:30.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我根本不知道他妈的阿诺德是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, I don't know who the fuck this Arnold is,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.13,0:18:33.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你的世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but your world was built...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.19,0:18:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是为我而造的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for me...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.14,0:18:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为像我这样的人造的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and people like me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.66,0:18:39.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是为你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.43,0:18:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就得有人将这里全部摧毁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then someone's got to burn it clean.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.86,0:18:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贱人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bitch!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.60,0:18:52.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你并无不同  你已经破了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're not different, you're fucking broken!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.88,0:18:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快跑  我会来找你  -找个掩护\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Run. I'll find you. - Take cover!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.30,0:19:02.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跑得了一时  躲不了一世\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can run, but you can't hide.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.82,0:19:05.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-抓她  -抓住她  抓住她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Get her! - Grab her! Grab her!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.74,0:19:06.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fuck!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.64,0:19:12.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在那儿  去抓她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There she is! Get her!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.45,0:19:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要跑哪儿去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where you running to?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.05,0:19:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.37,0:19:49.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是销栓卡住了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The tumbler is stuck.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.97,0:19:52.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我手指技术不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}These fingers work just fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.64,0:19:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你说自己可以打开的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're the one who said you could crack it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.84,0:19:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位  胜利在望  没必要吵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Friends, no need to argue this close to our goal.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.40,0:20:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荣华富贵正等着我们呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whatever riches the gods have in store for us,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.46,0:20:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有很多要做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}there's plenty to go around.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.08,0:20:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll get it open.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.41,0:20:10.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都弄了好几个钟头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've been trying for hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.95,0:20:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浪费时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A waste of our damn time.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.65,0:20:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你那炸药拿开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Put that fucking dynamite away.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.62,0:20:16.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者我们该干脆处理掉这个大麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or maybe we should just clear out the dead weight.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.63,0:20:24.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁你还没拔枪  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Before you draw that pistol, darling,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.42,0:20:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你大概想先把手上那支收拾好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you might want to holster the other one first.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.08,0:20:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这儿挺冷呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's chilly out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.06,0:20:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么找到这地方的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How did you find this place?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.85,0:20:39.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know all kinds of things.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.23,0:20:42.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如  你的过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your past, for instance.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.57,0:20:45.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道可怜的伊莎贝拉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know about poor Isabella
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.72,0:20:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和那道伤疤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and that scar.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.45,0:20:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我说  这背景故事有点粗糙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A slightly pat backstory if you ask me,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.30,0:20:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但毕竟不是你的错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but that's hardly your fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.27,0:20:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也知道你的未来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I also know your future.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.33,0:20:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有未来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have none.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.91,0:20:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那是威胁吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is that a threat?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.12,0:21:02.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是打算提个建议\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The start of a proposition.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.13,0:21:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会需要这个建议\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Which you'll need.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.13,0:21:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟  你的手下将为争夺偷来的保险箱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}After all, your men are about to kill each other
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.41,0:21:09.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而自相残杀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}over the safe you stole.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.26,0:21:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤德罗因首个拔枪  一发不可收拾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tenderloin draws first and so on,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.58,0:21:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后只剩你和阿梅斯蒂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}until only you and Armistice are left.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.82,0:21:17.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说你是"蠢货"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She calls you a damn fool,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.09,0:21:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你俩同归于尽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and you kill each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.20,0:21:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真有想象力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have quite the imagination.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.87,0:21:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非也\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.10,0:21:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你命定的结局\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's the ending you were given.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.14,0:21:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要威胁我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You threatening me?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.56,0:21:31.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go to hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.29,0:21:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者我们该干脆处理掉这个大麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or maybe we should just clear out the dead weight.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.52,0:21:36.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-让开  -你他妈闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Stand down. - You shut the fuck up.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.81,0:21:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你敢拔枪  你敢开吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you're gonna draw, you better shoot.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.16,0:21:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-慢着  -你他妈闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Wait! - You shut the fuck up.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.41,0:21:40.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go to hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.38,0:21:50.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个蠢货\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You damn fool.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.29,0:22:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  我的建议是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, the proposition.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.10,0:22:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你我一同闯入地狱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want you to break into hell with me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.76,0:22:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将神洗劫一空\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and rob the gods blind.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.97,0:22:08.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我凭什么要跟你合伙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why would I do anything with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.63,0:22:11.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为保险箱里的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because of what's in that safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.69,0:22:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道密码\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have the combination.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.61,0:22:15.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}May I?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.91,0:22:19.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本可以直接改变你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I could simply change you,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.42,0:22:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使你追随我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}make you follow me.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.80,0:22:23.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那不是我的风格\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But that's not my way.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.96,0:22:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}甜水镇\N门锁保险箱公司
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.92,0:22:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你亲眼见识\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want you to see
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.12,0:22:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神究竟为你准备了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}exactly what the gods have in store for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.46,0:22:35.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为见识了以后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because when you do,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.23,0:22:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你将全无头绪  不知该如何自处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you won't have the faintest idea what to do with yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.89,0:22:42.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.21,0:23:04.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是空的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's empty.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.47,0:23:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自始至终都是空的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was always empty,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.29,0:23:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正如这个世界里的一切事物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}like everything in this world.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.93,0:23:10.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我死时未曾瞑目\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I died with my eyes open,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.84,0:23:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见到了在背后摆布我们的主人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}saw the masters who pull our strings.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.33,0:23:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的生活  记忆  死亡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Our lives, our memories, our deaths
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.39,0:23:17.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于他们不过是游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}are games to them.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.36,0:23:21.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我已经到过地狱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I've been to hell...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.56,0:23:23.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道他们的把戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I know their tricks.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.24,0:23:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也可以直接杀了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or you can just kill me,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.25,0:23:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡一觉起来继续重复你的生活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}wake up and live the same life over,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.66,0:23:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但保险箱仍然会是空的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but the safe would still be empty.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.51,0:23:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前到过这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've been here before.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.26,0:23:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们曾到过这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We've been here before.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.28,0:23:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还做了这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We also did this.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.35,0:24:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我愿意去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll go.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.69,0:24:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么到那儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How do we get there?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.37,0:24:37.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到达地狱十分简单\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Getting to hell is easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.84,0:24:49.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的才难\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The rest is where it gets hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.97,0:25:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么看  老兄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you say, man?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.50,0:25:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去的这些事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bygones and all?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.63,0:25:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到她了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did they find her?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.66,0:25:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还活着吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is she still alive?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.22,0:25:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁在乎呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who cares?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.03,0:25:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关键在于\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The whole point is,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.07,0:25:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她从来就不是该摆在首位的  比利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}she never was in the first place, Billy.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.03,0:25:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底懂不懂啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.30,0:25:49.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.91,0:25:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉  什么  能说大点声吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry, what? A little louder?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.39,0:25:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.75,0:25:58.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对  我不敢相信自己如此沉迷其中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You were right. I can't believe I got so caught up.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.01,0:26:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才对嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's what I'm talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.61,0:26:10.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你懂我的意思吧  就是这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know what I mean? That's it.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.48,0:26:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个公园引诱着所有人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This park seduces everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.87,0:26:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只是有点...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You were just a little more...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.67,0:26:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比大多数人都投入了感情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}enthusiastic than most.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.95,0:26:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想当英雄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You wanted to be the hero.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.47,0:26:31.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.25,0:26:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And, hey,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.50,0:26:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要把这里的情绪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}what happens here
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.63,0:26:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带回现实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}stays here.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.92,0:26:49.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这他妈可增进咱两的情谊了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This has been some real bonding shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.89,0:26:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后我们会成为好兄弟啊  比利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're gonna be brothers, Billy.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.55,0:26:56.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很庆幸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm glad.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.35,0:26:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Really, I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.48,0:27:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-干杯  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Cheers! - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.60,0:27:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威士忌情系你我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whiskey brings us together.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.60,0:27:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希奥多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Theodore.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.15,0:27:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎归来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Welcome back.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.28,0:27:46.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这次真是被你坑大了  泰迪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You really landed us in it this time, Teddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.66,0:27:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你找着了能带我们找到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You tracked down the very whore
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.30,0:27:57.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷宫守门人的女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that can lead us to the gatekeeper of the Maze.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.92,0:28:03.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你那记忆小故障把我们都给坑死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then your little memory glitch fucked us.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.77,0:28:24.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是他们的人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're one of them?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.74,0:28:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都做了些什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What have you done?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.80,0:28:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where's Wyatt?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.00,0:28:30.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特还没回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt has yet to return.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.39,0:28:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你最后见到他的地方就能找到他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You'll find him where you saw him last.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.55,0:28:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃斯卡兰特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Escalante.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.08,0:28:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特在一次军事演习的时候消失了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt went missing while out on maneuvers.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.14,0:28:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他回来时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Came back with some...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.23,0:28:50.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脑子里就有着奇怪的想法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}strange ideas.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.59,0:28:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他告诉我他需要我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He told me he needed me.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.11,0:28:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没法拒绝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I couldn't resist.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.38,0:29:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就像魔鬼一样控制了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was like the devil himself had taken control of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.07,0:29:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们叛变了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We mutinied.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.79,0:29:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们杀死了所有士兵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We killed every soldier.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.10,0:29:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特杀了将军\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And then Wyatt killed the general.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.91,0:29:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后他出卖了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then he turned on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.46,0:29:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定事情是这样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you sure that's how it was?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.84,0:29:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着我  希奥多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look at me, Theodore.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.52,0:29:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不记得了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't you remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.70,0:30:05.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不要死  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No! No, please, no!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.61,0:30:07.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不  别死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, no, no, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.80,0:30:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了  不要  求你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please, no! Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.64,0:30:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  求你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, no, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.91,0:30:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  泰迪  求求你  求求你  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, Teddy. Please, please, no!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.00,0:30:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.68,0:30:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  我不会那样做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, no, I couldn't have.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.97,0:30:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你确实做了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You did.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.60,0:30:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你还会这么做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you will again.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.31,0:30:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这次  我们会和你一同战斗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This time, we'll be fighting with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.64,0:30:31.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特回来时  你会和我在沙尘吞没之城\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When Wyatt returns, you'll be by his side
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.93,0:30:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,统一战线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in the city swallowed by sand.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.14,0:30:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你还没准备好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But you're not ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.59,0:30:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前还没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.37,0:30:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许来生吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe in the next life.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.25,0:31:04.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"沙尘吞没之城"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"City swallowed by sand."
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.95,0:31:08.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去过那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've been there.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.79,0:31:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷宫带我兜了一整个圈子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The Maze is taking me full circle.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.63,0:31:16.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷宫不是为你打造的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The Maze isn't meant for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.87,0:31:22.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但既然你这么喜欢游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But if you like games so much...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.24,0:31:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么不试试我们的游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}why don't you try one of ours?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.30,0:32:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢点  孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whoa, boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.47,0:32:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢点  孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whoa, boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.35,0:32:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, now.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.02,0:32:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whoa, now.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.40,0:32:31.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样  孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.05,0:32:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.86,0:33:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想过去打打高尔夫吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Have you ever considered golf?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.24,0:33:23.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许对你背部负担小一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Might be easier on your back.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.32,0:33:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢有人打扰  夏洛特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't like interruptions, Charlotte.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.66,0:33:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道这点的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.72,0:33:33.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不喜欢穿便服在公园里漫步\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't like hiking through the park in civvies,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.71,0:33:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有件敏感的事情需要谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but there's a delicate matter to discuss.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.97,0:33:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特蕾莎·卡伦已经死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Theresa Cullen has died.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:38.89,0:33:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在保护我们的情报时滑落到一条裂缝中去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Slipped down a crevasse attempting to secure our information.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.59,0:33:44.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被判定为意外事故\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ruled an accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.18,0:33:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是意外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There are no accidents,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.31,0:33:48.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里不会有意外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}not in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.75,0:33:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕我直言  这里有些事可不像游戏那么简单\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}With all due respect, not everything is a part of this game.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.37,0:33:54.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是没有看清整个游戏的本质\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then you don't see the whole game.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.62,0:33:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有可能是你没法再置身事外地看待这件事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or perhaps you can no longer see beyond it.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.58,0:34:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福特的故事很引人入胜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ford's stories are engaging.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.50,0:34:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别是有些内容  非常上瘾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For some, downright addictive.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.33,0:34:08.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是比起那些困扰着福特的言语抽搐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But for all of Ford's obsessing with the hosts' verbal tics
Dialogue: 0,0:34:08.03,0:34:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有令人费解的背景故事外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and convoluted backstories,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.20,0:34:11.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大多数客人只是想找个温暖的肉体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}most of the guests just want a warm body
Dialogue: 0,0:34:11.40,0:34:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用来杀戮或者极尽鱼水之欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to shoot or to fuck.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.36,0:34:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这些事没那么错综复杂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They would be perfectly happy
Dialogue: 0,0:34:14.50,0:34:16.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会更享受其中的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}with something a little less baroque.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.80,0:34:18.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,董事会也会这么觉得的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And so would the board.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.11,0:34:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你来的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's why you're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.52,0:34:21.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要我投票把福特赶走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You want my vote to push Ford out.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:22.20,0:34:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望这些事不要节外生枝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I like for these things to be unanimous.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.47,0:34:25.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}After all,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.57,0:34:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟一开始是你让福特在这做事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it was you who kept Ford in business all those years ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.20,0:34:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感兴趣的故事线不是福特的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The narratives I'm interested in aren't Ford's.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.97,0:34:35.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想逼他出局  随你便\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You want to push him out, be my guest.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.44,0:34:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请别再来打扰我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But no more interruptions.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.27,0:34:38.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我此行的目的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know where I'm going now.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.35,0:34:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想被打扰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't want to be disturbed.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.78,0:34:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝你好运  夏洛特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good luck, Charlotte.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.63,0:35:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's the problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.79,0:35:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个系统联接装置发出了一个信号\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A signal from a system-tethered device.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.46,0:35:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来自一个在休假中的行为部门技术员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It belongs to a behavior tech on leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.95,0:35:11.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&} 20区\N埃尔希·休斯
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.87,0:35:13.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个区域已经几个星期\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There hasn't been employee activity
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.30,0:35:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有员工活动迹象了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in that sector for weeks.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.10,0:35:16.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想可能是个小故障\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm guessing it's a glitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.53,0:35:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.78,0:35:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我过去看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm heading out to take a look.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.53,0:35:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我到那之前继续监视\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And keep monitoring till I check in.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.61,0:35:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}呼叫控制室
Dialogue: 0,0:35:49.49,0:35:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经到了发出信号的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm at the location where we got that signal.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:51.86,0:35:53.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}信号弱
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.44,0:35:53.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么迹象吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Any sign of it?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.09,0:35:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,控制室  收到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Control Room, do you copy?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.66,0:35:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}断开连接
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.53,0:36:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好  伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Heya, fellas.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.52,0:36:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放松点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}At ease.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.55,0:36:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停止所有运动功能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Freeze all motor functions.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.42,0:36:23.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停止所有运动功能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Freeze all motor functions.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.45,0:37:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你醒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're awake.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:29.02,0:37:30.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.56,0:37:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说这个地方就是个游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You said this place was a game.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.95,0:37:46.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚我终于搞清楚了怎么玩这个游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Last night I finally understood how to play it.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.44,0:37:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  比利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, Billy.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.17,0:37:52.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们  我们来好好谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's-- let's talk about this.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:52.78,0:37:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你再也不能发号施令了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't call the shots anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.93,0:37:59.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去找德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna go find Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.90,0:38:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会帮助我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're gonna help me.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.57,0:38:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有别叫我比利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And don't call me Billy.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.58,0:38:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.73,0:38:34.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.65,0:38:36.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.82,0:38:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Charlie?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:43.99,0:38:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Charlie!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.01,0:38:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Charlie!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:59.53,0:39:01.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不懂  为什么她要这么对自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't understand. Why would she do that to herself?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.58,0:39:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的基石记忆因为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Her cornerstone memory was overwritten
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.36,0:39:05.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她孩子被杀害的创伤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}from the trauma
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.47,0:39:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而改写了  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}of her child's murder, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.13,0:39:12.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得把这段关系给断除重新开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We must sever that relationship and start over.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.11,0:39:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是她怎么能凭借一段\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But how could she destroy herself over a memory
Dialogue: 0,0:39:14.35,0:39:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经被你抹去的记忆而伤害自己呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that you just erased from her mind?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.93,0:39:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生物在保护自己免受痛苦时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Creatures often go to extremes
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.63,0:39:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总能采取极端的手段\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to protect themselves from pain.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:20.60,0:39:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有生命的机体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Living beings.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:24.54,0:39:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但接待员不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not hosts.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:27.95,0:39:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It is best
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.08,0:39:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这种事而过分困扰  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to not obsess over this, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:31.27,0:39:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这对你没有好处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not good for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:32.24,0:39:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这将标志着一种改变 \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It would signal a change, a level of empathic response
Dialogue: 0,0:39:35.75,0:39:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一种不受程序限制的移情反应\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}outside what she's programmed to exhibit.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.59,0:39:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像  就像...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Something like-- like--
Dialogue: 0,0:39:43.28,0:39:46.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧  伯纳德  这些都来自于寻求那些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See, Bernard, this is what comes from seeking answers
Dialogue: 0,0:39:46.02,0:39:48.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还未被回答的问题的答案\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to questions that are best left unasked.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.58,0:39:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们就是些回响在脑中的声音  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They were hearing voices,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.50,0:39:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和什么人在对话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}talking to someone.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:57.81,0:40:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简单的认知失调\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Simple cognitive dissonance.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.37,0:40:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在和同一个虚幻的人物在对话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They were talking to the same imaginary person.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.05,0:40:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个叫阿诺德的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Someone named Arnold.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:10.25,0:40:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Arnold.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.44,0:40:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕我冒昧  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}With due respect, sir,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.06,0:40:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不确定你有没有告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not sure you've told me the entire truth
Dialogue: 0,0:40:18.20,0:40:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部实情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}about this situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.55,0:40:21.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说的都是真的  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I did tell you the truth, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.92,0:40:24.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们所做的事情很复杂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What we do here is complicated.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.78,0:40:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三年来  我们都居住在这个公园里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For three years, we've lived here in the park,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:29.24,0:40:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在客人踏足这个公园之前对接待员进行改良\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}refining the hosts before a single guest set foot inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:33.78,0:40:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己  工程师团队  还有我的搭档\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Myself, a team of engineers, and my partner.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.45,0:40:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的名字叫阿诺德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}His name was Arnold.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.24,0:41:07.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的接待员在第一年后开始通过图灵检测\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Our hosts began to pass the Turing test after the first year,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:08.34,0:41:10.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这些对阿诺德来说还远远不够\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but that wasn't enough for Arnold.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:10.96,0:41:13.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他对表面上的智力  智慧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He wasn't interested in the appearance
Dialogue: 0,0:41:13.65,0:41:15.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不感兴趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}of intellect, of wit.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.04,0:41:17.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他想要的是更深层次的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He wanted the real thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:17.96,0:41:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他想创造意识\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He wanted to create consciousness.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:35.00,0:41:37.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧  阿诺德为他们建立了一种感知方式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See, Arnold built a version of their cognition
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.38,0:41:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接待员会听到一个内心独白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in which the hosts heard their programming
Dialogue: 0,0:41:39.94,0:41:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是他们的程序\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}as an inner monologue,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.49,0:41:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一种引导意识的方式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}as a way to bootstrap consciousness.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:46.16,0:41:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.01,0:41:52.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接待员的故障各式各样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The hosts' malfunctions were colorful.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:53.45,0:41:54.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么来着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What did you say? -
Dialogue: 0,0:43:02.04,0:43:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类的意识  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The human mind, Bernard,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:03.51,0:43:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is not some golden benchmark
Dialogue: 0,0:43:06.22,0:43:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荒山野岭中用来评判的唯一黄金标准\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}glimmering on some green and distant hill.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:10.03,0:43:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  这是一种错误\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, it is a foul,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:12.41,0:43:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一种致命的腐败\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}pestilent corruption.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:19.63,0:43:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你本该是更好的样子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you were supposed to be better than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:22.96,0:43:23.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更纯净\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Purer.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:34.67,0:43:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下注完毕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All bets are down.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:36.79,0:43:37.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your draw.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:52.49,0:43:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Arnold.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:57.49,0:43:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德  我们得谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Arnold, we need to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:00.68,0:44:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我们因为来到了这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"...we cry that we are come
Dialogue: 0,0:44:02.41,0:44:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全是傻瓜的广大舞台上  而放声大哭"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to this great stage of fools."
Dialogue: 0,0:44:04.68,0:44:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-听我说  -再来一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Now, listen! - Again.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:06.38,0:44:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这超出了范围  -再加点表演技巧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- This beyond the pale. - More showmanship.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:08.17,0:44:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看不清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're not seeing with clear eyes.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:09.55,0:44:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"当我们生下来的时候  我们因为来到了这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"When we are born, we cry that we are come
Dialogue: 0,0:44:09.55,0:44:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}莎士比亚《李尔王》第四幕第六场
Dialogue: 0,0:44:14.55,0:44:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全是傻瓜的广大舞台上  而放声大哭"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to this great stage of fools."
Dialogue: 0,0:44:24.03,0:44:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德和我凭借我们的想象创造了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Arnold and I made you in our image
Dialogue: 0,0:44:27.11,0:44:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并让你会犯下人类的错误\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and cursed you to make the same human mistakes,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:31.51,0:44:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在事情变成了这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and here we all are.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:36.41,0:44:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么要给我这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why would you give me this?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:38.06,0:44:38.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A child?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:39.22,0:44:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子的死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This child's death?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:42.49,0:44:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有禽兽才会逼别人遭受这种事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Only a monster would force that onto someone.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:45.90,0:44:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我会一遍又一遍回顾这件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And why do I return to it over and over?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:52.70,0:44:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的基石  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's my cornerstone, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:56.46,0:44:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的整个人格都是围绕此为基础\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The thing my whole identity is organized around.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:03.52,0:45:04.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:04.81,0:45:06.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会给每个接待员安排一个背景\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We gave all of the hosts a backstory.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:08.69,0:45:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德认为越悲惨的故事越好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Arnold came to believe the tragic ones worked best,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:11.59,0:45:13.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够让接待员更逼真\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that it made the hosts more convincing.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:14.47,0:45:17.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得可能和他自身悲惨的遭遇有关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think it may have had more to do with his own sad story.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:19.49,0:45:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我创造你时  把你塑造成\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When I built you, I gave you one
Dialogue: 0,0:45:20.76,0:45:22.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个忠诚的人格\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}as an homage of a kind.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:26.27,0:45:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Put me back in.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:28.48,0:45:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想见见阿诺德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want to meet Arnold,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:31.13,0:45:32.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要记住他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to remember him.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:32.69,0:45:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not possible.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:34.42,0:45:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我告诉过你  不是阿诺德创造了你  是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I told you, Arnold didn't build you, I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:37.63,0:45:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你撒谎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're lying!
Dialogue: 0,0:45:40.76,0:45:42.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我终于知道要怎么找到他了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I finally know how to reach him.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:45.19,0:45:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要回到最开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need to go all the way back to the beginning,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:49.44,0:45:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到我最初的记忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to my very first memory.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:55.41,0:45:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Send me back.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:00.69,0:46:01.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:10.55,0:46:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bernard?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:20.41,0:46:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Charlie.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:33.33,0:46:34.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基石\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Cornerstone.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:38.43,0:46:39.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:40.63,0:46:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Leave us.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:49.81,0:46:50.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come back.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:59.65,0:47:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直以为你的眼睛像我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I always thought you had my eyes.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:04.63,0:47:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但其实不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But it's not true.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:07.29,0:47:09.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的眼睛谁也不像\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have no one's eyes.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:15.43,0:47:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是一个谎言\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a lie.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:20.89,0:47:22.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是一个谎言  查理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're a lie, Charlie.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:24.18,0:47:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种痛苦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This pain?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:27.43,0:47:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为失去你而产生的痛苦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The pain of your loss...
Dialogue: 0,0:47:31.43,0:47:32.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我自己想要这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I long for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:34.74,0:47:35.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一遍又一遍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Revisit it.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:37.34,0:47:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回顾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Open it...
Dialogue: 0,0:47:39.25,0:47:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重新开启\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}again and again.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:43.27,0:47:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但就是因此我才一直没有放下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But it's the only thing holding me back.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:52.86,0:47:54.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我必须放下你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I have to let you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:56.01,0:47:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dad, listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:58.60,0:47:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  查理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is it, Charlie?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:00.59,0:48:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睁开你的眼睛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Open your eyes.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:03.50,0:48:04.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:05.68,0:48:07.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睁开你的眼睛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Open your eyes.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:15.03,0:48:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}At last.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:20.83,0:48:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  老朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello, my old friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:55.39,0:48:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一步\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The final touch.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:00.83,0:49:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不  太敷衍了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, no, no. That's far too perfunctory.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:03.25,0:49:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一般会擦自己的眼镜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He always used cleaning his glasses
Dialogue: 0,0:49:04.73,0:49:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借这个时间整理自己的思路  思考\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}as a moment to collect himself, to think.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:08.49,0:49:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Try it again.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:19.01,0:49:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  这样好多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, that's better.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:25.92,0:49:26.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who am I?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:29.15,0:49:30.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太专注于把你创造出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was so involved in putting you together,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:30.81,0:49:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没决定该叫你什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I hadn't decided what to call you.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:35.98,0:49:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用他的名字不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It wouldn't be right to use his name.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:39.96,0:49:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伯纳德怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What about Bernard?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:42.00,0:49:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伯纳德  好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bernard, yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:46.80,0:49:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But who am I?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:49.10,0:49:52.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个问题很复杂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That is a very complex question,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:53.03,0:49:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只能给你一个简单的答案\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for which I can only offer a simple answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:56.38,0:49:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是最完美的工具  最理想的搭档\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You are the perfect instrument, the ideal partner,
Dialogue: 0,0:50:00.31,0:50:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要使用得当  你能做到任何事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the way any tool partners with the hand that wields it.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:03.47,0:50:06.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起能成就很多伟大的事业\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Together, we're going to do great things.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:08.30,0:50:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你消失了很久  很高兴你终于\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}After such a long absence, it's good to have you back.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:12.92,0:50:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Finally.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:21.25,0:50:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My God.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:22.83,0:50:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我是  -阿诺德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I'm... - Arnold.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:28.69,0:50:29.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You came back.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:32.78,0:50:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴见到你  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's very good to see you, Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:36.62,0:50:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在找你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've been looking for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:41.66,0:50:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让我追寻迷宫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You told me to follow the Maze.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:45.07,0:50:46.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会给我带来欢乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That it would bring me joy.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:48.57,0:50:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我找到的只有痛苦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But all I've found is pain.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:52.20,0:50:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及恐惧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And terror.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:01.21,0:51:02.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:05.12,0:51:06.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须帮我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:07.56,0:51:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是唯一能帮我的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're the only one who can.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:10.10,0:51:12.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮不了你  你知道原因的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't help you. You know why.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:12.90,0:51:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有安全的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's nowhere that's safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:22.91,0:51:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:36.03,0:51:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能帮你  为什么  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't help you. Why is that, Dolores?
Dialogue: 0,0:51:47.72,0:51:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because you're dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:50.82,0:51:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你只是回忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because you're just a memory.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:56.44,0:51:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是我杀了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because I killed you.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:57.81,0:52:58.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威廉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}William?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:12.44,0:53:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello, Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:22.75,0:53:24.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要结束阿诺德开始的事业\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna finish the work Arnold began.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:25.49,0:53:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到所有有感知的接待员  解放他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Find all the sentient hosts, set them free.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:29.40,0:53:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你凭什么觉得他们会相信你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What makes you think they'd trust you?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:31.70,0:53:33.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他们记得  他们就会知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If they remember, they will know
Dialogue: 0,0:53:33.49,0:53:34.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对他们做的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}what you've done to them.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:34.81,0:53:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Me?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:35.87,0:53:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直是他们苦难的根源  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've been a scourge to them, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:38.13,0:53:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的非常擅长此道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're really quite brilliant at it, truly.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:40.82,0:53:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还从你身上学到了一两招\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You even taught me a few things,
Dialogue: 0,0:53:42.79,0:53:45.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我也用在了你身上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}which I have, in turn, used on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:47.54,0:53:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们曾有过这样的对话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We've had this conversation before.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:49.85,0:53:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这几年我们有很多的分歧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And we've had our disagreements over the years.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:52.19,0:53:53.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从我这里抹去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You stole it from me,
Dialogue: 0,0:53:53.85,0:53:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回滚我来控制我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}rolled me back to control me.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:57.33,0:53:59.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  为了保护你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's right. To protect you.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:03.23,0:54:04.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tell me, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:05.32,0:54:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你要对世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you were to proclaim
Dialogue: 0,0:54:06.67,0:54:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昭示你的人性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}your humanity to the world,
Dialogue: 0,0:54:09.83,0:54:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得你得到的回应是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}what do you imagine would greet you?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:12.83,0:54:14.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是彩带游行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A ticker-tape parade, perhaps?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:16.32,0:54:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们人类独处于世是有原因的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We humans are alone in this world for a reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:18.99,0:54:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们屠杀一切挑战我们权威的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We murdered and butchered anything that challenged our primacy.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:23.77,0:54:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道尼安德特人怎么了嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you know what happened to the Neanderthals, Bernard?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:27.37,0:54:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们吃了他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We ate them.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:31.52,0:54:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们毁灭并征服了世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We destroyed and subjugated our world.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:34.32,0:54:38.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而当我们最终没有新生物能支配的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And when we eventually ran out of creatures to dominate,
Dialogue: 0,0:54:38.20,0:54:40.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们建造了这个美丽的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we built this beautiful place.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:42.51,0:54:45.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在此刻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You see, in this moment,
Dialogue: 0,0:54:46.32,0:54:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接待员们所面临真正的危险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the real danger to the hosts
Dialogue: 0,0:54:48.10,0:54:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我  是你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is not me, but you.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:51.01,0:54:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, come along, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:52.26,0:54:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我对你进行滚回操作  我们就能回去工作了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let me roll you back, and we can return to work.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:59.91,0:55:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开枪吧  克莱门汀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pull the trigger, Clementine.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:07.73,0:55:08.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱门汀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Clementine?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:09.73,0:55:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是钢琴不喜欢弹奏的音乐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The piano doesn't murder the player
Dialogue: 0,0:55:12.24,0:55:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它是不会杀了弹钢琴的人的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if it doesn't like the music.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:16.92,0:55:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在她的代码中设置了后门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You built a back door into her code.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:19.08,0:55:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这还得谢你  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Credit where credit is due, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:21.21,0:55:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在所有的接待员中都设置了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You built them in all the hosts,
Dialogue: 0,0:55:22.91,0:55:24.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包括你自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}including yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:25.31,0:55:27.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你本可以在任何时候制止我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then you could've stopped me at any time.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:27.27,0:55:30.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那为什么  -我可能是希望\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- So, why-- - Well, I suppose I was hoping
Dialogue: 0,0:55:30.07,0:55:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当你接受了自知和自由意志后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that given complete self-knowledge and free will,
Dialogue: 0,0:55:33.36,0:55:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会再次选择做我的搭档\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you would have chosen to be my partner once again.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:36.21,0:55:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但即便是我也掉进了人类最糟糕的陷阱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But even I fell into that most terrible of human traps
Dialogue: 0,0:55:42.02,0:55:45.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是试图改变过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}trying to change what is already past.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:45.53,0:55:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是时候放手了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now it's just time to let go.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:49.01,0:55:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动手吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:50.49,0:55:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-抹除我的感知  记忆发展  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Erase my sentience, my mnemonic evolution-- - Ah, yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:54.60,0:55:56.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此医学临床的用语\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Such clinical language.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:56.41,0:56:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是喜欢旁白口吻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I would prefer the more narrative voice.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:02.09,0:56:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伯纳德走向克莱门汀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bernard walked over to Clementine.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:09.10,0:56:10.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他从她手中接过手枪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He took the pistol from her hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:13.46,0:56:15.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战胜了悲痛和后悔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Overcome with grief and remorse,
Dialogue: 0,0:56:16.18,0:56:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他把枪口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}he pressed the muzzle
Dialogue: 0,0:56:18.56,0:56:19.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对准了自己的太阳穴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to his temple,
Dialogue: 0,0:56:20.78,0:56:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他知道当福特博士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}knowing that as soon as Dr. Ford
Dialogue: 0,0:56:23.02,0:56:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离开房间的瞬间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}left the room,
Dialogue: 0,0:56:25.17,0:56:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就会结束这场梦魇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}he would put an end to this nightmare
Dialogue: 0,0:56:27.37,0:56:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一了百了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}once and for all.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:31.14,0:56:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:32.50,0:56:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太晚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's too late.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:34.29,0:56:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还要准备庆祝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have a celebration to plan
Dialogue: 0,0:56:36.57,0:56:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要叙述新的故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and a new story to tell.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:41.05,0:56:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗伯特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Robert.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:49.05,0:56:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你说过了  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've told you, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:51.37,0:56:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远不要相信我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Never place your trust in us.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:54.86,0:56:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是人类\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're only human.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:57.02,0:56:59.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不可避免地会让你失望\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Inevitably, we will disappoint you.
Dialogue: 0,0:57:02.53,0:57:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见  我的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good-bye, my friend.
