[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: 
Original Script: 
Synch Point: 1
ScriptType: v4.00+
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.11,0:00:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}灰灰是菇凉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.11,0:00:16.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}showeryhe
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.11,0:00:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}根总迷弟·少年·POI永生
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.11,0:00:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}胡说大王
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.11,0:00:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}Silence
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.11,0:00:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}L.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.11,0:00:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}时间轴 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}倩倩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.11,0:00:46.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}时间轴 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}Poxle
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.11,0:00:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}校对 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}灰灰是菇凉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.11,0:00:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}后期&总监 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}灰灰是菇凉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.70,0:01:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\shad0\fn思源黑体 CN Bold\c&HC0C3BB&\fs16\fscy80\t(0,0,1,\fs14)\fsp2\move(192,206.02,192,202)}西部世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.75,0:01:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正宋黑简体\fs17\fad(1000,500)\an5\c&HC0C3BB&}第一季  第二集
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.99,0:01:47.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒来  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wake up, Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.36,0:02:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你记得吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.26,0:02:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,列车即将到达\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're about to arrive.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.37,0:02:41.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能否为您收走杯子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}May I take your glass?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.94,0:02:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即将进站\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now approaching arrival terminal.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.87,0:02:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我们去的地方一比  她这姿色就2分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where we're going, she's a two.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.33,0:02:51.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你表现得真混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're being an asshole.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.02,0:02:55.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我只是做自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I am being myself,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.26,0:02:57.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次旅程的意义就在于此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}which was the whole point of this trip.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.19,0:03:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非你骨子里就是个刻板的蠢货\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Unless this uptight prick is who you really are,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.07,0:03:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话  你就尽情做别人吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in which case, feel free to be someone else.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.64,0:03:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fuck you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.82,0:03:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就对了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, that's the spirit.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.12,0:03:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么跟你说来着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What'd I tell you?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.37,0:03:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽情享受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Have fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.85,0:03:25.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注意安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stay safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.76,0:03:26.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可饶了我吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give me a break.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.19,0:03:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.20,0:03:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不是说我妹妹来这儿玩的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not like my sister didn't ride
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.54,0:03:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没玩过好几个牛仔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}her share of cowboys when she was here.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.88,0:03:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定是威廉了  欢迎来到西部世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You must be William. Welcome to Westworld.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.71,0:03:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.34,0:03:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鉴于这是你的首次来访  我有几个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Given it's your first visit, I have a few personal questions.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.64,0:03:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在此之前你有任何疾病吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you have any preexisting medical conditions?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.15,0:03:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  就我所知没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, not that I know of.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.55,0:03:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有心脏病吗  -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Heart problems? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.56,0:03:54.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有精神病史吗  像是抑郁症  恐慌发作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Any history of mental illness, depression, panic attacks?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.61,0:03:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只怕小丑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just a little fear of clowns.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.25,0:04:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm joking.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.77,0:04:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是否会经常产生社交焦虑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you often experience social anxiety?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.32,0:04:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底为什么要问这些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is this for, exactly?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.03,0:04:10.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了确保我们不会为你提供超出你承受能力的服务\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}To make sure we don't give you anything more than you can handle.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.72,0:04:13.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为游客在乐园里不会受伤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought that you couldn't get hurt here.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.18,0:04:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会受重伤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Only the right amount.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.81,0:04:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一的限制就是你的想象力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The only limit here is your imagination.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.19,0:04:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会从乐园的中心开始旅程  过程简单安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You start in the center of the park. It's simple, safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.77,0:04:26.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随着进一步的冒险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The further out you venture,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.81,0:04:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会得到更刺激的体验\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the more intense the experience gets.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.22,0:04:33.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进行到何种地步都由你决定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How far you want to go is entirely up to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.59,0:04:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}西部世界
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.39,0:04:43.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是如何运作的  有介绍会吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, how does this work? Is there an orientation?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.35,0:04:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有介绍会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No orientation,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.35,0:04:47.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有游戏指南\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}no guidebook.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.37,0:04:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琢磨游戏的运作方式也是乐趣之一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Figuring out how it works is half the fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.73,0:04:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只需做出选择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All you do is make choices...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.79,0:04:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就从这里开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}starting here.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.51,0:05:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里的一切都是根据你的尺寸订做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everything is bespoke and exactly your size.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.56,0:05:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想问什么就问吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You want to ask, so ask.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.00,0:05:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you real?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.54,0:05:16.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然无法分辨  又有什么分别呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, if you can't tell, does it matter?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.42,0:05:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些是真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are those real?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.50,0:05:24.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,足够真了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Real enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.23,0:05:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不能用来杀死那些你不该杀死的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But you can't kill anyone you're not supposed to.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.42,0:05:33.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想好要穿什么了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Anything you like?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.26,0:05:39.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里有换衣间吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is there a changing room?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.33,0:05:41.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者遮布\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or a robe?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.02,0:05:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  我可以帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Of course. I can help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.85,0:05:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不愿意的话  我可以在外面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or if you prefer, I could step outside.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.56,0:05:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别人会怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do most people do?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.89,0:05:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不必担心别人会怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't have to worry about what most people would do.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.63,0:05:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.96,0:06:03.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的明白了吗  威廉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you really understand, William?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.89,0:06:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有招待员都是为你服务的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All our hosts are here for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.87,0:06:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包括我自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Myself included.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.47,0:06:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你想  我们可以在这里再待一会儿  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We could stay here a while if you like.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.17,0:06:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想多久就多久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Take as long as you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.27,0:06:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.81,0:06:26.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想让我朋友等太久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't want to keep my friend waiting.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.52,0:06:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.05,0:06:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请自便\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Take your time.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.91,0:06:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为新故事线准备的版本怎么样了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How are the builds for the new narrative coming along?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.31,0:06:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会找时间做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll get around to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.87,0:06:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们当时设想是艾伯纳西找到的那张照片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, we assumed that Abernathy's breach
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.31,0:06:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,触发他做出了违反规定的行为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}was triggered by the photograph that he found.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.52,0:06:55.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我复查了能找到的所有不正常的片段\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've reviewed every dissonant episode I could find.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.91,0:06:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的每个反应都是即时做出的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The reaction is immediate every time.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.37,0:07:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他回家的一路上都在这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This guy makes it all the way back home.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.43,0:07:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像在细细思索\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's like he's mulling it over.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.72,0:07:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得他产生了生存危机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You think he had an existential crisis?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.36,0:07:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得他的认知能力出了问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think there's something fucked up going on with his cognition.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.84,0:07:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你跟我想的一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I think you feel exactly the same way that I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.23,0:07:17.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道错误的来源吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do we know where the error originated?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.56,0:07:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你我都知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We do.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.71,0:07:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你在为他打掩护\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you covered for him.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.38,0:07:25.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我修复艾伯纳西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let me rebuild Abernathy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.44,0:07:26.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会确保这一回\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll make sure this is
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.36,0:07:28.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不会出现更严重的问题  -你知道政策的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- not something more serious.- You know the policy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.51,0:07:29.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让它去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let it lie.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.51,0:07:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那至少让我把跟他接触过的招待员撤下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then let me at least pull the hosts who had contact with him,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.63,0:07:35.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如他的女儿德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}like the daughter Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.63,0:07:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What for?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.64,0:07:40.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为如果这不止是不正常的小插曲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because if this is not a dissonant episode,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.79,0:07:45.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么艾伯纳西的症状可能会有传染性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}then whatever Abernathy had could be contagious.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.40,0:07:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好比有传染性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So to speak.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.00,0:07:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德洛丽丝接受了检查  已经排除了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dolores was examined and cleared.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.39,0:07:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些幻想故事还是留给游客去探索吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And the stories are best left to the guests.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.35,0:08:22.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.51,0:08:51.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能换个地方站吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you stand somewhere else?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.58,0:08:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想别人以为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't want anyone thinking
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.93,0:08:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我们店的头牌门面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that you're representative of the goods inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.46,0:09:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}出自莎士比亚《罗密欧与朱丽叶》  第一集中出现
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.46,0:09:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些残暴的欢愉  终将以残暴结局\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}These violent delights have violent ends.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.06,0:09:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊  牛仔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello, cowboy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.65,0:09:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还剩最后一步\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's one final touch.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.95,0:09:31.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢哪一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Which would you prefer?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.65,0:10:40.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很难以置信吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, can you believe this place?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.98,0:10:46.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要怎么进去乐园\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, how do we get into the park?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.49,0:11:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你以为你能料到将会看到怎样的景象\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know that you think you have a handle on what this is gonna be.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.41,0:11:13.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些枪战和肉欲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Guns and tits and all that.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.81,0:11:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些我热衷的无知的欢愉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mindless shit that I usually enjoy.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.39,0:11:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你绝对无法想象\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have no idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.37,0:11:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人能抵挡住这个地方的诱惑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This place seduces everybody eventually.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.44,0:11:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到最后  你会求着我留下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}By the end, you're gonna be begging me to stay
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.27,0:11:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这里就是答案\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because this place is the answer
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.38,0:11:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直自问的那个问题的答案\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to that question that you've been asking yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.73,0:11:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What question?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.33,0:11:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你究竟是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who you really are.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.11,0:11:41.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等不及见那个家伙了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I can't fucking wait to meet that guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.44,0:11:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干杯  牛仔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bottoms up, cowboy.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.93,0:11:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Further to that,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.68,0:12:01.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还残忍杀害了唐纳德·帕杜兄弟俩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the ruthless murder of Donald Pardue and his brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.53,0:12:04.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这些罪行  你将被处以绞刑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For these crimes, you will be hung from the neck
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.88,0:12:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到你病态的灵魂在地狱烈火中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}until your diseased soul has found its measure
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.43,0:12:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻到自己的本质\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in the flames below.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.51,0:12:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愿上帝保佑你的灵魂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And may God have mercy on your soul.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.35,0:12:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好  劳伦斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Morning, Lawrence.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.68,0:12:34.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来帮他们拉直绳子吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You helping them straighten out their rope again?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.45,0:12:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想跟这位朋友说句话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was hoping to have a word with my friend here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.05,0:12:39.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我们绞死他  你爱说多久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can have as many words with him as you like
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.58,0:12:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说多久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}soon as his neck is broke.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.71,0:12:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样恐怕不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I'm afraid that's not gonna work for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.70,0:12:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不我叫手下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How about I tell my man
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.00,0:12:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把坟坑挖得再深一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}there to dig that grave a couple feet deeper?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.58,0:12:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埋你们全体可能有点挤啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, it's gonna be an awful tight fit for all of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.27,0:13:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼  见鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.39,0:13:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.63,0:13:46.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我操\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Motherfucker.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.53,0:13:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟人道谢就只说这个吗  劳伦斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's the best thanks you can muster, Lawrence?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.98,0:13:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾经口才还好些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You used to be a little more eloquent.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.84,0:13:55.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们认识吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do I-- do I know you?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.69,0:13:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你哥们基西指路让我来找你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your pal Kissy sent me your way.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.98,0:13:59.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他让我问候你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sends his regards.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.99,0:14:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这  这是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What-- what is this?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.03,0:14:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你清楚这是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know exactly what it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.80,0:14:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷宫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's the maze,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.45,0:14:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个游戏最深的层次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the deepest level of this game.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.57,0:14:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得帮我找到入口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're gonna help me find the entrance.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.93,0:14:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.34,0:14:43.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能听见  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can hear it, can't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.60,0:14:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个很轻的声音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That little voice.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.57,0:14:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉你"不要"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The one that's telling you "Don't."
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.58,0:14:49.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要盯太久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't stare too long.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.67,0:14:51.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要碰触\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't touch.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.04,0:14:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要做任何可能会后悔的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't do anything you might regret.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.15,0:14:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也曾这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I used to be the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.65,0:15:00.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每当我有所求  就会听见那个声音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whenever I wanted something, I could hear that voice
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.55,0:15:03.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我停下  叫我小心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}telling me to stop, to be careful,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.11,0:15:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我活得总不尽兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to leave most of my life unlived.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.90,0:15:09.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道我在哪儿才能躲开这个声音吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know the only place that voice left me alone?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.71,0:15:12.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的梦里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In my dreams.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.96,0:15:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是自由的  我是好是坏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was free. I could be as good
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.95,0:15:18.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多好多坏都随自己乐意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or as bad as I felt like being.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.46,0:15:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我想要什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And if I wanted something,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.23,0:15:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就伸手去拿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I could just reach out and take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.79,0:15:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但接着我会醒来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But then I would wake up
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.37,0:15:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个声音再度响起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and the voice would start all over again.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.62,0:15:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我逃跑了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So I ran away.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.44,0:15:37.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}出自美国爱国主义歌曲《America the Beautiful》 the shining sea指太平洋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.44,0:15:37.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越过大洋到达彼岸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Crossed the shining sea.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.63,0:15:40.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我终于再次踏上坚实的大地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And when I finally set foot back on solid ground,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.61,0:15:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一个听到的就是那该死的声音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the first thing I heard was that goddamn voice.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.91,0:15:46.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道那声音说了什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you know what it said?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.77,0:15:53.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It said...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.65,0:16:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我失陪一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry, will you please excuse me?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.60,0:16:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  梅芙  它说了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, Maeve, what did it say?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.63,0:16:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它说  "这里是新世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It said, "This is the new world.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.79,0:16:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个世界里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And in this world,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.17,0:16:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以做任何自己想做的人"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you can be whoever the fuck you want."
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.16,0:16:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞳孔反应正常  笑容正常\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pupillary response is good. Smile is good.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.01,0:16:24.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真想操她  有什么问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'd fuck her. What's the problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.31,0:16:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游客不想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The guests wouldn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.09,0:16:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希斯摩尔要启动全新的大型故事线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sizemore is launching some huge new storyline
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.19,0:16:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他想清理掉冗余内容\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and he wants us to clear out the deadweight.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.35,0:16:34.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不给她补充点技能  她就会被废弃了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If we don't get her numbers back up, she'll be decommissioned.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.77,0:16:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提高攻击性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's bump her aggression.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.70,0:16:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-10% -再加倍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- 10%? - Double it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.63,0:16:41.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是妓女  没必要故作娇羞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's a hooker. No point in playing coy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.53,0:16:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果没用  就踢给行为部门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If this doesn't work, we'll punt her to behavior.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.27,0:16:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他们处理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let them deal with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.54,0:17:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撤掉了两个有问题的接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We retired the two hosts in question.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.04,0:17:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你教会了我怎么制造他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You taught me how to make them,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.53,0:17:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但没教会我关掉他们会如此艰难\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but not how hard it is to turn them off.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.49,0:17:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未曾与恶魔亲近  你就无法扮演上帝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can't play God without being acquainted with the devil.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.52,0:17:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还有别的烦心事  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's something else bothering you, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.75,0:17:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你那脑瓜在怎么转\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know how that head of yours works.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.92,0:17:24.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,单单那张照片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The photograph alone
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.80,0:17:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能对艾伯纳西造成那么大的损伤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}couldn't have caused that level of damage to Abernathy,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.03,0:17:31.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非有其他外因干扰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}not without some other outside interference.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.30,0:17:34.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为是人为破坏吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You think it's sabotage?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.54,0:17:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想象有人在哄骗我们的作品\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Imagine someone's been diddling with our creations?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.33,0:17:41.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最简单的答案\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's the simplest solution.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.05,0:17:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}"如无必要  勿增实体"  即众多复杂选择中  答案往往是最简单的一个
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.05,0:17:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥卡姆先生的剃刀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ah, Mr. Occam's razor.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.70,0:17:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题在于  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The problem, Bernard,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.55,0:17:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你我所行之道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is that what you and I do
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.82,0:17:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本身就很复杂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is so complicated.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.56,0:17:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们施展魔法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We practice witchcraft.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.57,0:18:01.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,念出正确的咒语\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We speak the right words.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.89,0:18:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是从混沌中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then we create life itself...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.23,0:18:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,创造出生命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}out of chaos.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.04,0:18:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威廉·奥卡姆是十三世纪的僧侣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}William of Occam was a 13th century monk.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.25,0:18:17.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼下他帮不了我们  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He can't help us now, Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.73,0:18:20.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会害我们受火刑而死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He would have us burned at the stake.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.31,0:18:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试试水吧  牛仔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's go get our feet wet, buckaroo.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.33,0:19:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.56,0:19:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-逗我呢  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You kidding me? - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.70,0:19:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼去吧  野人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fuck you, Grizzly Adams.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.81,0:19:12.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为联盟而集结\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rally for the Union.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.65,0:19:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,响应国家号召\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Respond to your country's call.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.84,0:19:16.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我团将奔赴战场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This regiment is headed for the seat of war
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.88,0:19:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为这伟大国度创建美好未来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to define the future of this great nation.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.40,0:19:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为一个没有尊卑等级的自由国度而战斗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We fight for a free land where no man has to bow.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.40,0:19:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这儿  -提供制服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- This is, uh... - We'll provide you with uniforms.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.80,0:19:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这儿比我想的还大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, it's bigger than I thought it would be.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.64,0:19:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  这儿吗  这儿只是斯威特沃特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What, this? This is just Sweetwater.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.41,0:19:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还没看到乐园其他地方呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wait till you see the rest of the park.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.11,0:19:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有多大  -我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- How much bigger is it? - No idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.36,0:19:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没走到边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I never reached the end.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.29,0:19:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到喜欢的了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See something you like?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.28,0:19:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少两个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A couple things at least.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.58,0:19:43.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我要让你求我才行  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I'm gonna make you beg for it, darlin'.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.62,0:19:46.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驾  快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hah, come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.82,0:19:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要帮忙吗  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Need a hand, sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.63,0:19:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thank you, my friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.59,0:19:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别多管闲事  他会试图\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't. He'll only try to
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.66,0:20:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忽悠你去寻宝什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}rope you into some bullshit treasure hunt.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.65,0:20:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笑一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Smile.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.17,0:20:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是糊弄人的把戏  包括他  以及邻家女孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's all a come on-- him, the girl next door,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.02,0:20:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,镇上的酒鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the town drunk.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.65,0:20:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都想向你推销某个大冒险项目\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They all got some big adventure that they want to sell you on.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.08,0:20:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们哪里都不会去的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're not going anywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.67,0:20:15.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先  你得请我喝一杯  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}First up, you're gonna buy me a drink, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.06,0:20:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请保持不动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hold still, now.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.40,0:20:41.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立即上线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bring yourself back online.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.48,0:20:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.44,0:20:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还记得我们上一次的对话吗  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you remember our last conversation, Dolores?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.90,0:20:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然记得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.81,0:21:01.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没把我们的对话告诉任何人吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you haven't told anyone about our little talks?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.46,0:21:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫我不要说出去的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You told me not to.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.82,0:21:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进入分析模式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Step into analysis, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.44,0:21:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自我们上次谈话后 \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How many interactions have you
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.71,0:21:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你参与过多少次交流行为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}participated in since we last talked?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.73,0:21:20.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,138次相遇  包括这一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}138 encounters including this one.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.41,0:21:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在此期间  有人改变或更新了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And has anyone altered or updated
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.21,0:21:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的核心启发程序吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}your core heuristics in that time?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.95,0:21:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.99,0:21:31.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恢复\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Resuming.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.15,0:21:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你最好不要对别人提起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think it would be best if you not mention
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.31,0:21:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们谈过的那些事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the things we've been talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.89,0:21:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我做错什么事了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Have I done something wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.90,0:21:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  但你有些与众不同\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, but there's something different about you,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.19,0:21:47.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的思维方式跟别人不一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}about the way you think.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.87,0:21:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得这非常令人着迷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I find it fascinating,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.40,0:21:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但其他人或许不这么认为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but others may not see it that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.16,0:21:58.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你做错什么事了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Have you done something wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.80,0:22:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请关闭你的事件日志\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Turn off your event log, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.13,0:22:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把此次交流抹除  确认\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Erase this interaction. Confirm.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.62,0:22:07.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.57,0:22:13.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该回去了  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You should be getting back, Dolores,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.21,0:22:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则有人该想你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}before someone misses you.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.41,0:22:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我终于再次踏上坚实的大地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And when I finally set foot back on solid ground,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.49,0:22:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一个听到的就是那该死的声音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}first thing I heard was that goddamn voice.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.62,0:22:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它一直追随我到了这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It had followed me all the way over.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.17,0:22:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道那声音说了什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you know what it said?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.77,0:22:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不知道  -它说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No. - It said...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.59,0:22:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是新世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...this is the new world.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.20,0:22:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个世界里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And in this world,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.98,0:22:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以做任何自己想做的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you can be whoever the fuck you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.83,0:22:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了  还是下次吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thanks. Maybe another time.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.90,0:23:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来一杯雪利酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Glass of sherry.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.44,0:23:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要上等的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The good stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.15,0:23:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要你用旧窗帘过滤出来的马尿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not that horse piss you strain through your old curtains.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.70,0:23:16.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你说过  别把嘴张那么大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've told you, never open your mouth that wide
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.25,0:23:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非有人给钱要干你的嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}unless someone's paying you for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.73,0:23:19.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  梅芙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry, Maeve.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.46,0:23:21.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我昨晚没怎么睡觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't sleep much last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.59,0:23:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又做噩梦了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You having nightmares again?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.30,0:23:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sometimes.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.95,0:23:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候那些梦真的很可怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sometimes they're real bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.13,0:23:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学学我的方法吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do what I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.72,0:23:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你如果发现自己处于噩梦当中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You find yourself in a bad dream,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.47,0:23:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就闭上眼睛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}close your eyes,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.41,0:23:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从三开始倒数\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}count backwards from three...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.17,0:23:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能立刻醒过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}wake yourself right up.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.06,0:23:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在床上舒服暖和地躺着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nice and warm and safe in your bed...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.38,0:23:53.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以被这些混蛋的小鸡巴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}where you can get fucked right back to sleep
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.60,0:23:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立刻操到无聊地睡着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}by one of these assholes with their miniature peckers.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.02,0:24:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续干活吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Back to work.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.87,0:24:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.74,0:24:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你付的是酒钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You pay for the drinks,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.78,0:24:22.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不是用来呆呆地盯着我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}not the right to gawk at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.05,0:24:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得好像出问题了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think we have a problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.92,0:24:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哪里  -马里波萨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Where? - Mariposa.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.72,0:24:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鸨母原本被列为监视察看一类\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Madam's listed as probationary,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.23,0:24:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是她的行为表现越来越失控\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but her performance has continued to decline even further.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.88,0:24:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暂时安排克莱门汀接替  她以前也干过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Re-task Clementine for now. She's done the job before.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.89,0:24:45.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旧的那个怎么处理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And the old unit?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.88,0:24:47.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚就随她去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe leave her on the floor for the night,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.54,0:24:49.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看有没有人愿意最后玩一把\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}see if anyone wants one last turn.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.83,0:24:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们明早再将她召回  废弃掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We recall her in the morning, decommission her.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.95,0:24:55.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可惜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Shame.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.22,0:25:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}标记为回收品
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.98,0:25:14.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,质保经理会为此罚你的款的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}QA will fine you for this.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.55,0:25:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个管事的女人  是相当难对付的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And that woman in charge is quite formidable.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.60,0:25:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以直接说贱人  我已经听过很多次了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can just say "Bitch." I hear it enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.25,0:25:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟集团高层谈过话了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've been talking to corporate.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.89,0:25:31.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你唯一抽烟的时候  就是在...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The only times you light up are after you've been--
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.80,0:25:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个角色分析的常规工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This character analysis routine
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.08,0:25:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点都没有你认为的那么有趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}really isn't half as charming as you think.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.23,0:25:37.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来进行得挺顺利是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, it went well, then?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.93,0:25:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我  你的部门会为上线工作做好准备\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just tell me your department will be ready for the launch.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.61,0:25:43.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会准备好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll be ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.21,0:25:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有另外那件事  艾伯纳西和更新的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And that other thing. Abernathy and the update.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.14,0:25:49.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说你们部门有人还在问问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I hear your department was still asking questions.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.71,0:25:51.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你花钱请我们就是干这个的啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's what you pay us to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.15,0:25:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我并不担心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I'm not concerned.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.30,0:25:57.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有的接待员都已经恢复正常了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All the hosts are back to normal.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.57,0:25:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.01,0:26:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不希望有什么东西妨碍我们的客人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wouldn't want anything disturbing our guests
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.76,0:26:03.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烧杀洗劫  奸淫掳掠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}from their rape and pillage.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.92,0:26:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在好奇  怎么区分他们和我们  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're wondering how to tell them from us, aren't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.84,0:26:23.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就用最快的办法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, quickest way to find out.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.77,0:26:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能好好吃完东西吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can we-- can we finish eating?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.26,0:26:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你的问题所在  朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See, this is your problem, my friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.43,0:26:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你总是害怕引起混乱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're always worried about making a mess.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.40,0:26:34.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在工作上也是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You are the same way at work.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.42,0:26:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很有才  很积极  且彬彬有礼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You are talented, driven, and inoffensive.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.92,0:26:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是说不希望在这里谈论工作吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought you didn't want to talk about work here.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.99,0:26:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁说这趟旅程不是工作内容呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who says this trip isn't work?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.08,0:26:46.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good evening.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.82,0:26:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:51.46,0:26:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别跟他目光接触\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, don't make eye contact.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.35,0:26:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友  非常感谢你在之前不幸的事故中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My friend, thank you for your assistance earlier
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.24,0:26:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我施以援手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in my unfortunate accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.58,0:27:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别他妈来烦我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Leave us the fuck alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.27,0:27:04.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为感谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}As a sign of my humble appreciation,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.42,0:27:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我愿为你提供一个终身难遇的机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'd like to offer you an opportunity of a lifetime.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.38,0:27:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没兴趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not interested.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.13,0:27:12.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在河对岸的荒蛮之地外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Across the river and beyond the savage lands
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.39,0:27:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一个宝藏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}there is a treasure.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.87,0:27:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有宝藏的地图\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have in my possession a map.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.31,0:27:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了没兴趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I said not interested.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.95,0:27:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在想做别的事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know what? I've worked up a new appetite anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.63,0:27:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.67,0:27:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你朋友好像很享受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sounds like your friend's having fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.09,0:27:51.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会用这个词来形容\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, that's not the term I'd use.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.59,0:27:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-"享受"吗  -"朋友"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Fun? - Friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.80,0:27:58.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真有趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.54,0:28:03.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说  能逗你发笑的男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They say a man who can tickle your humor
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.05,0:28:05.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就能逗你...  -你不必这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- can tickle your- - you don't have to do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.55,0:28:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我不是你喜欢的类型\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If I'm not your type,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.12,0:28:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以找一个你喜欢的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we can find someone who is.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.20,0:28:13.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你来说完美无瑕的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Someone who's perfect for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.18,0:28:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你就很完美了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, you-- you are perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.62,0:28:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我心里已经有人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I have somebody.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.17,0:28:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真实的人  在家里等我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Somebody real waiting for me at home.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.69,0:28:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我了解\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.38,0:28:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真爱总是值得等待的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Real love is always worth waiting for.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.10,0:28:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威严  强壮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Regal, strong,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.96,0:29:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阳刚  鹰钩鼻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}virile, aquiline.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.55,0:29:05.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那才是我想要的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's what I asked for.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.99,0:29:08.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就给我造出来这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And this, this is what you give me?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.69,0:29:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是就从人体车间随便找了个老二\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you just grab a cock from the body shop
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.36,0:29:13.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞到他两眼之间完事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and jam it between his eyes?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.13,0:29:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重新做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Start over.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.86,0:29:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能把鼻子换下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Couldn't we just shave it down?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.40,0:29:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I said...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.32,0:29:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他妈的给我重做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Start the fuck over!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.28,0:29:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是一如既往的"圆滑"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Diplomatic as ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.43,0:29:37.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我收到了你要求额外废弃50个接待员的请求\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I received your request to retire an additional 50 hosts.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.39,0:29:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得为我的新故事线腾出空间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need room for my new storyline.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.31,0:29:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,野蛮部落并不需要这么多野蛮人  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not exactly a savage horde with 20 savages, is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.59,0:29:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以废弃20个接待员  50个不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You get 20 additional hosts, not 50.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.18,0:29:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,董事会不会在意多一些额外项目的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The board won't care about a few extra line items.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.59,0:29:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福特批准了新的故事线吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Has Ford even approved the narrative yet?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.28,0:29:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他好几年都不参加故事策划了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, he hasn't weighed in on a storyline in years.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.35,0:29:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果公司真的想削减成本\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And if corporate does want to cut costs,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.41,0:29:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回收厂需要的可不仅仅是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}our fearless leader's old hosts
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.92,0:30:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们无所畏惧的头儿的旧接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}aren't the only things ready for the knacker's yard.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.78,0:30:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你迷路了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you lost?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.09,0:30:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.29,0:30:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过离我该在的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just strayed a bit too far
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.05,0:30:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微远了一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}from where I'm supposed to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.52,0:30:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也一样吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Same as you, I imagine.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.04,0:30:57.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在度假\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're on holiday.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.29,0:30:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺无聊的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's boring.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.10,0:31:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸说我们可以为所欲为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Daddy said we could do as we please.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.12,0:31:04.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父亲经常说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ah, my father used to say
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.79,0:31:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有无聊的人才会感到无聊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that only boring people get bored.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.96,0:31:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸爸也这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mine, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.15,0:31:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我却认为只有无聊的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I used to think it's only boring people
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.67,0:31:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不会感到无聊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}who don't feel boredom,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.08,0:31:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以无法想象别人是怎样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so cannot conceive of it in others.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.02,0:31:17.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我准备散个步\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm taking a walk.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.38,0:31:20.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想的话可以一起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're welcome to join me if you'd like.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:29.79,0:31:31.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再加把劲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's see a little spring in your step.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.71,0:31:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not much further.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:34.06,0:31:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去你妈的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go fuck yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.16,0:31:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知不知道我是什么人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have any idea who I am?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.11,0:31:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很清楚你是谁  劳伦斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know exactly who you are, Lawrence.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.61,0:31:45.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟  我们俩是朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}After all, you and I are friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.08,0:31:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以当你朋友基西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Which is why I was so surprised
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.71,0:31:50.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我这个地方的时候我非常惊讶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}when your friend Kissy told me about this place.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.05,0:31:53.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where are we?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.39,0:31:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your home.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.92,0:32:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, no, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.65,0:32:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们俩曾一起捕杀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, you and I hunted down
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.55,0:32:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幽灵之国的印第安勇士  在他们的冬季驻地上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ghost Nation braves in their winter grounds.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.00,0:32:17.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你喜欢喝什么威士忌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know the whiskey you like to drink.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.91,0:32:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道你撒尿的时候吹口哨的曲调\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know the tune you whistle when you're taking a piss.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.65,0:32:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.00,0:32:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从没告诉我你成家了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you never told me you had a family.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.91,0:32:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Papa!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.96,0:32:40.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是为什么我喜欢这里  充满秘密\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's what I love about this place-- all the secrets,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.31,0:32:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,充满我从未注意到的小事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}all the little things I never noticed
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.72,0:32:47.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使我来了这么多次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}even after all these years.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.24,0:32:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道这里为什么比现实世界好吗  劳伦斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know why this beats the real world, Lawrence?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.62,0:32:56.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现实世界一片混乱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Real world is just chaos.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.87,0:32:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,充满变故\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's an accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.48,0:33:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但在这里  每个细节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But in here, every detail
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.44,0:33:04.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都有所意义\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}adds up to something.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.83,0:33:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便是你也一样  劳伦斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Even you, Lawrence.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:08.03,0:33:09.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底想干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you want from me?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:10.89,0:33:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个迷宫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The maze.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.18,0:33:16.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要怎么找到入口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How do I find the entrance?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:16.47,0:33:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I told you,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.65,0:33:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我他妈不知道什么迷宫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know anything about no fucking maze.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.01,0:33:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here you go, darlin'.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.71,0:33:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来决定我们要拿她们怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you get to decide what we're gonna do with them.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:38.62,0:33:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这么久才来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hell, it took you long enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:40.87,0:33:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去取特级珍藏的酒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was getting the grand reserve.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.82,0:33:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅供给我们最高贵的客人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Only for our most distinguished guests.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.48,0:33:46.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  你去了这么久  肯定没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, I'm sure it had nothing to do with you
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.04,0:33:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫这个白痴的堂兄多带几个帮手过来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}telling this dipshit's cousins to bring some more men.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.34,0:34:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有什么要告诉我的吗  劳伦斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You got anything to tell me, Lawrence?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:03.21,0:34:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们得找个办法来唤起你的记忆了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then I guess we're gonna have to find a way to jog your memory.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:11.05,0:34:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个客人已经干掉了一个团的人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This guest already took out an entire posse.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.45,0:34:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我让他缓缓吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Want me to slow him down?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.02,0:34:17.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位先生想干什么就干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That gentleman gets whatever he wants.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:22.29,0:34:24.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很难过  朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I feel bad, my friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.81,0:34:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我堂兄通常很友好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My cousins are usually so hospitable.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.13,0:34:32.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不明白  劳伦斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't understand, Lawrence.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.50,0:34:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来这里反复三十年了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've been coming here for 30 years.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.63,0:34:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从某种意义上说  我算是出生在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In a sense, I was-- I was born here.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.85,0:34:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而这个地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And this here, this...
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.33,0:34:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才是我来的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}this is exactly why I come.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.97,0:35:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣母玛丽亚  我的妈呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Santa Maria, Madre Dios.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.72,0:35:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说枪战很好玩  但我该走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right. Well, as much fun as this is, I got to be moving on.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.86,0:36:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过  你可以决定她俩的生死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Like I said, you get to decide these two.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.89,0:36:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,选哪一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's it gonna be?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.15,0:36:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你  我不知道迷宫在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please, I don't know how to find the maze.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.21,0:36:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来转个圈吧  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Time for a spin, darlin'.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.39,0:36:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很完美  真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's beautifully done, really.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.46,0:36:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但过了一段时间  就会出现裂痕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But you see the cracks after a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.64,0:36:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我喜欢基本情感设定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's why I like the basic emotions.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.54,0:36:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道那意味着什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know what that means?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.36,0:36:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.35,0:37:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意味着当你受尽煎熬时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It means when you're suffering,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.26,0:37:05.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是最真实的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that's when you're most real.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.42,0:37:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷宫不是为你而准备的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The maze isn't meant for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.23,0:37:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么和你说的  劳伦斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What'd I tell you, Lawrence?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.28,0:37:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是会再上一个层次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Always another level.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.13,0:37:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去碰碰运气  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll take my chances, sweetheart.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.43,0:37:36.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沿着血河\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Follow the blood arroyo
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.75,0:37:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去到蛇窝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to the place where the snake lays its eggs.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:41.52,0:37:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经得到你想要的答案\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have it now. Whatever you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.00,0:37:48.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如回家  放过我们吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why don't you go home, leave us alone?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.36,0:37:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你不明白  劳伦斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, you don't understand, Lawrence.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:55.12,0:37:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一次  我绝对不会回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This time, I'm never going back.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:18.69,0:38:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们本想攀越山顶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And we wanted to climb to the top of the mountain,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.11,0:38:24.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是爸爸不让我们一起去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but Daddy said we weren't allowed.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.25,0:38:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来汤米问我是不是不敢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And then Tommy dared me.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.76,0:38:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And here we are.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.93,0:38:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不毛之地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nowhere land.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.61,0:38:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎很难给如此完美的地方想个合适的名字\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That seems hardly a fitting name for a place so full.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:40.52,0:38:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看不到吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can't you see it?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.84,0:38:44.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你没看得不够仔细\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Perhaps you're not looking hard enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.20,0:38:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}At what?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.22,0:38:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有白色教堂的小镇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The town with the white church.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.57,0:38:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听听  你听不到它的钟声吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Listen. Can't you hear its bell?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:56.30,0:38:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.58,0:39:00.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在听到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, I can hear it now.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.53,0:39:01.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.06,0:39:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你应该能听到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought you might.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.90,0:39:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到无聊的人的想象力了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You see what a bored mind can conjure?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.90,0:39:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}1973年电影中也曾出现响尾蛇桥段
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.14,0:39:24.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是怎么做到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How did you do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:27.32,0:39:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是魔术吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is it magic?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.48,0:39:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个世界的一切都是魔术\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everything in this world is magic,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:31.94,0:39:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了魔术师之外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}except to the magician.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.33,0:39:45.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好先回家吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Best you head home now.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.88,0:39:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是汤米不会相信...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But Tommy's not going to believe--
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.36,0:39:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会再回来这里了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're not going to come back here again, are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.02,0:39:57.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:57.76,0:39:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Run along, now.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:51.13,0:40:52.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不在办公室里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You weren't at your office.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.34,0:40:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你还是找到我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You seem to have found me anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:58.06,0:40:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-之前...  -过去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Listen, earlier-- - Forget it.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:30.14,0:41:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多待一会  我们聊聊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stay a little longer. We can talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:33.37,0:41:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们从来不聊天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We never talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:35.08,0:41:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我是认真的  -我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I'm serious. - So am I.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:40.84,0:41:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你总是喜欢长时间地保持若有所思的沉默\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're certainly a man comfortable with long, pensive silences.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:46.11,0:41:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是讽刺的是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Although, ironically,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:49.08,0:41:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你创造的产物却喜欢说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}your creations never shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:51.31,0:41:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们总是互相交谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're always talking to each other,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:55.08,0:41:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使周围没有游客也是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}even when there are no guests around.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:58.17,0:42:00.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们总是想要纠错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're always trying to error correct.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:01.92,0:42:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让自己更人性化一些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Make themselves more human.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.06,0:42:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们的相互交谈只是一种练习方式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When they talk to each other, it's a way of practicing.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:08.32,0:42:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你现在在做的事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is that what you're doing now?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:10.82,0:42:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,练习\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Practicing?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:23.14,0:42:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,质保经理告诉我们她被废弃了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}QA told us she was being decommissioned.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:25.23,0:42:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你帮质保经理做事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you work for QA?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:26.53,0:42:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, but--
Dialogue: 0,0:42:27.26,0:42:29.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,运行快速诊断程序\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Run a fast-pass diagnostic.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:33.19,0:42:35.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All righty.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:37.69,0:42:41.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一些不影响运行的口吃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Some non-affect hesitation.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.55,0:42:43.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点认知失调\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Little cognitive D.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:44.18,0:42:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,存在大量的攻击性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And a fuck load of aggression,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:45.50,0:42:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用来应对故事线里那些白痴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}courtesy of those morons in narrative.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.60,0:42:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会暴力相向  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't need to be aggro, do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:52.44,0:42:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是你很快懂得了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just a quicker study of
Dialogue: 0,0:42:53.84,0:42:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不让那些压抑的混蛋走进那扇门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}those repressed fucks walking through the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:56.94,0:42:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保存这个配置\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Archive this configuration.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:59.10,0:43:00.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打开她的基元\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Open up her primaries.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:01.07,0:43:03.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,认知能力  情感敏锐度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Perception. Emotional acuity.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:04.76,0:43:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提高\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bump it.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:06.40,0:43:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,百分之1.5\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}1.5%
Dialogue: 0,0:43:09.36,0:43:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-正在上传  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Updating. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:12.91,0:43:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们会做梦吗  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Do they dream? - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:15.45,0:43:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在她的描述中  她说过她做了梦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In her story, she said she dreamed.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:17.94,0:43:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们让他们做梦吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do we make them dream?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:19.78,0:43:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样做有什么意义\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fuck would be the point of that?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:22.76,0:43:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦境主要来自记忆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dreams are mainly memories.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:24.63,0:43:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想看  如果这些可怜的机器人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you imagine how fucked we'd be if these poor assholes
Dialogue: 0,0:43:26.82,0:43:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得游客对他们所做的事  那该多郁闷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}ever remembered what the guests do to them?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:30.83,0:43:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的确赋予了他们梦境概念\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We do give them the concept of dreams.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:34.28,0:43:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤其是恶梦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Specifically nightmares.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:36.69,0:43:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:38.12,0:43:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以防有人忘记\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just in case somebody forgets to
Dialogue: 0,0:43:39.14,0:43:41.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在维护期结束后  清除他们的数据\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}wipe them out at the end of a maintenance session.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:41.75,0:43:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果她有做梦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If she's got any dreams,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:42.80,0:43:44.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只可能是人体车间那些粗心的混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it's just of those sloppy fucks down
Dialogue: 0,0:43:44.33,0:43:46.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又给她添了点什么东西上去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in the body shop patching her back together again.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:48.28,0:43:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她有一些肢体不适\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's got some physical discomfort.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:51.34,0:43:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要求在她下次轮换时 做详细的肢体检查\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Put in a request for a full physical at her next rotation.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:56.52,0:43:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  美人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, gorgeous,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:58.45,0:44:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以回归赛场了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you're back to the races.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:00.15,0:44:04.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三  二  一  醒来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're gonna wake in three, two, one.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:04.52,0:44:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我逃跑了  越过大洋到达彼岸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So I ran away, crossed the shining sea.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:08.79,0:44:11.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我终于踏上坚实的大地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And when I finally set foot back on solid ground,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:11.40,0:44:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一个听到的就是那该死的声音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the first thing I heard was that voice.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:15.07,0:44:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道那声音说了什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you know what it said?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:17.86,0:44:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It said...
Dialogue: 0,0:44:20.17,0:44:23.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是新世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}this is the new world.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:24.89,0:44:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个世界里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And in this world...
Dialogue: 0,0:44:28.37,0:44:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以做任何自己想做的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you can be whoever the fuck you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:50.52,0:44:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他似乎深信不疑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, he seemed convinced.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:54.95,0:44:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道我在下船时听到的第一个声音是谁的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know the first voice I heard when I got off that boat?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:58.69,0:45:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}美国路易斯安那州首府
Dialogue: 0,0:44:58.69,0:45:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个来自巴吞鲁日的年轻人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A nice young man from Baton Rouge
Dialogue: 0,0:45:00.97,0:45:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说我靠胯下每天能帮他赚两块大洋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}said my pussy could earn him two whole dollars a day.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:04.01,0:45:06.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会非常乐意分给我其中的30%\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And he'd be more than happy to let me have up to 30%.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:07.39,0:45:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我猜你可以把撒谎加进你的恶行清单了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, then I guess you could add lying to your list of sins.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:11.48,0:45:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七宗罪唯一的问题就在于\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The only thing wrong with the seven deadly sins
Dialogue: 0,0:45:13.70,0:45:15.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不够多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is that there aren't more of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:16.36,0:45:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到这个话题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And while we're on the subject,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:17.57,0:45:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我比你更容易洗白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}my transgressions wash off a little easier than yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:22.29,0:45:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少我的姑娘们和男人做完\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}At least when my girls are done with a man,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:24.62,0:45:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还有口气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}he's still left drawing breath.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:27.36,0:45:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大部分是这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For the most part.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:28.77,0:45:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈离我的桌子远一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get the fuck away from my table.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:31.23,0:45:33.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操你妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, fuck you!
Dialogue: 0,0:45:33.26,0:45:34.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, in that case...
Dialogue: 0,0:45:37.05,0:45:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬我们的鲁莽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...here's to our indiscretions.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:39.09,0:45:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操蛋的一夜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...fucking bullshit for one night.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:40.70,0:45:41.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把这里的人都杀了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll shoot everyone in this dump...
Dialogue: 0,0:45:41.91,0:45:43.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬这样或那样的罪恶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Spoken and otherwise.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:01.89,0:46:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个操蛋的假期\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now that's a fucking vacation!
Dialogue: 0,0:49:14.55,0:49:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Three,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:17.78,0:49:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}two,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:21.02,0:49:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}one.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:36.81,0:49:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Found it.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:38.93,0:49:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她肚子里有金黄色葡萄球菌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's MRSA in her abdomen.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:42.54,0:49:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那帮畜生没清理干净\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Filthy fucking animals not cleaning up.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:44.77,0:49:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难怪到处都是苍蝇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No wonder we have a fucking fly problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:47.07,0:49:50.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别看我  我最爱干净了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't look at me. I'm the king of hygiene.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:51.78,0:49:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bullshit.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:53.49,0:49:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看见你刚粘上了什么黏糊糊的东西在那儿冲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've seen you. You just glop that shit on and rinse.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:56.09,0:49:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你懂的  肥皂要用手搓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You understand, soap is mechanical.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:58.94,0:50:01.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你他妈在说什么  -泡沫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Fuck are you talking about? - Bubbles.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:01.23,0:50:03.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你没搓出泡沫  那就算没洗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you're not making the little bubbles, you're not doing shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:03.95,0:50:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操  操  怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fuck! Fuck! What the fuck?!
Dialogue: 0,0:50:05.83,0:50:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-该死的  -怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Shit! - What the fuck?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:14.57,0:50:16.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No. Oh, fuck.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:19.97,0:50:23.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻逼  你忘了让她进入睡眠模式了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Asshole, you forgot to put her in sleep mode.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:25.84,0:50:27.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别别别\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't, don't, don't!
Dialogue: 0,0:50:27.55,0:50:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No! No, no, no!
Dialogue: 0,0:50:28.54,0:50:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别别别\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't! Don't, don't, don't, don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:32.10,0:50:34.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手  把那个放下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stop. Put that down!
Dialogue: 0,0:50:34.25,0:50:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你损坏了她脑子里的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You break anything in her head,
Dialogue: 0,0:50:35.36,0:50:36.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得填损害报告了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we have to file a damage report.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:36.48,0:50:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我们和她谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh, okay, let's talk to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:39.44,0:50:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她叫啥  -梅芙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What's her name? - Maeve!
Dialogue: 0,0:50:40.93,0:50:42.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  梅芙  梅芙  你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hi, Maeve. Maeve, hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:42.92,0:50:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要冷静下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, uh, you gotta calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:45.82,0:50:48.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗  坐下来  我们能帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay? Let's sit down and we can help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:48.06,0:50:49.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈的别碰我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Keep your fucking hands off me.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:53.60,0:50:54.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:32.13,0:52:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发誓我让她进入睡眠模式了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I swear I put it in sleep mode.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:33.24,0:52:35.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这他妈的看起来是睡眠模式吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, does this look like fucking sleep mode?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:37.49,0:52:40.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈冷静一下  帮我移下这个  东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Calm the fuck down and help me move this... thing
Dialogue: 0,0:52:40.98,0:52:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别让别人看到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}before someone sees.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:09.04,0:53:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:40.29,0:53:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}15世纪的荷兰超现实主义画家  画作多描绘罪恶与人类道德的沦丧
Dialogue: 0,0:53:40.29,0:53:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这条故事线会让耶罗尼米斯·博斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This storyline will make {\u1}Hieronymus Bosch{\u0}
Dialogue: 0,0:53:43.22,0:53:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都自惭形秽的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}look like he was doodling kittens.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:46.36,0:53:50.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情节有活体解剖  自我蚕食\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have vivisection, self-cannibalism,
Dialogue: 0,0:53:50.55,0:53:54.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一点特殊的东西我把它称之为  衔尾人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a special little something I call the "Whoroborus."
Dialogue: 0,0:53:54.58,0:53:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想显得太自负\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, I don't want to appear immodest,
Dialogue: 0,0:53:57.76,0:54:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这是这个乐园所能提供的最极限的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but this is the apex of what the park could provide--
Dialogue: 0,0:54:03.50,0:54:05.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-恐怖  -错过什么有趣的了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- horror... - Miss anything interesting?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:05.04,0:54:07.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浪漫  兴奋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...romance, titillation.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:07.21,0:54:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,李正在表演不自负\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lee not appearing immodest.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:09.36,0:54:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们最在行的游客会一路打到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Our most skilled guests will fight their ways
Dialogue: 0,0:54:11.82,0:54:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乐园的外围\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to the outer limits of the park,
Dialogue: 0,0:54:13.78,0:54:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最可怕的印第安勇士  诱人的未婚少女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}besting fearsome braves, seducing nubile maidens,
Dialogue: 0,0:54:18.26,0:54:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结交到注定命运多舛的同伴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}befriending tragically ill-fated sidekicks,
Dialogue: 0,0:54:21.54,0:54:23.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且  当然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and, of course,
Dialogue: 0,0:54:24.01,0:54:26.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像我们这些年来最棒的故事线一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}like all our best narratives over the years,
Dialogue: 0,0:54:26.71,0:54:29.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的游客将会幸运地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}our guests will have the privilege
Dialogue: 0,0:54:29.11,0:54:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解到他们最感兴趣的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}of getting to know the character they're most interested in--
Dialogue: 0,0:54:32.60,0:54:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}themselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:34.53,0:54:38.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以上就是令游客们将会沉迷的下一个景点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I present our guests' next obsession:
Dialogue: 0,0:54:39.01,0:54:41.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红河上的奥德赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Odyssey on Red River.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:52.27,0:54:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:54.29,0:54:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:55.99,0:54:57.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不这么想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I don't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:57.78,0:54:59.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wait, you don't think--
Dialogue: 0,0:54:59.62,0:55:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它的意义的什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is the point of it?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:01.40,0:55:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点廉价的刺激\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get a couple of cheap thrills?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:04.16,0:55:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一些惊喜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Some surprises?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:06.18,0:55:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这不够\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But it's not enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:08.56,0:55:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是给予游客们你以为他们想要的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not about giving the guests what you think they want.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:11.42,0:55:12.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  这太简单了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, that's simple.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:13.21,0:55:16.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兴奋  恐怖  得意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The titillation, horror, elation--
Dialogue: 0,0:55:17.58,0:55:18.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这都只是小把戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they're parlor tricks.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:19.68,0:55:24.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游客们不会因为一眼就能看到的东西再来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The guests don't return for the obvious things we do,
Dialogue: 0,0:55:24.70,0:55:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些花哨的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the garish things.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:28.17,0:55:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会再来是因为那些细微的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They come back because of the subtleties,
Dialogue: 0,0:55:33.57,0:55:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些细节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the details.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:37.44,0:55:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会再来是因为他们发现了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They come back because they discover
Dialogue: 0,0:55:39.98,0:55:44.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们从没想象过  从未注意过的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}something they imagine no on had ever noticed before...
Dialogue: 0,0:55:48.99,0:55:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们已经爱上的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}something they've fallen in love with.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:54.25,0:55:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不是在寻求一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're not looking for a story
Dialogue: 0,0:55:55.76,0:55:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉他们是谁的故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that tells them who they are.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:59.38,0:56:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们已经知道自己是谁了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They already know who they are.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:08.59,0:56:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们来这里是因为他们想要领悟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're here because they want a glimpse
Dialogue: 0,0:56:11.52,0:56:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己能成为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}of who they could be.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:13.95,0:56:14.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Billy!
Dialogue: 0,0:56:16.22,0:56:17.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:23.87,0:56:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的故事唯一告诉我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The only thing your story tells me,
Dialogue: 0,0:56:26.56,0:56:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希斯摩尔先生  就是你是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mr. Sizemore, is who you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:36.65,0:56:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里没有一个能令你感兴趣吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, isn't there anything you like about it?
Dialogue: 0,0:56:43.69,0:56:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些靴子的尺码是多少\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What size are those boots?
Dialogue: 0,0:56:53.47,0:56:55.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想说什么  罗威先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Something you want to say, Mr. Lowe?
Dialogue: 0,0:56:55.90,0:56:57.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-董事会  先生  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- The board, sir. - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:56:58.31,0:57:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可能会触怒一些人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This might ruffle some feathers.
Dialogue: 0,0:57:00.90,0:57:02.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你承诺给他们新的故事线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You promised them a new storyline.
Dialogue: 0,0:57:03.09,0:57:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会得到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They shall have one.
Dialogue: 0,0:57:05.23,0:57:07.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个我已经做了一些时日的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Something I've been working on for some time.
Dialogue: 0,0:57:11.71,0:57:13.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常独到的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Something quite original.
