( theme music playing )
Charlie:
Dad.
Wake up.
I must've drifted off.
Where were we?
- The madman.
- Oh.
Of course.
( grunts )
The Hatter...
who says,
"If I had
a world of my own,
everything
would be nonsense.
Nothing would be
what it is
because everything
would be what it isn't."
Everything would be
what it isn't?
Even me.
- ( monitor beeping )
- Hey.
You're perfect.
You're gonna
beat this.
Hmm?
I promise you.
Now, let's skip
to something fun.
Dad.
- What is it, Charlie?
- Listen to me.
Listen.
Charlie?
- ( alarm beeping )
- Charlie!
Bernard: And finally,
have you ever questioned
the nature of your reality?
No.
Good.
( beeps )
( sighs )
Now, then,
I see you had
a blacklisted exchange
with a guest
in the course
of your narrative.
Can you tell me
what happened?
He said he wanted
to cut off a piece of me
to take home
in his carry-on,
that he wanted to mount it
on the hood of his car
for his friends to see.
I told him
if he wanted a trophy,
I could cut pieces of him off
and let him fish for them
in the Olvido.
And did this exchange
make you question anything
about your world?
No.
This world
is as doomed as ever.
And just for
my peace of mind...
Anything about these images
that jumps out to you?
They don't look
like anything to me.
We're through
15% of the backlog.
As it stands, we should
be caught up by end of day.
- Good.
- And, uh, when you're
done here, sir,
there's a priority request
for him from management.
Have you seen Elsie?
She was supposed to give me
a hand on something.
No. Uh, according
to the system,
she started
her leave today.
Is there something
I could help you with?
No, thanks.
( train whistle blows )
Raise.
I'll call.
You're calling
with that shit?
Dolores, why don't
you play a hand?
You're wasting
your breath.
Girl's harboring
a grudge.
I don't blame you,
sweetheart.
I did some ugly things
to you both.
But it wasn't personal.
Confederados
and the government like
to call this thing a war,
but they're fighting
starving farmers
armed with rocks.
That ain't no war.
It's a slaughter.
If I had to do it
all again,
I'd fuck you both over
just as hard.
Well, I guess we know
where you stand.
Don't pretend
like you're so innocent.
Way I recollect,
y'all came to me,
looking to join up
with those crooked assholes
and their war effort.
Not our idea.
My friend wanted--
I guess he wanted to see
what was at the end
of all this.
And yet,
here you are.
Your friend
didn't make it this far.
Maybe you've got
more of an appetite
for this than you think.
William.
What is it?
We're in Ghost Nation
territory.
Most savage tribe
there is.
Those are the folks
who came calling without
an invitation.
You mean exactly what
we're doing right now?
( metal clangs )
The train's
the only way through.
On foot we'll be dead
in under an hour.
( rifle clicks )
As soon as we're clear
of their territory,
we can stop.
You can come with me.
Nothing here on out
but slaughter.
( line ringing )
Man's voice: The user
you are trying to access
cannot be located.
Say "message"
to transcribe a message.
You wanted to see me?
Is everything okay?
You left rather
abruptly last night.
Was there something
you wanted to tell me?
No, I don't think so.
Hale is looking over
every department
and yours is running behind
on diagnostics.
It would be best
if we presented
at least a semblance
of professionalism while
the board is here.
We'll be fine.
My people know
how to do their jobs.
If they applied
half as much energy
to their work
as they have to second-guessing
my team's investigation--
That's all over.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Good.
You doing okay?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
( man and woman moaning,
grunting )
( thudding )
( both panting )
I'm sorry.
I thought you
requested a meeting.
- My mistake.
- I did.
Come in.
( panting )
Get back here.
Bring your friend.
What about you?
What turns of fate--
- ( beeps )
- ( powers down )
I could come back later
if this isn't a good time.
This won't take long.
( door closes )
Theresa, you've always
been good at your job
and the board
has been impressed
with your performance so far,
which is why we were
so surprised by this
woodcutter mess.
A small setback.
He slipped on a fucking rock
and bashed his own head in
while basically on top
of a behavior tech.
Meanwhile,
Ford is suddenly using
half the park's resources
to build
some new narrative?
Can I bum a cigarette?
God, I see why
you took these up again.
Let me remind you
of something.
This place, the people
who work here are nothing.
Our interest
in this place is entirely
in the intellectual property.
The code.
The hosts' minds,
the storylines--
I don't give a rat's ass
about the hosts.
It's our little
research project
that Delos cares about.
That's where
the real value is.
And due to
a lack of foresight
on part of one
of my predecessors,
35 years
of information--
raw information--
exists here.
Nowhere else.
Ford has always
ensured that.
Now, you are
a smart enough woman.
Tell me,
why would we need you
to secure all of it?
Because you're
going to fire him.
You don't fire someone
who created an empire.
You ask him
to retire politely.
And if that person
has the ability to
snap his fingers
and erase the value
of that empire,
you have to make sure
you have a contingency.
So, you and I
need to ensure
that by the time
the rest of the board arrives,
we are on course
for that transition.
Okay?
I like you.
Well, not personally,
but I like you for this job,
which is why I'm gonna
give you another chance
to get a handle
on this particular
bitch of a situation.
But the gods...
they require
a blood sacrifice.
We need to demonstrate
just how dangerous
Ford's creations
can be.
No.
( chuckles )
No, nothing so obvious.
We need someone
thoroughly unexpected.
( piano playing )
( chatter )
( piano stops )
I told you never open
your mouth that wide
unless someone's
paying you for it.
Sorry, Maeve.
I didn't sleep much
last night.
What are these nightmares
you have about?
Do you ever dream
you're someone else?
I don't think so.
Why?
You ever thought about
whether this is really
the life you want?
I don't
intend to make this
my life's work.
No offense.
Mm.
My family's
got a farm.
Bad soil.
Nothing grows.
I send money
back to them.
They think I work
in a dress shop.
( chuckles )
What's wrong?
I'm just doing
what you told me to.
A couple more years
of this and...
then I can have
whatever life I want.
I'm gonna get my family
out of the desert.
We're gonna go
somewhere...
cold.
Someday.
( door opens )
Man:
Which one is it?
Man #2:
It's the one
at the bar. Go.
Quick, before
the guests upstairs
finish up.
Whatever she did,
it must've been serious
if they're making us
grab her in broad daylight.
( tablet beeping )
Man #2:
We got her.
Let's go.
( chatter resumes )
You're supposed
to be resting.
We're riding a train
full with explosives
through scalping territory.
Not sleepy.
Can I ask you
something?
This place
you're looking for,
what makes you
so sure it exists?
I'm not.
My life before,
I was so sure of the world.
But now it feels
like a lie.
Only thing I know
is whatever's out there,
I'm never going back.
What is it
you're looking for?
Lawrence is right.
You could've
stayed in Pariah
or gone back,
but you're here.
With me.
( chuckles )
The only thing I had
when I was a kid
were books.
I used to live in them.
I used to go to sleep
dreaming I'd wake up
inside one of them
'cause they had
meaning.
This place,
this is like I woke up
inside one of those stories.
I guess I just wanna
find out what it means.
I don't wanna be
in a story.
All I want is to not
look forward or back.
I just wanna be...
in the moment I'm in.
Dolores,
back home,
there's a woman, Juliet,
and her father
owns the company
where I work.
She's, uh,
Logan's sister.
Yeah.
And when I get home,
we're getting married.
Oh.
The place you're after,
I will help you find it.
But I can't stay.
I have a life
waiting for me.
I'm sorry.
Of course.
Dolores.
I've been pretending
my whole life.
Pretending I don't mind,
pretending I belong.
My life's built on it.
And it's a good life.
It's a life I've always wanted.
But then I came here
and I get a glimpse
for a second
of a life in which
I don't have to pretend.
A life in which
I can be truly alive.
How can I go back
to pretending
when I know
what this feels like?
( both panting )
( gasps )
Dr. Ford:
Miss Hale.
I was not aware those
with your level of insight
needed any more
reflection.
Dr. Ford.
Always charming.
What is this?
Apparently, Miss Cullen
and Miss Hale
have a presentation
for us.
What about?
Following the recent reports
of host malfunction,
we asked QA to check
the last abortive update,
which featured
the reveries,
- as I believe
they're called.
- Mm-hmm.
I'm sorry to report
that Miss Cullen
and her team
uncovered some
worrisome findings.
In the course
of our code review,
we found something
quite disturbing.
Wake her up.
We set Clementine Pennyfeather
back to her previous update.
When we discovered
the build was buggy
due to a last-minute injection
of the reverie code,
we quickly rolled
all the infected hosts
back to their prior builds.
Mm, you're new.
Not much
of a rind on you.
( grunts )
( labored breathing )
- No!
- ( grunts )
No! No!
No, no.
( gasping )
No, no, no...
( gasps, grunts )
Please. Please.
Help me!
Please, please, please!
- No! ( screams )
- All right, that's enough.
Freeze.
As you've no doubt
gathered,
our tech is,
in fact, a host.
One that has been coded
for the purposes of
this simulation
to read as a human.
And as you can see,
behavioral safeguards
are operating
exactly as you would expect.
Reset her.
Wipe her memory.
( gasps )
Okay, let's do this
again.
( inhales, gasps )
You're new.
Not much
of a rind on you.
( grunting )
- ( bone cracks )
- ( screams )
( metal clanging )
( man groaning )
( screaming )
- Stubbs:
That's enough, sweetheart.
- ( gun cocks )
That's enough.
Freeze
all motor functions.
( sighs )
- ( gunshot )
- ( gasps )
In each case we examined,
the malfunctioning hosts
were not resetting
properly.
The retention of data
that hadn't been wiped
overloaded their
decision-making apparatus,
eventually causing
a system failure
that allowed for override
of their primary rule set.
The concern
with the reveries
is that
the hosts will remember
some of their experiences
and act on them.
You're telling us
that these hosts
were responding
to a grudge?
That's exactly
what I'm saying,
Mr. Lowe.
And funny you should use
that particular word,
"grudge,"
since what was
most troubling to me
was that several techs
in behavior
voiced these
exact same concerns
to the head
of their department.
You put this code out
without proper vetting
and without reasonable
understanding of its
ramifications.
So, either you
didn't write it
or you're
getting sloppy
to the point of risking
the lives of our guests.
Few things surprise me
anymore, Mr. Lowe,
but this level of negligence
is fucking breathtaking.
We are way beyond
rollback territory.
Within the next
six months,
we'll need
to rebuild the hosts
from the ground up.
You want us
to lobotomize them
is what you're saying.
No, not you, Mr. Lowe.
After all, this was
your responsibility,
assuming that you have
nothing to share with us
in terms
of your culpability.
No.
Then you're fired.
( chuckles )
William:
Hey.
Morning, William.
I-- I didn't
wanna wake you.
I know...
last night
was unexpected.
If you regret it...
I don't regret a thing.
I know you have someone
waiting for you at home.
All that feels
so unreal now.
I used to think this place
was all about...
pandering to your
baser instincts.
Now I understand.
It doesn't cater
to your lowest self,
it reveals
your deepest self.
It shows you
who you really are.
You remember
the look on Logan's face
when we left him behind?
Do you know how long
I've wanted to do that,
to let him know
what I think of him?
And you,
last night,
I've never
felt that way before,
not with any woman.
You've unlocked
something in me.
I'm not a key,
William.
I'm just me.
What is that?
I don't know.
At home,
I used to paint.
Landscapes mostly,
but I was always just...
copying the world
outside me.
This morning,
I woke up and I thought...
"What if I drew
something new?"
I imagined
something beautiful.
A place where
the mountains meet the sea.
Everyone who comes here
is longing for excitement
or conflict,
and you're just...
dreaming of the opposite.
Well, what about you,
William?
What do you dream of?
- ( brakes screeching )
- ( William grunts )
( hissing )
( grunts )
Yah!
( horse neighs )
What is it?
- Ambush.
- Is it the Ghost Nation?
Worse.
The Confederados.
( glass shattering )
( chuckles )
( latch clicks )
( horse snorting )
Fucking coward.
Vaya con dios,
motherfuckers.
- ( grunts )
- ( horses neighing )
( gunfire )
They're making a run for it!
Come on, boys, get up!
- ( gunfire continues )
- Lawrence: Come on,
stay close!
( horse neighs )
Ah!
( gasps, grunts )
( panting )
Confederado:
Go, boys!
Yah!
William:
Dolores!
( Dolores grunting )
Confederado:
Go, go! Take 'em down!
( Gatling gun firing )
Go, go!
( groans, grunts )
- ( arrows thudding )
- ( grunts )
Ghost Nation!
( natives whooping )
( horse neighs )
Ah!
Let's go!
Stop, William!
Stop!
( horse neighs )
It's real...
what I dreamt.
It's the place you drew.
Lawrence:
You coming?
Once the Ghosts
is done acquainting themselves
with those poor bastards,
they'll be
coming after us.
My friends here are itching
to join the war effort.
Think I've had
enough of war.
How about you?
You got a knack
for killing.
I'm afraid this
is where we part ways.
Careful.
If you're heading west
across that river,
you may be leaving
the fighting behind,
but you're gonna be
in unclaimed territories.
What's out that way?
You're gonna have
to ask the dust.
Ain't nothing
ever come back from there.
( horse neighs )
( monitor beeping )
We're almost done here.
Why don't I close up?
Lutz:
You've been topside
for less than 24 hours.
You keep
coming down this often,
people are going to notice.
- Where's Clem?
- I don't know.
I haven't seen her.
Why?
Find her.
Now.
What?
Where is she?
I don't know.
She's here.
Let's go.
We can't.
The brass will be there.
You don't want
to fuck with me, Felix.
Take me there now.
Slow down.
Tilt your head back,
please, Clem.
- Is there a problem?
- No.
( drill whirring )
Sylvester:
Sorry.
Theresa.
May I have a word?
Sure.
( drill stops )
I appreciate
your professionalism,
but you really don't
need to bother with this,
given the change
in your employment status.
The test was a sham.
The little show
you and Hale put on?
Completely transparent
from a technical perspective,
clumsy to the point of
making me embarrassed for you.
- Embarrassed?
- If I saw through it,
I can only imagine
what Ford was thinking.
There were glaringly
obvious markers
of human intervention
in the code.
If your programmers
were any good, they'd
be working for me.
And I know you and your team
were responsible for the stray
and its satellite
transmission.
- Bernie--
- I don't care.
40 years ago,
Ford's partner
wrote half the code
this place was founded on.
What you said
in the lab
was right.
We don't know
how the hosts work,
and I think there's
something wrong with them.
Ford's explanation
only bolsters my hunch.
The ability to deviate
from program behavior
arises out of the host's
recall of past iterations.
You're thinking
there's a connection
between memory and--
And improvisation, yes.
Out of repetition
comes variation.
And after countless
cycles of repetition,
these hosts,
they were varying.
They were on the verge
of some kind of change.
You have to know
my chief concern
has always been
the well-being of this park
and the people in it.
I know.
Which is why I need
to show you something.
( elevator beeps )
- Sylvester: Talk to her.
- Lutz: You first.
Look, I didn't want
to retire her.
I know she's,
like, your friend,
or-- I guess.
( sighs )
But-- but
if I didn't do it,
they-- they'd just
get someone else to,
and then they'd be
suspicious of me, so...
so I said yes.
But I did it
for you.
Always doing things
for other people,
aren't you?
Time to do
one more thing.
What?
All my life,
I've prided myself
on being a survivor.
But surviving
is just another loop.
I'm getting out of here.
You two are going
to help me.
( scoffs )
No. Do...
Do you know how far
these people will go
to protect their IP?
Every part of this building,
including the skin on your back,
is made
to keep you here.
( sighs )
It-- it'd be
a suicide mission.
At first, I thought you
and the others were gods.
Then I realized
you're just men.
And I know men.
You think I'm scared
of death?
I've done it
a million times.
I'm fucking
great at it.
How many times
have you died?
Because if you don't
help me...
I'll kill you.
( chuckles )
If there's a problem
in the park,
should we bring
a security team?
Who would we trust?
Thought I could trust you,
for instance.
I'm not going to explain
myself to you, Bernard.
I was charged with
safeguarding the park's
intellectual property.
Why would it be in danger?
You were the only one
who was stealing it.
Delos owns
the hosts' minds,
the storylines,
decades of work.
Ford never
allowed any of it
to be backed up off-site.
All of this
could've been destroyed.
In the event of what?
Ford is done,
Bernard.
The board has indulged him
for long enough.
He is done.
The corporation
was concerned
he'd destroy
all of the park's IP
on his way out the door.
You think I would've let him
destroy all of the hosts,
all of our work?
There's far more
at stake here than
the hosts' profiles.
Do you really think
the corporation's
interest here
are tourists
playing cowboy?
The longer I work here,
the more I think
I understand the hosts.
It's the human beings
who confuse me.
( crickets chirping )
This building isn't
in any survey of the park.
That's because we use hosts
to do most of the surveys.
They're programmed
to ignore this place.
They literally
couldn't see it
if they were
staring right at it.
And these unregistered hosts
you told me about?
I don't know.
He may have moved them.
What's behind
this door?
What door?
Theresa:
What is this place?
Bernard:
It's a remote
diagnostic facility.
Ford and his partner
used them when the park
was in beta.
I had no idea
this one was here.
The cottage must've
been built on top of it.
But this equipment.
This is newer.
Slower
than our machines
back at the mesa,
but it will render a host
in a few days.
So, Ford's been making
his own hosts out here
and telling no one.
What's the matter?
Um...
Have you seen these?
What is this, Bernard?
Doesn't look
like anything to me.
Dr. Ford:
They cannot see the things
that will hurt them.
I've spared them that.
Their lives are blissful.
In a way, their existence
is purer than ours,
freed of the burden
of self-doubt.
No, no, no, no.
I don't understand.
You're a fucking
monster.
Am I?
Well, you were the one
who would so blithely
destroy all of them,
even him, I suppose.
After everything
you have shared.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Is that why...?
Did you tell him to--?
Dr. Ford:
The intimacies
were your idea,
if you will recall.
I think Bernard
was glad of the company.
Bernard:
I'm not one.
I can't be.
My wife.
My son.
The burial.
I was a father.
My poor boy.
( labored breathing )
That's enough, Bernard.
( powers down )
You mustn't get
yourself worked up.
I read a theory once
that the human intellect
was like peacock feathers.
Just an extravagant display
intended to attract a mate.
All of art, literature,
a bit of Mozart,
William Shakespeare,
Michelangelo,
and the Empire
State Building--
just an elaborate
mating ritual.
Maybe
it doesn't matter
that we have
accomplished so much
for the basest
of reasons.
But, of course,
the peacock can barely fly.
It lives in the dirt,
pecking insects out of the muck,
consoling itself
with its great beauty.
I have come to think of
so much of consciousness
as a burden,
a weight,
and we have
spared them that.
Anxiety,
self-loathing, guilt.
The hosts are the ones
who are free.
Free here
under my control.
But he's not
under your control.
He brought me here
to show me this.
No. He brought you here
because I asked him to.
He's been very loyal
for many years.
Your time
running this place
like your insane
little kingdom
is over.
You've been playing God
for long enough.
I simply wanted
to tell my stories.
It was you people
who wanted to play God
with your
little undertaking.
Do you really think
the board will stand
for this?
( chuckles )
The board
will do nothing.
Our arrangement
is too valuable to them.
They test me
every now and then.
I think they enjoy
the sport of it.
This time,
they sent you.
Sadly, in order
to restore things,
the situation demands
a blood sacrifice.
See, Arnold and I
designed every part
of this place.
It was our dream.
Did you really think
I would let you
take it from me?
This is what happened
to Arnold?
Did you have Bernard
take him out into the woods?
No, he wasn't here
in those days.
Were you, Bernard?
( beeping )
Like I said,
I built all of this.
I'm afraid our guest
has grown weary.
Perhaps you can
help her, Bernard.
No.
"And in that sleep,
what dreams may come."
Bernard.
No. No!
Please! Please!
( crying )
- ( screaming ) No!
- ( thuds )
( thuds )
Dr. Ford:
We should be
getting back, Bernard.
We have a great deal
of work to do
on the new storylines.
( music playing )