[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: 
Original Script: 
Synch Point: 1
ScriptType: v4.00+
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.08,0:25:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\bord0\alpha&70\shad0\fscx0\fscy0\t(0,500,\fscx12\fscy14\t(24500,25000,\fscx0\fscy0))\p1\c&HFFEBD1&\move(14,0,365,0,13500,15000)}m 195 227 l 228 227 l 149 147 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 180 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 l 163 71 m 134 164 l 195 227 l 228 227 l 150 148 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 177 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 {\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.08,0:25:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\shad0\alpha&70\fscx0\fscy0\t(0,500,\fscx8\fscy10\t(24500,25000,\fscx0\fscy0))\p1\c&HFFDF57&\move(15.7,32,366.7,32,13500,15000)\org(20,8)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.08,0:25:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\alpha&DD\bord0\shad0\fscx19\fscy20\p1\1a&H3D&\c&HFFFFFF&\blur10\move(3,31,353,31,13500,15000)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.08,0:25:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\bord0\shad0\fs14\b0\alpha70\frx3690\clip(5,6,380,38)\t(500,1000,\frx0\t(13500,15000,\clip(380,6,380,38)))\pos(28.385,21.386)}第一时间下载{\c&H00DEFF&}无删减美剧  {\c&HFFFFFF&}必须登录字幕组网站{\b1\c&HFFDF57&}www.zimuzu.tv
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.08,0:25:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an6\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\bord0\shad0\fs14\b0\alpha70\clip(380,6,380,38)\t(0,1500,\clip(5,6,380,38)\t(9500,10000,\frx3600))\pos(353.473,21.386)\b1\c&HFFDF57&}www.zimuzu.tv  {\c&HFFFFFF&}更好更快的原创翻译 双语字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.56,0:00:10.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}根总迷弟·少年·POI永生
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.56,0:00:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}胡说大王
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.56,0:00:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}潇然
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.56,0:00:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}showeryhe
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.56,0:00:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}SophiaSaaaga
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.56,0:00:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}小酸奶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.56,0:00:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}小泡椒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.56,0:00:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}翻译 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}星星与野狗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.56,0:00:50.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}时间轴 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}倩倩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.56,0:00:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}时间轴 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}Poxle
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.56,0:01:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}校对 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}根总迷弟·少年·POI永生
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.56,0:01:05.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\b1\fs17\fn方正仿宋繁体\move(-245.4,260.627,20,260.627,0,500)\clip(18.667,0.713,384,288)}后期&总监 {\fs20\fn方正小标宋_GBK}灰灰是菇凉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.19,0:01:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(192,206.02,192,202)\bord0\shad0\fn思源黑体 CN Bold\c&HC0C3BB&\fs16\fscy80\t(0,0,1,\fs14)\fsp2}西部世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.91,0:01:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(500,500)\fn方正宋黑简体\fs17\c&HC0C3BB&}第一季  第四集
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.66,0:01:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徳洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dolores?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.23,0:02:00.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.81,0:02:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你现在在哪儿吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you know where you are?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.10,0:02:03.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.14,0:02:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在梦里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm in a dream.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.84,0:02:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在此之前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Before this,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.18,0:02:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道发生了什么事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}do you know what happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.52,0:02:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的父母\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My parents...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.24,0:02:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们伤害了他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They hurt them.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.22,0:02:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请控制下你的情绪反应\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Limit your emotional affect, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.46,0:02:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来发生了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What happened next?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.21,0:02:30.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后他们杀了他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then they killed them.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.33,0:02:33.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And then...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.33,0:02:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跑了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I ran.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.25,0:02:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我关心的人都不在了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everyone I cared about is gone...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.38,0:02:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内心好痛苦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and it hurts...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.64,0:02:47.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撕心裂肺\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so badly.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.28,0:02:51.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你愿意  我可以让那种感觉消失\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can make that feeling go away if you'd like.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.95,0:02:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为什么要那样呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why would I want that?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.22,0:02:58.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种痛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The pain,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.52,0:03:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失去他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}their loss...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.15,0:03:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是他们留给我唯一的东西了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it's all I have left of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.75,0:03:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为悲痛会让你的内心更弱小\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You think the grief will make you smaller inside,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.99,0:03:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像你的心彻底瓦解了  但其实并不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}like your heart will collapse in on itself, but it doesn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.92,0:03:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我内心又敞开了一片空间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I feel spaces opening up inside of me
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.48,0:03:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像一栋我从未探索过的带有很多房间的大楼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}like a building with rooms I've never explored.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.88,0:03:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那很美  徳洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's very pretty, Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.38,0:03:33.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我们预先写好的程序吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did we write that for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.16,0:03:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,部分是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In part.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.77,0:03:40.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我改编自一段关于爱的有剧本对话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I adapted it from a scripted dialogue about love.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.74,0:03:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在的这些想法  有什么不对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is there something wrong with these thoughts I'm having?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.47,0:03:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.28,0:04:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但真正做决定的人  并非只有我一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I'm not the only one making these decisions.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.83,0:04:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能帮助我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you help me?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.74,0:04:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, what is it that you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.39,0:04:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.88,0:04:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  这个世界...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But this world...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.01,0:04:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得这个世界或许有什么不对劲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think there may be something wrong with this world.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.59,0:04:21.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藏在表层之下的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Something hiding underneath.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.88,0:04:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么是那个原因...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Either that or...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.19,0:04:26.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么就是我有什么毛病\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or there's something wrong with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.12,0:04:34.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可能疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I may be losing my mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.69,0:04:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让你尝试一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's something I'd like you to try.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.52,0:04:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a game.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.58,0:04:56.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个秘密\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A secret.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.83,0:04:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫做...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's called...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.91,0:05:01.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷宫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the Maze.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.61,0:05:03.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么样的游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What kind of game is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.23,0:05:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一种非常独特的游戏  徳洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a very special kind of game, Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.09,0:05:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目标就是找到迷宫的中心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The goal is to find the center of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.97,0:05:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你能做到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you can do that,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.65,0:05:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那或许你可以获得自由\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}then maybe you can be free.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.74,0:05:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.25,0:05:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我想获得自由\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think I want to be free.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.70,0:05:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.57,0:06:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在想什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Penny for your thoughts.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.55,0:06:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有没有遇到过  有时候话到嘴边却不记得了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ever had something on the tip of your tongue,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.81,0:06:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你越是努力去想  就越是想不起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but the harder you try to remember it, the more it slips away?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.24,0:06:32.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大多数触碰到我嘴边的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Most things that touch the tip of my tongue,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.05,0:06:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都很乐意忘掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm happy to forget.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.98,0:06:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了那个来自阿比林的牛仔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Except that cowpoke from Abilene.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.10,0:06:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他胯下的那玩意儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That thing he was packing--
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.74,0:06:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是终身难忘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that was something to remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.92,0:06:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只记得  你给那个牛仔免单了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All I recall is you letting that cowpoke skip out on his bill.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.45,0:06:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  我该付钱给他才对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hell, I oughta been paying him.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.10,0:06:51.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他对那玩意儿的灵活使用简直...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The way he used that thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.69,0:07:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好压一压他们的兴致\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Better cool them off
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.72,0:07:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则他们就会从赌博嫖娼升级到更恶劣的行为 \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}before they move from gambling and whoring
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.89,0:07:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,造成的破坏修复起来又要花很多钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to sins that are more costly to repair.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.57,0:07:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  梅芙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is the matter, Maeve?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.04,0:07:27.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的眼睛里有什么东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Something in your eye.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.18,0:07:43.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他妈能杀了它吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Aw, can you fucking kill it?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.21,0:07:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jesus.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.25,0:08:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么耽误了这么久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's the hold up?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.27,0:08:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要把那个放在下一趟运输车的最上层\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need that one on the next shuttle topside.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.44,0:08:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没处理完她  稍等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not finished with her yet. Hang on.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.11,0:08:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的腹部还有一颗子弹要取出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've got another bullet fragment to remove from her abdomen.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.74,0:08:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,质保部要求将她立即送过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}QA wants her back on the floor now.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.26,0:08:38.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把她修补下  然后放到...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just patch her and get her on the...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.04,0:08:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,...触碰到我嘴边的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}touch the tip of my tongue...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.58,0:08:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都很乐意忘掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm happy to forget.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.30,0:08:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了那个来自阿比林的牛仔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Except that cowpoke from Abilene.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.75,0:08:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他胯下那玩意儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That thing he was packing--
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.41,0:08:48.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那倒是让我终身难忘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that was something to remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.26,0:08:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他对那玩意儿的灵活使用简直...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The way he used that thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.79,0:10:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不会把这归为正常的接待员行为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I would not characterize this as normal host behavior.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.17,0:10:16.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你将之描述成符合正常范围的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yet you're describing it as within normal parameters.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.81,0:10:18.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它没有伤害我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, it didn't hurt us.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.11,0:10:19.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它的行为很反常\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Its behavior was unconventional.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.81,0:10:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它用一块石头砸碎了自己的脑袋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It smashed its own head in with a rock.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.07,0:10:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可能只是其撒玛利亚人反射的表现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It is possible that it's a manifestation of its Samaritan reflex.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.24,0:10:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有可能这种行为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And it's also possible that behavior
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.19,0:10:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会为此类问题树立专有的解决办法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}takes a proprietary approach to problems like this
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.61,0:10:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他们搞砸的时候  就可以不用承认了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to avoid having to admit when they fuck up.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.84,0:10:43.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知不知道它为什么会偏离循环\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do we have any idea what caused it to go off loop?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.24,0:10:45.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道  但我希望能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, but I am hoping
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.57,0:10:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恢复它的一些认知功能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to recover some of its cognition.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.38,0:10:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们成功地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We managed to
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.42,0:10:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在分解加剧之前  稳定了它的脑部\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}stabilize its wetware before there was too much decomposition.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.76,0:10:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.20,0:10:58.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Interesting.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.26,0:10:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底能不能从这玩意中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is there any hope of actually
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.58,0:11:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提取出一些东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}extracting something from this?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.82,0:11:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们可以试试  -不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- We can try. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.26,0:11:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在由我的团队接手调查\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My team will take over the investigation now.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.25,0:11:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的团队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your team?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.63,0:11:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你开玩笑吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you kidding me?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.58,0:11:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  这家伙连个揉成团的纸巾都打不开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, this guy couldn't debug a balled-up napkin.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.25,0:11:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你希望我们弄清楚到底出了什么问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If-- if you would like us to figure out what went wrong here,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.26,0:11:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要有获取的权限\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we need to be allowed to access it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.02,0:11:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有第二次机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No more second chances.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.63,0:11:23.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从今以后  质保部门会负责处理此类问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}QA will handle events like this from now on.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.43,0:11:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有意见吗  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is that going to be a problem, Bernard?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.11,0:11:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都有很多工作要忙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We've all got plenty of work on our plates.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.99,0:11:31.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你们想接手这个  没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you guys want to take this one, fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.34,0:11:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结束之后给我们一份调查报告就行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just get us a copy of the postmortem when it's done.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.30,0:11:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's get started.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.66,0:11:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直认为你给我这份工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, I always figured you gave me this job
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.66,0:11:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为我有话直说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because I speak my mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.63,0:11:48.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是这样  -很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I did. - Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.88,0:11:50.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你一出现就直接屈服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I would've preferred you not show up at all
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.37,0:11:52.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你还是别出现为好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if the first thing you were going to do is cave.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.30,0:11:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们认为我们有所隐瞒  -我们没有啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- They think we're not telling them something. - And we're not!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.18,0:11:57.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在明显出现了一种行为模式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There is clearly a pattern of behavior here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.74,0:11:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最早是艾伯纳西  现在又来一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}First there was Abernathy, and now there's this.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.17,0:12:02.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我见过出现幻听的接待员  还有爬上山顶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, I've got hosts imagining voices and climbing mountaintops
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.63,0:12:04.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去研究星象图的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to consult their astrological chart.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.23,0:12:06.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是什么小故障\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is not a fucking glitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.39,0:12:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道为什么  你不想让我告诉别人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And for some reason, you don't want me to tell anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.39,0:12:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像除了我之外  这里所有人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It is like everybody around here
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.67,0:12:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都在打着自己的小算盘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}has got some kind of fucking agenda except for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.75,0:12:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有...怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And-- what?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.15,0:12:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得我刚开始在这里工作的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I remember when I first started here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.59,0:12:21.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接待员看起来都栩栩如生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The hosts seemed very lifelike.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.82,0:12:24.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会开始对他们的行为进行过度解读\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You begin to read things into their behaviors.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.68,0:12:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别一副高高在上的样子  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Don't be patronizing. - Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.64,0:12:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接待员不会想象  但你会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The hosts don't imagine things, you do.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.87,0:12:34.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是猎户座\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's not Orion.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.03,0:12:36.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猎户座腰带上只有三颗星  不是四颗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There are three stars in Orion's Belt, not four.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.46,0:12:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定很冷吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You must be cold.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.90,0:12:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿上这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Take that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.46,0:12:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.57,0:13:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.28,0:13:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得带她回甜水镇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We gotta take her back to Sweetwater.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.18,0:13:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你开玩笑吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you fucking kidding?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.91,0:13:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗根  你知道她不属于这外面的世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, Logan, you know she doesn't belong out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.08,0:13:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你如果现在走了  那个亡命之徒斯利姆·米勒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You leave now, that no-good outlaw Slim Miller
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.41,0:13:20.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定就抓不到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is sure to evade our grasp.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.78,0:13:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No fucking way.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.01,0:13:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你带我来当这个傻逼赏金猎人的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You were the one who dragged me on this stupid bounty hunt.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.53,0:13:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少我们得把这件事做完\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The least we're going to do is see it through, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.97,0:13:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能带着她追捕犯人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can't take her on a bounty hunt.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.49,0:13:34.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你这么担心她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you're so concerned about her well-being,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.53,0:13:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我一枪爆了她的头就好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll just blow her brains out,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.18,0:13:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,园区会派人来回收她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and then the park will come get her.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.83,0:13:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能不能别总想着杀人操逼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you please stop trying to just kill or fuck everything?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.49,0:13:46.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now I get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.85,0:13:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.92,0:13:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,园区派她过来  好让你终于\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The park sent her so that you will finally
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.15,0:13:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能对某件事上心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}have something to give a shit about.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.63,0:13:54.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  控制中心的人肯定是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, yeah, I'm sure the people at the controls
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.27,0:13:55.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时刻监视着我的情绪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}are monitoring my every mood.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.43,0:13:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们就是这么做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's exactly what they're doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.50,0:13:59.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  难道你认为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, you really think it's a coincidence
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.97,0:14:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在甜水镇唯一会报以微笑的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that the only thing that you even smiled at back in Sweetwater
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.85,0:14:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这么出现在你面前只是个巧合吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}just happened to drop into your lap?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.20,0:14:10.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是公司为什么想对这里增持股份的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is why the company needs to bump our stake in this place.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.38,0:14:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们能让你拥有使命感\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They can even give you a sense of purpose.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.23,0:14:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说这趟旅程是为了欢迎我加入你们家族\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You said the trip was about welcoming me to the family.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.59,0:14:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实是公事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is business?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.61,0:14:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威廉  对我们家族而言  所有事都是公事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}With our family, William, everything is business.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.64,0:14:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得继续前进了  先生们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We better get a move on, gentlemen.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.59,0:15:01.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该就是这里了  劳伦斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This should be the place, Lawrence.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.72,0:15:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血河\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The Blood Arroyo.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.41,0:15:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有很多蛇  但都不会生蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Plenty of snakes, but none of the egg-laying variety.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.66,0:15:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你杀了我妻子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You killed my wife,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.22,0:15:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀了我家族的一群人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}severely pruned my family tree
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.16,0:15:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就为了找个什么迷宫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}all in pursuit of some goddamn maze.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.02,0:15:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底想找什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The hell you hope to find, anyway?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.95,0:15:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这整个世界就是一个故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This whole world is a story.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.87,0:15:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我每页都读过  除了最后一页\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've read every page except the last one.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.16,0:15:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得搞清楚结局如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need to find out how it ends.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.38,0:15:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要知道这一切意义何在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want to know what this all means.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.19,0:15:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧  这就是为什么我一直没念书识字\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See, now that's why I never learned to read.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.77,0:15:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们何不忘了那条该死的蛇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why don't we forget about this damn snake,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.50,0:15:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧去珀里亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}head to Pariah?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.24,0:15:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在那儿的朋友能帮我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My friends there can help us.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.31,0:15:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你朋友那没有我要找的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, your friends have nothing I'm looking for,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.64,0:15:46.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这趟旅程没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}not this trip.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.87,0:15:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Besides...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.26,0:15:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还是找到那条蛇了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think we found our snake after all.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.22,0:16:08.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可耻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Shame on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.40,0:16:10.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你昨天还是有妇之夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You were a married man up until yesterday.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.93,0:16:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她吗  不可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Her? Hell, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.13,0:16:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢有点泼辣的女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I like a little fire in my women.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.37,0:16:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她上过的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The only thing she's ever mounted
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.33,0:16:19.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕只有死人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}are dead heads on sticks.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.46,0:16:21.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该快点离开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We should get the fuck out of--
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.01,0:16:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我们的马又找到不少食物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We found some more food for the horses.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.06,0:16:34.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.22,0:16:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们饿得都变得脾气很暴躁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They were starting to get ornery.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.38,0:16:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和朋友只是在欣赏你的纹身\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My friend and I were just admiring your tattoo.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.24,0:16:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想知道其背后的故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'd love to know the story behind it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.72,0:16:46.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你的帽子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I like your hat.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.11,0:16:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我会把它留下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe I'll keep it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.15,0:16:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的都喂马吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The horses can have the rest of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.65,0:16:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们为何从未谋面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How in hell have we never met?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.78,0:16:56.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很明显是我的疏忽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Clearly a terrible oversight on my part.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.15,0:17:00.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能问一句  你前往何处吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where, may I ask, are you headed?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.12,0:17:07.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去拿回一些有价值的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}To retrieve something of great value.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.39,0:17:10.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你有点人手不足\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You look a little shorthanded.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.30,0:17:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们人手很充足\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We got enough men.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.22,0:17:22.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你有人手空缺了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Seems like you got a couple positions open.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.79,0:17:35.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一个接待员严重脱离了她的循环\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We've got a host making a pretty big deviation from her loop.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.72,0:17:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哪个  -甜水镇农场主的女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Which one? - The rancher's daughter from Sweetwater.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.17,0:17:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.18,0:17:44.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她在陪游客吗  -不清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Is she accompanying a guest? - Unclear.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.92,0:17:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板的新故事线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The boss is disrupting so many storylines
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.18,0:17:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打乱了很多情节  所以很难说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}with his new narrative, it's hard to tell.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.92,0:17:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把她标记给行为部门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Flag her with behavior.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.08,0:17:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们今天就能把她拉出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They can pull her today.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.44,0:17:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确保一切如常\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Make sure everything's checking out.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.18,0:18:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.06,0:18:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这镇子真漂亮  这是你的家乡吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a lovely town. Is this your home?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.99,0:18:40.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来自哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, where are you from?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.99,0:18:42.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Same as you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.14,0:18:44.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不记得了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't you remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.46,0:18:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.19,0:19:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ma'am?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.16,0:19:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说艾伯纳西农场有个女孩失踪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Got word a girl went missing from Abernathy Ranch.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.07,0:19:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是来自那里吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is that where you belong?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.63,0:19:14.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸爸肯定很担心你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sure your daddy's worried about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.87,0:19:33.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父亲死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My father's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.99,0:19:37.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not going back.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.18,0:19:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's going on here?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.10,0:19:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是在帮助一个迷路的游人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, just helping a lost traveler.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.71,0:19:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她没迷路  她是跟我一起的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's not lost, she's with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.61,0:19:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.67,0:19:59.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-祝你们早安  -谢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Y'all have a nice morning. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.42,0:20:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有关于斯利姆的线索了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, we got a lead on Slim.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.49,0:20:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你愿意  可以留在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can stay here if you want,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.46,0:20:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到时候折返回来接你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I'll just circle back and get you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.15,0:20:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我觉得自己需要继续走下去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I think I need to keep going.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.66,0:20:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.12,0:20:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来她需要确保\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Apparently, she needs to make certain
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.70,0:20:31.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们要找的东西在他们认为的那个地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}this thing they're looking for is where they think it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.95,0:20:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说如果消息没问题  就给我们信号\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She said she'd signal if the information was good.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.12,0:20:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来这就是信号了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Guess that's the signal.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.25,0:21:18.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉给你和朋友带来了不便\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry if I caused trouble with you and your friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.59,0:21:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  没有  没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, no, no. No, it's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.84,0:21:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴你找到了我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm glad you found us.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.56,0:21:24.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没问你要去哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't get a chance to ask where you're headed.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.24,0:21:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't really know yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.25,0:21:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为他们会把你们放在特定的地区或者路上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I guess I figured they kept you in zones or on paths or...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.98,0:21:40.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前相信每个人都有自己的路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I used to believe there was a path for everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.17,0:21:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我发现自己从未想过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now I think I never asked
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.59,0:21:45.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那条路会把我带往何方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}where that path was taking me.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.76,0:21:54.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会在秋天把牲口赶下山\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We would bring the herd down off the mountain in the fall.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.79,0:21:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时我们会在路上弄丢一只\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sometimes we would lose one along the way,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.83,0:21:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会很担心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I'd worry over it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.90,0:22:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My father...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.98,0:22:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父亲会告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My father would tell me...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.06,0:22:13.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们自会找到回家的路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that the steer would find its own way home.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.85,0:22:15.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常  它们都会回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And, often as not, they did.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.50,0:22:19.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从未想过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Never occurred to me that
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.58,0:22:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们带它们回来是为了屠宰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we were bring them back for the slaughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.34,0:22:31.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在要怎样找到自己的路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How are you going to find your way now?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.36,0:22:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你或许不会明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not sure you'll understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.21,0:22:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时我感觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sometimes I feel...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.57,0:22:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么东西在呼唤我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}like something's calling me.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.68,0:22:58.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我在这以外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Telling me there's a place for me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.92,0:23:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个地方在等我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}somewhere beyond all this.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.09,0:23:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白这种感觉  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, I know that feeling, Dolores.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.79,0:23:07.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白这种感觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know that feeling.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.26,0:23:13.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你真的不想回归以前的生活吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But you really don't want to go back to your old life?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.57,0:23:48.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.83,0:23:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.59,0:23:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打了个寒颤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just got a chill.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.35,0:24:01.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅此而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.79,0:24:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们还是回篝火边坐着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's-- let's go back to the fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.66,0:24:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该是累坏了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're probably exhausted.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.38,0:24:19.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-直接跟他说  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Just talk to him. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.67,0:24:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh, excuse me, sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.42,0:24:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕我冒昧打扰  但我必须说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't want to intrude, but I just had to say
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.40,0:24:30.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我十分敬仰您\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that I'm such an admirer of yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.38,0:24:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您设的基金救了我妹妹的...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your foundation literally saved my sister's--
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.22,0:24:35.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说一个字我就割开你的喉咙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}One more word and I'll cut your throat.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.12,0:24:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.92,0:24:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我他妈是来度假的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is my fucking vacation.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.04,0:24:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然  他们要找的东西在欧哈监狱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Apparently, whatever they're looking for is in the Ojal prison.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.78,0:24:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些疯子计划从北方军骑兵队手里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}These lunatics plan to steal a cannon
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.15,0:25:00.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷走一门大炮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}from the Union cavalry unit.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.21,0:25:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炸出一条路杀进去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Blast their way in.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.70,0:25:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没时间玩这么幼稚的游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't have time for color-by-numbers bullshit.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.58,0:25:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我天一亮就出发\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll ride at dawn.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.41,0:25:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要什么  我会从监狱弄出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll go get whatever you want out of that prison
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.61,0:25:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲自带给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and bring it back myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.32,0:25:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前提是你能活着出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Suppose you make it out alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.92,0:25:23.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你开价多少\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's your price?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.40,0:25:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要几个字\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nothing but a few words.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.04,0:25:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想知道你纹身背后的故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want the story behind your tattoo.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.56,0:25:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么会有兴趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's your interest in it?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.84,0:25:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听说过一个叫阿诺德的人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You ever heard of a man named Arnold?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.45,0:25:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他算是最早在这些地方定居的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You could say he was the original settler of these parts.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.06,0:25:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他创造了一个供人们为所欲为的世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He created a world where you could do anything you want,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.84,0:25:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}except one thing--
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.34,0:25:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这里死不了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you can't die.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.52,0:25:52.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说无论这个世界多么接近真实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Which means no matter how real this world seems,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.67,0:25:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仍然不过是场游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it's still just a game.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.32,0:25:58.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但后来阿诺德打破了自己定下的规矩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But then Arnold went and broke his own rule.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.40,0:26:02.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就死在这座乐园里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He died right here in the park.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.15,0:26:07.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我相信他还有一个故事剩下没讲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Except I believe he had one story left to tell.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.59,0:26:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个充满真正的危险和暴力的故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A story with real stakes, real violence.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.50,0:26:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以说我来这里是为了尊崇他的遗志\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You could say I'm here to honor his legacy.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.39,0:26:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为你身上的纹身\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I think your tattoo
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.63,0:26:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谜局的下一部分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is the next piece of the puzzle.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.57,0:26:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你愿意赌吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, do we have a wager?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.18,0:26:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要闯进监狱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You aim to break into a prison
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.01,0:26:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,独自带出20个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and take out 20 men alone?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.23,0:26:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是独自\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:35.26,0:26:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要带上这位劳伦斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll take Lawrence here.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.10,0:26:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还需要一根火柴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I'll need one match.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.24,0:26:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一根火柴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}One match,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.27,0:26:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一把手枪  加一个白痴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}one pistol, and one idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.94,0:26:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我愿意赌一把\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll take those odds.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.97,0:27:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算这一路上都对我沉默以对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You gonna give me the silent treatment the whole way there?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.26,0:27:18.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你本该任我被绞死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You should've left me hanging from those gallows.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.71,0:27:20.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少我还能安详地死去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}At least I could've died in peace
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.27,0:27:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用忍受你的抱怨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}without having to hear you yammer.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.53,0:27:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜你没火吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't suppose you have a light?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.53,0:27:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,车里禁止抽烟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No smoking in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.69,0:27:37.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常情况下  那当然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Normally, I'm sure,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.71,0:27:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这是你能抽到的最好的烟草\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but this is the finest tobacco a man can enjoy.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.45,0:27:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在外国妞儿丰腴的大腿上用手卷成\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hand-rolled on the ample thighs of exotic women.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.05,0:27:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许你也该试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Perhaps you'd like to try one yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.82,0:28:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,选择  劳伦斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Choices, Lawrence.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.40,0:28:05.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对自己说  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, you tell yourself
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.07,0:28:06.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在就像是我案板上的鱼肉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you've been at the mercy of mine
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.69,0:28:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这样你就不用费心为自己考虑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because it spares you consideration of your own.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.98,0:28:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为如果你真的考虑过自己的选择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because if you did consider your choices,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.63,0:28:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你将不得不面对一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you'd be confronted with a truth
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.94,0:28:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你无法理解的真相\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you could not comprehend--
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.48,0:28:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做出的选择都并非自主选择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that no choice you ever made was your own.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.57,0:28:22.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直都是个囚犯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have always been a prisoner.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.90,0:28:31.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我告诉你  我是来释放你的呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What if I told you I'm here to set you free?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.71,0:28:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.66,0:29:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷马贼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Horse thieves.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.89,0:29:05.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的白痴  几乎当着我们的面开枪打死了几个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Damn fools shot up a couple of pokes practically in front of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.16,0:29:06.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我见到的唯一一个白痴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, the only fool I see
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.20,0:29:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是站在我面前的这位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is the one standing right in front of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.69,0:29:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警官  你拘捕了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Deputy, you have there in your custody
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.43,0:29:12.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三地最大的通缉犯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the most wanted man in three territories--
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.66,0:29:19.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,劳伦斯·佩德罗·马里亚·冈萨雷斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lawrence Pedro Maria Gonzalez.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.74,0:29:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说你法场脱身的事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Heard you slipped the rope.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.74,0:29:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还害死了几个好人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dropped some damn good men in exchange.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.53,0:29:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的说法是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The way he tells it,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.76,0:29:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他更喜欢被行刑队执行枪决\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}he's more partial to a firing squad.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.70,0:29:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们很乐意成全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I reckon we'll be happy to oblige.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.27,0:29:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我他妈要杀了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna fucking kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.36,0:29:48.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许等将来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe someday.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.67,0:29:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他和那个人关一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lock him up with the other man.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.25,0:30:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,享受雪茄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Enjoy the cigars.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.83,0:30:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去你妈的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go fuck yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.77,0:30:08.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And just who are you supposed to be?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.40,0:30:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的救命恩人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your salvation.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:40.29,0:30:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我们之前没见过吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't believe we've ever met.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.28,0:30:44.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  确实没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, we haven't.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.19,0:30:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直以来似乎都是个...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, you always seemed like a--
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.51,0:30:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经过市场检验的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a market-tested kind of thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:52.97,0:30:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一杆大枪  优美的疤痕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Big gun, tasteful scar.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.28,0:30:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受限于自己的小小圈子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Locked in your little cycle
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.53,0:31:02.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像追自己尾巴的珍贵狮子狗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}like a prized poodle after its own tail.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.06,0:31:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听起来好像是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You sound like a man who's grown tired
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.14,0:31:06.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活的不耐烦了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}of wearing his guts on the inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.27,0:31:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没必要这么生气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's no need to get testy.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.76,0:31:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是对你的世界观很好奇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm just curious about your worldview.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.76,0:31:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某种半土著的乱七八糟的东西吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Some kind of half-native mumbo jumbo?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.50,0:31:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很简单\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's simple.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.87,0:31:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为只有真正的勇者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I believe that only the truly brave
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.97,0:31:22.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才敢于正视这个世界  并明白世间的一切...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}can look at the world and understand that all of it--
Dialogue: 0,0:31:23.60,0:31:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是神或是人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}gods, men,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.06,0:31:29.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有其他一切  都终将以悲剧收尾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}everything else-- will end badly.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.62,0:31:32.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人可以被拯救\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No one will be saved.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.57,0:31:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那或许我们的共同点比我想的要多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe we've got more in common than I thought.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.26,0:31:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What about you?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.94,0:31:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎样的命运转折让你流落至此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What turns of fate have brought you here?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.09,0:31:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说来话长\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a long story.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.21,0:31:44.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没那个闲工夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And we don't have the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.63,0:31:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惜我们的时间可比你那朋友多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Got more time than your friend, sadly.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.55,0:31:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再过几天  我的朋友们就会来救我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It will be a few more days before my friends show up.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.47,0:31:51.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Three days.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.86,0:31:52.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常情况下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Normally.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.78,0:31:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕我等不及了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm afraid I don't have time for that,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.49,0:31:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们现在就走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so we're leaving now.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.61,0:32:04.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收到制造烟火效果的请求\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've got a request for a pyrotechnic effect.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.94,0:32:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶魔  低当量  两个装药\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Los Diablos, low-yield, two charges.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.88,0:32:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,批准\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Approved.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.05,0:32:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在授权\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Authorizing.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.53,0:32:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟上  赫克托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Step lively, Hector.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.10,0:32:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有遗言吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Any last words?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.96,0:32:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧动手吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get it over with.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.42,0:33:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我操\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Motherfucker.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.34,0:33:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一根火柴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}One match.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.14,0:33:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很有能力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're a capable man.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.37,0:33:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去的地方你能帮上忙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We could do with your help where we're going.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.84,0:33:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Afraid not.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:53.94,0:33:55.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们欠你个人情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We owe you a debt.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:55.62,0:33:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你这位朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, your friend here
Dialogue: 0,0:33:57.27,0:33:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只欠我一两句话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}simply owes me a word or two.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.40,0:34:00.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说出来就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That'll do.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.59,0:34:02.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给个建议...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And a word of advice--
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.90,0:34:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们要找的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that thing you're looking for?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.68,0:34:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不可能在那个保险箱里是找到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're never gonna find it in that safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.44,0:34:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们闯进我们镇子时我才7岁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was seven when they rode into my town.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.19,0:34:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有着魔鬼犄角  带着面具的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Masked men in devils' horns.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.76,0:34:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们杀光所有人...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They killed everyone--
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.83,0:34:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妇女  幼童  连牲口都不放过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}women, children, even the animals.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.26,0:34:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们把我母亲从下巴劈开到裆部\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They gutted my mother from her jaw to her sex.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.03,0:34:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不得不把她温热的鲜血\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I had to paint her warm blood
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.13,0:34:45.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,涂满我的全身\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}over my skin to make sure
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.76,0:34:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他们以为我死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that they would think I was dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:48.08,0:34:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我长大后开始追杀他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Every one of them I tracked down,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.55,0:34:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会把死在我手下之人的血再次涂满全身\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I used their blood to paint my skin again.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.70,0:34:56.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只剩下一个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Only one man left.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:58.05,0:34:59.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛇头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The head of the snake.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.88,0:35:04.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫什么名字\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's his name?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.77,0:35:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有很多名字\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He has many names.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:09.94,0:35:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大多数人叫他怀亚特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Most know him as Wyatt.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.16,0:36:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  小姑娘  这...这是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, little girl, what-- what is this?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.51,0:36:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What does it mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.56,0:36:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别白费口舌了  女士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't waste your breath, lady.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:18.63,0:36:21.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那属于他们所谓的宗教\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That thing's part of their so-called religion.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.96,0:36:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人会告诉你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ain't none of them's gonna tell you nothing about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.72,0:36:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一小时5块钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's $5 for an hour,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:34.78,0:36:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你先洗澡就4块\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}4 if you bathe first.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.48,0:36:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们只点一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, if we just get the one,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.00,0:36:43.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我第二个上  能不能打个折\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}do I get a discount for being second and all?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.83,0:36:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我们能商量出解决办法的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sure we can work something out.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:46.99,0:36:47.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.27,0:37:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个高个子  我以前见过他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The tall one, I've seen him before,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.46,0:37:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的画像贴在邮局窗口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}hanging in the window of the post office.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:05.62,0:37:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,土匪吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bandits?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.76,0:37:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得他们来是有目的的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you think they're here for something?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.10,0:37:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得他们可不仅仅是来操女人的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think they're interested in more than a turn at Franny's backside.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.12,0:37:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得他是赫克托的同伙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think he rides with Hector.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:14.94,0:37:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传闻跟野蛮人一起生活的就是他吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is that the one they say lives out with the savages?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.01,0:37:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's the one.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:34.07,0:37:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要走了吗  我才刚到呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Taking off? I just got here.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.64,0:37:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经给了我需要的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You gave me what I needed.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.07,0:37:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是这个作用吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, is that all I'm good for?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:41.78,0:37:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮你缓解压力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Letting off a little stress?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.10,0:37:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁说我有压力了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who says I'm stressed?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.28,0:37:47.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你表现得挺明显了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have your tells.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.11,0:37:52.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, yes, Bernard,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:52.05,0:37:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,观察大师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}master of observation.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.94,0:38:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天我得找福特谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tomorrow I have to talk to Ford.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:05.32,0:38:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.63,0:38:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在园区制造混乱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's creating chaos in the park.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:09.12,0:38:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,董事会的人随时会来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And the board will be descending at any moment.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.31,0:38:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要争取点时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need to buy some time.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:14.80,0:38:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我给点建议吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Some advice?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.00,0:38:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好不要让他发现你很紧张或有防御性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Best to not show him you're nervous or defensive.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:20.21,0:38:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有什么好防御的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have nothing to be defensive about.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.92,0:38:24.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就不要交叉双臂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then don't cross your arms.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.52,0:38:27.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是一种古老的直觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's an ancient instinct.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.59,0:38:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何动物的肚子都是最脆弱的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The belly is the most vulnerable part of every animal.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.88,0:38:35.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我比作惊恐的野兽  竟然还挺性感的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's so sexy being compared to a frightened beast.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.64,0:38:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就对了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:38.68,0:38:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是你该有的姿态\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's the posture you're looking for.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:47.86,0:38:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sometimes,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.92,0:38:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管你尽了最大的努力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}despite your best efforts,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.99,0:38:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你其实本来就那么迷人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you can actually be quite charming.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.46,0:39:11.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邻居来投诉了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Have the neighbors complained?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:11.88,0:39:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该说  他们在问各种问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Safe to say, they're asking questions.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:14.72,0:39:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然这些石头很难移开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The rocks would prefer not to move,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.74,0:39:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们还是要把它们清除\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but we shall move them yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.15,0:39:24.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我能帮帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Perhaps I can help you with that.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.59,0:39:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在开发的故事线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The narrative you're creating
Dialogue: 0,0:39:26.97,0:39:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是一项大工程\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is clearly a massive endeavor.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.89,0:39:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你需要更多时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you need more time,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:30.13,0:39:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得董事会肯定会乐意照顾一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sure the board would be happy to oblige.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:32.73,0:39:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们肯定更加乐意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sure they'd be happier
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.93,0:39:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我无限期推迟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for me to delay it indefinitely.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.12,0:39:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.92,0:39:53.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You imagine I have gone mad...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:53.83,0:39:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.25,0:39:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失去了理智\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lost my way?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.14,0:39:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是担心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're simply concerned
Dialogue: 0,0:39:57.50,0:40:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你即将带来的改变程度过大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}about the extent of the changes you're making.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.76,0:40:03.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想保护你的遗产\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We want to protect your legacy.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:03.17,0:40:04.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的遗产\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My legacy?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:10.89,0:40:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是很喜欢这个地方  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't like this place very much, do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:13.71,0:40:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多年来  我见过很多你这样的人来来去去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've seen many of you come and go over the years,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.29,0:40:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能看出谁喜欢这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I can tell the ones who enjoy their time here
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.40,0:40:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而谁不喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and the ones who don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.39,0:40:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我挺欣赏的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I admire it,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.12,0:40:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里的大胆风格\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the audacity of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.13,0:40:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都忘了这里有多美\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've forgotten how beautiful it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:29.09,0:40:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我小时候跟父母来过一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I came here once as a child with my parents.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:32.01,0:40:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们甚至就在这张桌子边坐过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think we even sat at this table.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:34.19,0:40:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许...也许是那张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or maybe-- maybe that one.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:43.46,0:40:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开始在这里工作时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When I started working here,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.86,0:40:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我意识到我不会喜欢这个地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I realized this place wasn't something I would enjoy.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.20,0:40:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一开始  我想象一切都会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In the beginning, I imagined things would be
Dialogue: 0,0:40:56.51,0:40:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常平衡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}perfectly balanced.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.26,0:41:03.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我甚至为此和我的搭档阿诺德打赌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Even had a bet with my partner, Arnold, to that effect.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.15,0:41:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们编了一百条充满希望的故事线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We made a hundred hopeful storylines.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.83,0:41:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了  几乎没人接受那些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Of course, almost no one took us up on them.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:07.65,0:41:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我输了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I lost the bet.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:10.25,0:41:14.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿诺德总是对人类抱有一些阴暗的看法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Arnold always held a somewhat dim view of people.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:14.53,0:41:16.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他更喜欢接待员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He preferred the hosts.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.52,0:41:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他求我不要引入你们这些人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He begged me to not let you people in,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.88,0:41:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些投资者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the moneymen.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:20.42,0:41:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像提洛岛一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Delos.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:21.82,0:41:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我告诉他我们会没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I told him we'd be fine,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:22.94,0:41:25.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们并不知道你们所花的钱  是用来建设什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that you didn't understand what you were paying for.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:26.01,0:41:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是什么商业投机  不是什么主题公园\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not a business venture, not a theme park,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:29.54,0:41:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是一整个世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but an entire world.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:33.12,0:41:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每一分一毫都是我们设计的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We designed every inch of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.71,0:41:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每片草叶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Every blade of grass.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:47.20,0:41:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里  我们就是神\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In here, we were gods.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:49.86,0:41:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们只是我们的客人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you were merely our guests.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:13.27,0:42:15.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那阿诺德结局如何呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And how did that work out for Arnold?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.65,0:42:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不幸  他丧失了远见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sadly, he lost his perspective.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:19.78,0:42:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He went mad.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:22.53,0:42:24.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有  你也清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I haven't, as you well know.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:24.93,0:42:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看事情  一直非常清楚透彻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have always seen things very clearly.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:35.87,0:42:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和我父母当年就坐在这张桌子边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is the table I sat at with my parents.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.67,0:42:43.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就坐在这张椅子上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is the chair I sat in.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:45.75,0:42:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们对客人了如指掌  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We know everything about our guests, don't we?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:47.97,0:42:51.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们对我们的员工也是如此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}As we know everything about our employees.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:53.52,0:42:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你小心伯纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I do hope you will be careful with Bernard.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:59.46,0:43:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的性情很敏感\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He has a sensitive disposition.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.66,0:43:08.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常抱歉  小姐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I beg your pardon, señorita.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:16.65,0:43:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些年来有很多你这样的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There have been many of you over the years,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:19.71,0:43:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一直  几乎一直\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and we have always-- almost always
Dialogue: 0,0:43:22.07,0:43:24.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都能想办法解决\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}found a way to make it work.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:24.59,0:43:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  我客气地请求你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, I will ask you nicely,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:29.64,0:43:31.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}please...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:31.46,0:43:33.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要挡我的道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}don't get in my way.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:48.70,0:43:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,董事会会同意我的意见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The board will agree with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:51.49,0:43:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会派代表来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They'll be sending a representative.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:53.73,0:43:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他们已经派人来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But they already have.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:55.14,0:43:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为他们会告诉你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought they would've told you.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:59.63,0:44:01.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了  摩奴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That won't be necessary, Manu.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:01.63,0:44:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用再来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:03.37,0:44:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以和其他人一起走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can join the others.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:21.63,0:44:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以告诉董事会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can tell the board that
Dialogue: 0,0:44:22.75,0:44:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会及时完成我的故事线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}my narrative will be completed on time,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:25.54,0:44:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会是怀旧的风格\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and it won't be a retrospective,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:29.11,0:44:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信你们都恐惧会是那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}as I'm sure you have all feared.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:39.35,0:44:41.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是多愁善感之人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not the sentimental type.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:52.14,0:44:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍尔登说斯利姆带了一大帮手下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Holden says this Slim's got a whole gang with him,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:56.02,0:44:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我要你留在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so I need you to stay here.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:58.43,0:44:59.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你们寡不敌众\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you're outnumbered,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:59.27,0:45:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最不该的就是让一个人袖手旁观\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the last thing you need is somebody standing by.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:01.27,0:45:03.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我可以帮忙  -不  不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I can help. - No, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:05.14,0:45:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你也许不懂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know it doesn't make any sense to you,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:06.58,0:45:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我在这不会受伤  而你却会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but I can't get hurt in there, but you can.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:08.95,0:45:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想看到你受伤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I would hate to see that happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:10.77,0:45:14.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待在这里  好吗  注意安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just stay here. Okay? Be safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:26.24,0:45:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你享受到告别之吻了吗  -闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Did you get a good-bye kiss? - Shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:27.93,0:45:30.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的  如果明天之前你还没上她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Seriously, if you don't bang her by tomorrow,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:30.08,0:45:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她就归我了  -好了  听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I'm calling dibs. - Okay, listen up.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:32.40,0:45:34.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一会儿场面会非常混乱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's gonna be a bag of nails in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:34.13,0:45:36.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯利姆和他的手下人数太多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Slim and his boys got us outnumbered.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:36.77,0:45:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最关键的是  这地方是由一个家庭经营的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}On top of that, there's a family runs this place.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:40.20,0:45:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,善良的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good people.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:41.28,0:45:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须确保那狼心狗肺的混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need to make sure that snake-hearted son of a bitch
Dialogue: 0,0:45:43.26,0:45:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没有试图...  -是是是  懂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- doesn't try to-- - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:44.69,0:45:46.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冒险  赏金  我们懂的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Risk, reward. We got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:46.40,0:45:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  我们把这些混蛋杀个爽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on. Let's go fuck these fuckers up.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:52.37,0:45:54.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那他妈是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The fuck is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:56.03,0:45:57.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你看我像条狗吗  -不  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I look like a dog to you? - No, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:00.15,0:46:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿这些喂狗去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Feed that to them.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:05.63,0:46:07.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该拔枪了  狗杂种\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Slap leather, cocksuckers.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:07.33,0:46:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, God!
Dialogue: 0,0:46:35.02,0:46:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我告诉过你的  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did I fucking tell you, or what?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:11.58,0:47:12.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,升级版\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Upgrade.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:13.05,0:47:14.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:17.28,0:47:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我爱抱怨  但这真是鲁莽的行为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ain't normally the type to complain, but this is just foolhardy.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:20.95,0:47:23.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人去和怀亚特较量\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Two men taking on Wyatt.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:23.21,0:47:26.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你再多嘴  我就把马收回  劳伦斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Keep talking, and I'm gonna take the horse back, Lawrence.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:26.39,0:47:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀亚特手下的怪胎们刚刚消灭了上一支\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wyatt's freaks just wiped out the last group
Dialogue: 0,0:47:28.78,0:47:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前去搜寻他的小队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that went seeking him out.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:31.88,0:47:35.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而现在我们正骑马跟踪他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And here we are riding right after him.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:38.32,0:47:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想说服你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm just trying to convince you
Dialogue: 0,0:47:40.73,0:47:44.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别让我俩像个局外人一样被杀死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}not to get yourself and me as a bystander killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:44.54,0:47:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会让自己被杀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not gonna get myself killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:48.21,0:47:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别以为我没听出这其中的差别\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't think I didn't notice that distinction.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:11.24,0:48:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来怀亚特的手下还留下了一人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Looks like Wyatt's men left somebody behind after all.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:17.30,0:48:18.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰迪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Teddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:20.53,0:48:22.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早该猜到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I should've guessed.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:23.06,0:48:25.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你  结束我的痛苦吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please, put me out of my misery.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:26.82,0:48:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  泰迪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry, Teddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:30.62,0:48:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎你只剩痛苦了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It looks like misery's all you got.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:35.92,0:48:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放我下来  该死的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let me out of this, God damn it!
Dialogue: 0,0:48:38.50,0:48:40.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通缉令上写着无论死活  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That reward is dead or alive, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:40.62,0:48:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好还是活着带回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Always best to bring them in alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:42.61,0:48:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少塞上他的嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can we at least gag him?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:44.60,0:48:46.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好主意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's a fine idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:51.63,0:48:53.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Aw, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:53.12,0:48:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我知道你们是为了赏金\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, I-- I know you're in it for the money.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:54.76,0:48:56.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不是真正的执法者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You ain't no real lawman.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:56.26,0:48:57.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Shut up, you.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:57.19,0:48:59.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我老板埃尔·拉佐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, my boss, El Lazo,
Dialogue: 0,0:48:59.14,0:49:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他付你的钱  会比治安官给的多一倍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}he'll pay you twice what the marshals will
Dialogue: 0,0:49:01.22,0:49:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你给我解绑把我送去珀里亚就行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if you cut me loose and get me to Pariah.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:03.86,0:49:06.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我听好了  你个下贱的混球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Listen to me, you lowdown piece of dirt.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:06.34,0:49:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些人是不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}These men won't--
Dialogue: 0,0:49:11.06,0:49:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你他妈搞什么  -放轻松  兄弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What the fuck?! - Relax, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:13.94,0:49:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道我们有多幸运\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have no idea how lucky we just got.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:16.51,0:49:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸运  你刚打死了一个无辜的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lucky? You just shot an innocent man.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:18.22,0:49:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  他是个机器人  和她还有斯利姆一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, he's a robot, just like her and just like Slim here,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:21.48,0:49:24.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过斯利姆是埃尔·拉佐的手下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}except that Slim works for El Lazo,
Dialogue: 0,0:49:24.26,0:49:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而埃尔·拉佐则是享受公园最高刺激的入场券\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and El Lazo is our ticket to the best ride in the park.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:28.35,0:49:31.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的傻逼任务把我们引向了一个复活节彩蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your bullshit mission led us right to an Easter egg.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:34.54,0:49:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能放他走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're not going to let him go.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:36.25,0:49:37.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, well. Look at you.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:39.11,0:49:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对你越发感兴趣了  农场女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're starting to grow on me, farm girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:40.62,0:49:41.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我让开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, out of the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:44.41,0:49:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你敢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't you dare.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:45.92,0:49:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See?
Dialogue: 0,0:49:47.24,0:49:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多有趣啊  现在我们都拿枪对准一个人质\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is gonna be fun! Now we're each gonna have one.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:49.82,0:49:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不会操我的人质\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I won't fuck mine either.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:51.76,0:49:53.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真令人恶心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're disgusting.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:53.08,0:49:54.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是个小嗜好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just an acquired taste.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:54.53,0:49:56.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会慢慢爱上我的  我保证\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're gonna grow to love me, I promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:49:59.07,0:50:00.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  行吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on. Hmm?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:02.83,0:50:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:04.90,0:50:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我一起当坏人吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go black hat with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:07.53,0:50:10.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  你要去拯救这女孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, you got to, you know, save the girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:10.18,0:50:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在该给我找点事做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now give me a little something.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:11.58,0:50:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么毛病\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is your problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:12.38,0:50:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一脱离现实世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The second we get away from the real world,
Dialogue: 0,0:50:14.56,0:50:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就变成一个邪恶的混蛋了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you turn into an evil prick.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:16.27,0:50:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邪恶吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Evil?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:18.02,0:50:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这他妈是个游戏啊  比利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a fucking game, Billy!
Dialogue: 0,0:50:19.83,0:50:23.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别叫我比利  -你还想赢得她的芳心吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Don't call me Billy! - Are you still trying to impress her?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:23.03,0:50:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我保证她根本毫不在意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because I guarantee she does not give a shit
Dialogue: 0,0:50:24.81,0:50:25.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么玩这场游戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}about how you play this game.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:25.99,0:50:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧  德洛丽丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you, Dolores?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:26.84,0:50:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在说什么  威廉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's he talking about, William?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:29.05,0:50:32.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来一趟黑暗之旅  她是不会有事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She will be just fine with a trip down the dark side.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:32.82,0:50:34.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也不会有事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And so will you.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:38.14,0:50:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Trust me.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:46.83,0:50:49.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以珀里亚怎么走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, which way to Pariah?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:50.40,0:50:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来交给我就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, you just let me take it from here.
Dialogue: 0,0:50:58.68,0:51:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  好戏要来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, time for the floor show.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:00.86,0:51:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次有几位客人是赫克托的随行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Got some guests riding with Hector this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:23.76,0:51:25.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他们点靶子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's give them something to shoot at.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:26.76,0:51:28.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给几个士兵重置任务\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Retask a few of those soldiers.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:29.74,0:51:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你带着一群携带武器的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you're riding into our town
Dialogue: 0,0:51:31.51,0:51:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑进我们的小城\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}under the company of armed men,
Dialogue: 0,0:51:33.09,0:51:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你需要报上你此行所为何事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you'll need to state your business.
Dialogue: 0,0:51:35.97,0:51:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大破坏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mayhem.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:19.65,0:52:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, hello there.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:22.39,0:52:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:23.98,0:52:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这种方式找人谈谈还真有意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Interesting way of starting a conversation.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:26.95,0:52:29.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天就是个有趣的日子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, it's an interesting kind of day.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:39.15,0:52:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可爱的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, my lovely friend,
Dialogue: 0,0:52:41.94,0:52:43.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想做什么交易\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}what deal is it you want to make?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:44.78,0:52:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来取保险柜里的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're here for what's in the safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:47.62,0:52:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, how would you know that?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:49.00,0:52:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一眼就能看出想要特殊服务的男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can always tell when a man wants something that's not on the menu.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:54.45,0:52:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会给你密码\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll give you the combination
Dialogue: 0,0:52:56.40,0:52:58.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以此交换一些答案\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}in exchange for some answers.
Dialogue: 0,0:52:58.48,0:53:00.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我有你要的答案\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You assume I have any answers.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:02.74,0:53:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这世界疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This world is madness.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:06.98,0:53:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要了解关于这个的事情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want to know about this.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:11.17,0:53:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有几个在农场的家庭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've got a couple families in the homestead
Dialogue: 0,0:53:13.09,0:53:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,改了他们的既定活动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}who changed their itinerary.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:14.19,0:53:15.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们要进城了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're headed into town.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:16.06,0:53:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该20分钟左右到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Should be there in 20 minutes or so.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:17.93,0:53:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那地方血流成河\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The place is a bloodbath.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:19.73,0:53:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:21.30,0:53:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阻止他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Cut these guys off.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:22.44,0:53:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他们的武器卡壳  派出骑兵队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jam their weapons and send in the cavalry.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:33.50,0:53:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:37.84,0:53:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把他们在监狱里关一个晚上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll give them a night in lockup,
Dialogue: 0,0:53:39.40,0:53:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后让一名马里波萨的女孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}then have one of the girls at the Mariposa
Dialogue: 0,0:53:40.93,0:53:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把钥匙藏在早饭里带给他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}bring them a key hidden in their breakfast.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:43.11,0:53:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦客人们安置好了  我们来清场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If the guests are squared away, let's wrap it up.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:46.06,0:53:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是暗影\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is a shade.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:50.10,0:53:51.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神圣的本地传说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sacred native lore.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:52.41,0:53:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会做这种小人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They make figures of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:53:56.42,0:53:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,60\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}60.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:05.87,0:54:07.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暗影是做什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And what does the shade do?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:09.02,0:54:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你见过暗影吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've seen this?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:10.50,0:54:12.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:12.28,0:54:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跨越世界的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The man who walks between worlds.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:14.95,0:54:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们从地狱被派来监督我们的世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They were sent from hell to oversee our world.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:21.13,0:54:22.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,47\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}47.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:35.82,0:54:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你对我最后的要求吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is this the last thing you required of me?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:39.27,0:54:40.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们需要的时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'Cause we need a little more time
Dialogue: 0,0:54:40.93,0:54:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比警队会给的要长一些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}than the constabulary will allow.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:42.51,0:54:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  如果我对你有这种兴趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sweetheart, if I took that manner of interest in you,
Dialogue: 0,0:54:44.67,0:54:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可轮不到你说我们需要多久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you'd have no say in how long we'd need whatsoever.
Dialogue: 0,0:54:52.86,0:54:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为我疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought I was crazy,
Dialogue: 0,0:54:55.91,0:54:57.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前中了枪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but I got shot...
Dialogue: 0,0:54:58.79,0:55:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}here.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:01.76,0:55:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有伤痕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's no wound.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:03.06,0:55:04.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  但我确实中枪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, but I was shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:05.56,0:55:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这东西站在我面前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And this was standing over me.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:07.69,0:55:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后一切就像没发生过一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And then it was as if it never happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:10.21,0:55:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你切开这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want you to cut me right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:31.31,0:55:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢将手无寸铁的女人开膛破肚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not in the habit of cutting into defenseless women.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:35.00,0:55:36.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也有脸当邪恶歹徒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Some big, bad outlaw.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:36.72,0:55:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦游者说有些人能看到他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The Dreamwalker said there were some who could see them.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:42.29,0:55:44.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那是上天的恩赐  -恩赐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- That it's a blessing from God. - A blessing?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:44.65,0:55:46.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能看到操控你的主人们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}To see the masters who pull your strings.
Dialogue: 0,0:55:52.20,0:55:54.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不知道他们在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They don't know what they're talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:02.27,0:56:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想躺着死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You'd rather die lying down or...
Dialogue: 0,0:56:05.32,0:56:06.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是站着死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}up on your feet?
Dialogue: 0,0:56:08.11,0:56:09.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go to hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:28.28,0:56:29.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go on, then.
Dialogue: 0,0:56:31.25,0:56:32.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是头一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This would be the first goddamn time
Dialogue: 0,0:56:32.77,0:56:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我连续两次求一个男人对我动手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've had to ask a man to put his hands on me twice.
Dialogue: 0,0:57:00.86,0:57:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开门  艾斯卡顿  不然我们就开枪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Open up, Escaton, or we'll fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:57:04.53,0:57:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What does it mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:57:07.71,0:57:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说明我没有疯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That I'm not crazy after all.
Dialogue: 0,0:57:09.24,0:57:11.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一次机会了  艾斯卡顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Last chance, Escaton!
Dialogue: 0,0:57:11.43,0:57:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出来投降  不然我们就开枪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come out or we're shooting!
Dialogue: 0,0:57:16.74,0:57:19.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有这一切都无所谓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And that none of this matters.
